<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Vacation on The Hydrant</title>
    <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/tags/vacation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Vacation on The Hydrant</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2018 20:18:26 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://dogsbuttbrew.com/tags/vacation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>San Francisco - 2018 - Day 6</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/07/san-francisco---2018---day-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2018 20:18:26 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/07/san-francisco---2018---day-6/</guid>
      <description>Flying home is tough, but today was tougher than normal since our flight wasn&amp;rsquo;t until 8:30. I think I would almost prefer a midday flight. We theoretically had enough time to do some stuff, but we managed to accomplish all that we had set out to do in the prior 5 days. So it was going to be awkward. As I sit here, we were 3 hours early for our 8:30 PM flight to Denver, but it has been delayed by an hour, so we will be sitting here for some time!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Francisco - 2018 - Day 5</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/07/san-francisco---2018---day-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2018 20:18:22 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/07/san-francisco---2018---day-5/</guid>
      <description>Our penultimate day of vacation started out early-ish. Of course, we got out to Starbucks and had some donut holes from our new favorite donut shop in California, the creatively named &amp;ldquo;Jelly Donut,&amp;rdquo; where I can&amp;rsquo;t say I ever saw a jelly donut there&amp;hellip; I was a little nervous to be going to the wharf today because it was a weekend, so tourist traffic would be high. Our ultimate goal was to get to our whale watching tour by 3:00 which took off at the wharf, and the website gave instructions to places where you could park inexpensively for $50 a day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Francisco - 2018 - Day 4</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/07/san-francisco---2018---day-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2018 20:18:16 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/07/san-francisco---2018---day-4/</guid>
      <description>Day 4 - I finally was able to get up in time to hit the road for a run. While I&amp;rsquo;m quite out of shape, I was still able to cut 25 seconds per mile off of my new-normal running speed while in the oxygen rich California air! Almost enough to get me to go out and do it again on this trip&amp;hellip; Almost&amp;hellip;
Much like yesterday, today was about doing the things that Jenny and I had planned on doing on our last trip but were prevented from doing due to the wildfires in Wine Country.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Francisco - 2018 - Day 3</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/07/san-francisco---2018---day-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2018 22:16:20 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/07/san-francisco---2018---day-3/</guid>
      <description>Friday was all about Muir Woods. Jenny and I had planned to visit here when we came to the area last September but weren&amp;rsquo;t able to make it due to the wildfires at the time. We were lucky to have seen a sign that warned visitors that they needed a parking reservation prior to visiting. We had secured a noon parking reservation for the day, but we were a little early.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Francisco - 2018 - Day 2</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/07/san-francisco---2018---day-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2018 22:16:15 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/07/san-francisco---2018---day-2/</guid>
      <description>After some much needed sleep, we woke up fairly early-ish and took in the world famous Embassy Suites complimentary breakfast! Well, most of us did. Despite getting up in time, Ethan decided not to partake.
The first order of business, feed the addiction, off to the local Starbucks. Once that was out of the way, we were free to head downtown for a day in the city. Our first stop was Fisherman&amp;rsquo;s Wharf.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Francisco - 2018 - Day 1</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/07/san-francisco---2018---day-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 21:48:18 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/07/san-francisco---2018---day-1/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been traveling WAY too much lately. After a brief trip to Jacksonville, the boys and I went into the mountains last weekend, then I boarded a plane to Chicago on Monday only to return on Tuesday in anticipation of an early Wednesday departure to San Francisco. I&amp;rsquo;m happy I&amp;rsquo;m not sick!!! Can&amp;rsquo;t say the same for Quinton, however. Jenny called me on Monday evening to inform me that Quinton had been throwing up all day and into the evening.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018 Boy&#39;s Trip - Day 2</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/07/2018-boys-trip---day-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 20:50:03 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/07/2018-boys-trip---day-2/</guid>
      <description>Day 2 We started the day slowly, as any good boy&amp;rsquo;s trip would. Since we didn&amp;rsquo;t go to bed until later, we slept in until after 8:00. I sort of wanted to get going, so I got up and started cooking half of our 2 pounds of bacon and a dozen eggs. The smell was enough to wake Ethan up by 8:30, mainly because the apartment was so full of smoke that I think he started suffocating.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018 Boy&#39;s Trip</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/07/2018-boys-trip/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2018 20:29:30 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/07/2018-boys-trip/</guid>
      <description>Day 1 Here we sit at 521 Elm St. in historic Leadville, CO, our VRBO for the weekend. Ethan, Quinton, and I are doing our first &amp;ldquo;boy&amp;rsquo;s weekend.&amp;rdquo; It was hard leaving Jenny and Mireille behind, but we stayed the course and are going through with it.
The trip up here was rougher than expected. Traffic out of Denver to the mountains via I70 was somehow worse than it normally would be when we are coming up to ski, but we persevered.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spring Break 2018 - Day Three</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/03/spring-break-2018---day-three/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Mar 2018 20:15:04 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/03/spring-break-2018---day-three/</guid>
      <description>Taos Our third day was dedicated to Taos. Having slept in a little, but not quite as much as the prior day, we had a little extra time to do some swimming in hopes of getting away from the crowds in the pool. We weren&amp;rsquo;t successful in avoiding crowds, but we did get about 45 minutes of swimming in before we left the hotel. Mireille, Quinton, and I played some hide and seek (it&amp;rsquo;s more fun than you would think).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spring Break 2018 - Day Two</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/03/spring-break-2018---day-two/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 21:34:29 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/03/spring-break-2018---day-two/</guid>
      <description>Los Alamos Thank goodness, today started out MUCH later than the prior one. Nobody really stirred until 9:00, giving Mireille a much needed 13 hours, and Quinton an even more needed 11.5. Of course, I was also happy to finally get 10 myself, though I was up several times in the night for the &amp;ldquo;old man pee.&amp;rdquo; While we all got ready, Jenny and Mireille went to get some coffee at the very convenient on presmises Starbucks in the lobby.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spring Break 2018 - Day One</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/03/spring-break-2018---day-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2018 21:00:53 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/03/spring-break-2018---day-one/</guid>
      <description>AM As we suspected, and as is typical, we were up way too early. Mireille woke up around 7:00 the first time, Quinton followed about 7:30. While Mireille was able to fall back to sleep for a bit, Quinton was screaming for food by 8:00, so we were up! We left Ethan to sleep while the rest of us went down to one of the dozen or so restaurants the hotel had to offer for a nice buffet breakfast.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spring Break 2018 - The Drive</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/03/spring-break-2018---the-drive/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 22:29:27 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/03/spring-break-2018---the-drive/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Are we going to the hotel tonight?&amp;rdquo; This is the question repeated at least nightly for the last two weeks by our youngest, Mireille. For some reason she just loves hotels! I think it has something to do with the swimming pools. Perhaps she just likes to travel! At any rate, it had been a constant anthem for the last several weeks - &amp;ldquo;are we going to the hotel?&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Colorado Adventure Series - Snow Mountain Ranch Day 4</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/08/colorado-adventure-series---snow-mountain-ranch-day-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2017 17:52:46 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/08/colorado-adventure-series---snow-mountain-ranch-day-4/</guid>
      <description>Day 4 Today started out much the same as the last. I got up &amp;ldquo;early&amp;rdquo; and headed out for a quick run around the campus. The main difference today was that Ethan decided he would come with me! He&amp;rsquo;s training for soccer and was supposed to run 5 miles over the weekend. He decided that 3.2 at 9000 feet was a rough equivalent of 5 at 5280, which I&amp;rsquo;m inclined to agree with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Colorado Adventure Series - Snow Mountain Ranch Day 3</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/08/colorado-adventure-series---snow-mountain-ranch-day-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2017 16:52:46 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/08/colorado-adventure-series---snow-mountain-ranch-day-3/</guid>
      <description>Day 3 Day three started out later than day 2. With nothing really pushing us out of bed, the room slept in. I got up &amp;ldquo;early&amp;rdquo; around 7:00 or so and circumnavigated the property on a &amp;ldquo;run&amp;rdquo; of sorts. Not sure you can really call it a run. Jogging occured, but a lot of walking also occurred. It was very brisk to start the day, at only 36 degF, and a bit of fog made it a little spooky, but it was good to get out and about and get the blood pumping earlyish.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Colorado Adventure Series - Snow Mountain Ranch Day 2</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/08/colorado-adventure-series---snow-mountain-ranch-day-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2017 21:52:46 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/08/colorado-adventure-series---snow-mountain-ranch-day-2/</guid>
      <description>Day 2 Our first full day of vacation! Today is exciting because it will be most of our first time whitewater rafting. We were to be in Kremmling, about 45 miles away, by 8:30 for our half day whitewater rafting adventure. So we set an alarm for 6:30, which was fine with everybody considering we were all in bed early the night before, got dressed, had breakfast at the cafeteria, and headed west on 40 to the bustling metropolis of Kremmling via Granby.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Colorado Adventure Series - Snow Mountain Ranch Day 1</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/08/colorado-adventure-series---snow-mountain-ranch-day-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2017 20:52:46 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/08/colorado-adventure-series---snow-mountain-ranch-day-1/</guid>
      <description>Prelude When we first moved to Colorado two years ago, we made a point of being &amp;ldquo;tourists in our own state.&amp;rdquo; It seems so often that we live somewhere and never really get to experience it like somebody who visits. Life always seems to catch up with us. Lord Soccer demands attention, work, school, the house&amp;hellip; It&amp;rsquo;s a never ending cycle of demands on our time. So we&amp;rsquo;ve tried to keep it more fresh here in Colorado, since there is so much to see out here (despite there not being any measurable amount of recreational water anywhere out here).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Colorado Adventure Series - Crested Butte</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/08/colorado-adventure-series---crested-butte/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2016 21:38:05 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/08/colorado-adventure-series---crested-butte/</guid>
      <description>A couple of weeks ago, friends of ours from Wisconsin contacted us and asked if we wanted to spend some time with them in Crested Butte. They have a condo there that they were going to be visiting, and we decided it would be fun to check it out. I have to say, I&amp;rsquo;m glad we did.
Crested Butte is quite a long drive from our home. At about 4.5 hours, it&amp;rsquo;s by far the furthest we&amp;rsquo;ve traveled for this summer&amp;rsquo;s adventures, but we couldn&amp;rsquo;t pass up the opportunity to check it out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summer Vacation 2014 - Day 5 - Saturday</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/summer-vacation-2014---day-5---saturday/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2014 21:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/summer-vacation-2014---day-5---saturday/</guid>
      <description>That&amp;rsquo;s right, we&amp;rsquo;re going a little Tarantino here with the time jumping and what-not. By now it&amp;rsquo;s been nearly two weeks and the scars are just starting to form. This will be a blissfully short retrospective on the fifth day of our summer vacation, lest it is lost for all time to the memory of the harrowing experience of the trip home.
Saturday was not at all unlike Friday in most regards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summer Vacation 2014 - There and Back Again</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/summer-vacation-2014---there-and-back-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2014 23:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/summer-vacation-2014---there-and-back-again/</guid>
      <description>Introduction 9:30 on Monday, June 30, 2014. We&amp;rsquo;re all showered, Quin is in bed, Jenny&amp;rsquo;s powering through another bout with Facebook, I&amp;rsquo;m watching The Wolverine with Ethan&amp;hellip; It&amp;rsquo;s easy to forget about the events of the last 36 hours. It&amp;rsquo;s taken me an hour to type up the summary on this page, so I can only imagine how long the actual account will take me. This will be an epic, to be sure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summer Vacation 2014 - Day 4 - Friday</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/summer-vacation-2014---day-4---friday/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2014 23:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/summer-vacation-2014---day-4---friday/</guid>
      <description>Friday started our first full day at camp. We had hoped to get a vacation run in this morning, but alas, it was not meant to be. We were able to get moving in time for our 8:30 breakfast meet-up for new families. New families were quite the thing this year with the camp doubling in size or so over the last couple of years.
After breakfast we dropped the kids off with their age appropriate groups, each color coded by shirt color.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summer Vacation 2014 - Days 1-3 - Tuednesday and Thursday</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/summer-vacation-2014---days-1-3---tuednesday-and-thursday/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2014 00:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/summer-vacation-2014---days-1-3---tuednesday-and-thursday/</guid>
      <description>This year&amp;rsquo;s edition of summer vacation is to the Mile High City where we are attending an African and Caribbean Heritage Camp. It&amp;rsquo;s been a few years since we&amp;rsquo;ve been in Denver in the summer, so we were pretty excited to get things started.
The plan was to make the 15 hour drive from Tuesday through Wednesday morning. After 2&amp;frasl;3 day of work, we packed up the car and&amp;hellip; waited for Target to deliver some new patio furniture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spring Break 2014 - Home!</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/spring-break-2014---home/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2014 22:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/spring-break-2014---home/</guid>
      <description>Raining again this morning. As we were packing our room, I was thinking on my post from last night and how I had forgotten to put some important color on it. After the mall, the three boys (Ethan, Quin, and Loudon) and I went swimming in the pool. After we had swum for awhile, a couple of young girls came in - I would estimate they were around 10 or 11 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spring Break 2014 - Mall of America</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/spring-break-2014---mall-of-america/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2014 22:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/spring-break-2014---mall-of-america/</guid>
      <description>The day started REALLY late this morning. The plan was to meet Uncle Bryce and Loudon at the Mall of America (MOA) at 10:00 to do rides and other fun stuff. When 9:00 rolled around and we were still having difficulty getting Quin out of bed, we knew we were going to have to delay a bit. It seems that vacation finally caught up to the 6 year old, who went to bed at midnight the night previous and hadn&amp;rsquo;t slept much to date.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spring Break 2014 - The Museum</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/spring-break-2014---the-museum/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2014 21:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/spring-break-2014---the-museum/</guid>
      <description>Ethan and I knocked one of our meager goals for this vacation off this morning, we had breakfast at Taco Bell! Yeah, we have lofty goals. We piled down a couple of waffle tacos and breakfast burritos each and headed into St. Paul to take in the Minnesota Museum of Science.
The MMS is one of the better science museums I&amp;rsquo;ve been to, quite honestly. We easily spent 3.5 hours there without even doing a movie!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spring Break 2014 - Minnesota</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/spring-break-2014---minnesota/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2014 22:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/spring-break-2014---minnesota/</guid>
      <description>We departed Neillsville sometime between 9:00 and 10:00 AM, right on schedule. Jenny&amp;rsquo;s plans didn&amp;rsquo;t have us overtaxing ourselves today. The plan was to hit a couple of tourist stops south of the Twin Cities, then drive up to spend the late afternoon/evening at Blaine&amp;rsquo;s in Inver Grove Heights.
Our first stop was at (LARK Toys)[http://www.larktoys.com/] in Kellogg Minnesota. This was not our typical drive for a vacation as it involved ZERO interstate time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vacation - The Emergency</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/vacation---the-emergency/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2014 23:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/vacation---the-emergency/</guid>
      <description>Vacation just isn&amp;rsquo;t vacation until there&amp;rsquo;s a trip to the E.R. So today officially started our vacation!
This afternoon was pretty nice outside. It was around 60 degrees, not too much wind, so the kids went outside and played baseball. They were chasing the balls all around the property, including through some longer brush and what-not.
After a long day of playing, and a long night the night before, Quin was pretty tired.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spring Break 2014 - Happy Easter!</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/spring-break-2014---happy-easter/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2014 13:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/spring-break-2014---happy-easter/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Grady Spring Break, 2014! The itenerary is quite extensive, to be sure, and the destinations exotic!
The trip started yesterday where we left the house in the van around 9:00 AM, heading north! Yes, you read that correctly, we headed NORTH for spring break. Didn&amp;rsquo;t say we were all that bright! The first stop was probably just off of MTV&amp;rsquo;s list of destinations for this year&amp;rsquo;s spring break, Neillsville, WI.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sweet Vacation - Alabama</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/sweet-vacation---alabama/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2013 22:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/sweet-vacation---alabama/</guid>
      <description>Home at last! Strange way to start a blog about our vacation to Alabama, but I ended up not really writing during the vacation - something I&amp;rsquo;m sure I&amp;rsquo;ll regret in the end as I&amp;rsquo;m sure there is some level of excruciating detail that I will miss out on by not doing this in real time, but in the end I&amp;rsquo;m sure it will save you, dear reader, from the droning on that would undoubtedly result from a real-time, blow-by-blow that I would have otherwise forced you to endure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Memorial Day!</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/happy-memorial-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 21:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/happy-memorial-day/</guid>
      <description>We had the opportunity to travel to Spread Eagle, WI near Iron Mountain, MI for Memorial Day this year. A friend of ours works for a company that owns a &amp;ldquo;cabin&amp;rdquo; on a lake up there, which they allow their employees to rent by the week during the year. When say cabin, I mean a 5 bedroom, 4000 square foot, modern home that is situated on a lake up north. So we joined 3 other families up there for the weekend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Great West Adventure - Day 9 - Travel day</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/great-west-adventure---day-9---travel-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2011 22:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/great-west-adventure---day-9---travel-day/</guid>
      <description>The last day of vacation is always the dreaded travel day. We were lucky enough to be able to get some laundry done at mom and dad&amp;rsquo;s before we left (OK, Jenny got it done), so we (Jenny) would not have to do it when we (Jenny) got home. But travel days are always a pain. Most of the morning was spent biding time until our flight. We departed pretty early for the airport - we had a 1:00 flight and arrived at the airport at 11:00, so we had plenty of time to get some pizza and wait at the gate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Great West Adventure - Day 8 - Don&#39;t look down...</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/great-west-adventure---day-8---dont-look-down.../</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2011 00:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/great-west-adventure---day-8---dont-look-down.../</guid>
      <description>Day 8 was to be a relaxing day! In that right, it wasn&amp;rsquo;t too bad. Mom and dad wanted to show off their new winter home state to us, though, so we headed out of town on Arizona 88 around 10:30 to catch up on some history and engineering marvels. Our first stop was Tortilla Flat, a (very) small stop on the way up to the Roosevelt Dam on the Salt River.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Great West Adventure - Day 7 - Permission to Board</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/great-west-adventure---day-7---permission-to-board/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2011 23:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/great-west-adventure---day-7---permission-to-board/</guid>
      <description>There was no plan in the works for today other than to drive back to Phoenix at some point. Small portion of the day, only 6.5 hours&amp;hellip; Surprisingly, though, it seemed relaxed since we didn&amp;rsquo;t have an itinerary. So we started out the day like we did any other day on vacation, we ate at a local breakfast establishment. This time we found a local favorite, Panera Bread. Excellent bagels and sandwiches - oh who am I kidding, we just wanted something fast.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Great West Adventure - Day 6 - It&#39;s a zoo out there</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/great-west-adventure---day-6---its-a-zoo-out-there/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2011 11:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/great-west-adventure---day-6---its-a-zoo-out-there/</guid>
      <description>In case there was any question to the subtitle of yesterday&amp;rsquo;s post, we were watching the weather where the cute weather lady exclaimed that the clouds were pretty moist and deep, and that she wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be surprised to see them start to rain at any time. I found that amusing - I suppose I&amp;rsquo;ve never really progressed past the age of 12 as far as my maturity level goes&amp;hellip;
I again find myself 3 days tardy in posting this, so I think this will be pretty short.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Great West Adventure - Day 5 - Moist and Deep</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/great-west-adventure---day-5---moist-and-deep/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2011 23:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/great-west-adventure---day-5---moist-and-deep/</guid>
      <description>Man, I have to start doing these as they happen. This is my third log today!!! To get me through it, I&amp;rsquo;ve gone to the fridge to finish off my San Diego brew sampler with a Karl Strauss Brewing Company Boardwalk Black Rye. Tasty!!!
Today&amp;rsquo;s plan was to go to Seaworld. We figured we would do things a little differently today since we completely missed supper yesterday, so we opted for a smaller breakfast of Subway sandwiches and Starbucks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Great West Adventure - Day 4 - A Ton of Bricks</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/great-west-adventure---day-4---a-ton-of-bricks/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2011 23:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/great-west-adventure---day-4---a-ton-of-bricks/</guid>
      <description>Day 4 - San Diego. Today started out early with Quin waking around 6:00 - he&amp;rsquo;s getting better. He and I passed time playing iOS games on the iPhone and iPad in the second room of our suite while Jenny and Ethan grabbed 90 more minutes of sleep. By 7:30, Jenny got up and I hit the road for a quick run along the water.
By 9:00 we were off for a full day of vacationing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Great West Adventure - Day 3</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/great-west-adventure---day-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2011 22:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/great-west-adventure---day-3/</guid>
      <description>Since we were up by 6:00 anyway, we decided to try to get an early start at things, so we got ready and left by 8:00. My parents graciously lent us their vehicle - they are currently going without any sort of motorized vehicle of their own, relying instead on pedal power and favors from friends - so we loaded it up and took off on our 6 and 1&amp;frasl;2 hour drive to San Diego.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Great West Adventure - Day 2</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/great-west-adventure---day-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2011 22:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/great-west-adventure---day-2/</guid>
      <description>As should probably be expected, since Quin went to bed at around 6:00 local time, he woke up around 4:30 local. I suppose the day was going to start early! We aimed to do quite a bit during this day, but ultimately decided to back it off a bit seeing as how we were still a bit groggy from the previous day&amp;rsquo;s travels. We did manage to get to the (Superstition Mountain Museum)[http://www.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Great West Adventure - Day 1</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/great-west-adventure---day-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2011 22:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/great-west-adventure---day-1/</guid>
      <description>3:45 AM - the alarm called out the start of our Great West Adventure. We were ticketed for a 7:00 departure from Milwaukee&amp;rsquo;s General Mitchell Airport. With 3 and 10 year old in tow, we didn&amp;rsquo;t want to leave anything to risk. So we all showered the night before, set the alarm for 3:45, and aimed to leave by 4:15.
The plan went off without a hitch - the crew was excited for the trip.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ski Vacation - Part II</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/ski-vacation---part-ii/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2011 20:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/ski-vacation---part-ii/</guid>
      <description>Tuesday was another ski day. This time it was adult ski day. Quin was going back to school, and Ethan was enrolled in Woodward, an indoor extreme ski and snowboard school. The warehouse is immense with fake snow ramps that empty into foam pits and trampoline sections to teach people how to tumble with ease through the air. I think Ethan was in for a fun day!
Ethan and I went down to Woodward to drop him off while Jenny dropped Quin off at school.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ski Trip - Interlude</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/ski-trip---interlude/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2011 16:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/ski-trip---interlude/</guid>
      <description>OK, I hope this goes away like almost all other things, because if it comes back and is something serious, I will look like a schmuck. But Ethan had his little spell with sickness yesterday, during which he thought he was going to throw up. He is a fan of the drama! Today, he has a low grade headache as far as I can tell, because he&amp;rsquo;s running around, tubing, and being a general 9 year old menace, but after sitting on the couch for 30 minutes drinking water and eating popcorn he started complaining of a headache again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>St. Germain - Day 4</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/st.-germain---day-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2010 19:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/st.-germain---day-4/</guid>
      <description>It was windy and cool today, and I am training for a 1&amp;frasl;2 marathon, so I picked today to do my long run of the week. I mapped out a route before we left that took me around the entire lake. While I was supposed to run only 10 miles, the prospect and symmetry of running around the entire lake was too good to pass up, so Tim Z. and I ended up running a little over 11.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>St. Germain - Day 5</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/st.-germain---day-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2010 19:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/st.-germain---day-5/</guid>
      <description>Still a little cool to start the day, so Quin and I made bacon and egg sandwiches for breakfast before we headed out fishing with Tim and Logan Ziegler. The fishing wasn&amp;rsquo;t all that great, but we did have a close encounter with an eagle. It was pretty awesome, actually. We heard something heavy in the trees, then the eagle flew just above the water not more than about 20 feet from the boat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>St. Germain - Day 6</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/st.-germain---day-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2010 19:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/st.-germain---day-6/</guid>
      <description>Last night was an early one - we were all pretty beat from 5 days of vacation, so by 10:00 pretty much everybody was in bed already.
Today started warmer, but still windy. After Jenny and I each had a run we ran into town to get some chai tea and a smoothie. We then ventured into Eagle River to hit the liquor store. All that took a surprisingly long time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>St. Germain - Day 7</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/st.-germain---day-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2010 19:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/st.-germain---day-7/</guid>
      <description>It was my morning to get up with Quin. He didn&amp;rsquo;t go to bed until 10:00 last night, so it was a bit of a surprise when he got up at 6:00 like normal. Luckily I just convinced him to lay down and within about 10 seconds he fell back to sleep until 8:00. By that time his diaper was a wreck! I was changing the mess that had accumulated saying something about &amp;ldquo;stinky poop&amp;rdquo; or something, and Quin said &amp;ldquo;I poop potty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>St. Germain - Summary</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/st.-germain---summary/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2010 19:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/st.-germain---summary/</guid>
      <description>All good things must come to an end. We pretty much just got up and left first thing on Sunday morning. It was looking like a very hot day, and the time we did spend outside packing the cars found us swatting at a lot of mosquitoes which had been very sparse the rest of the week.
Lots of interesting things happened during the week, but here is a quick summary of some of the more memorable things:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>St. Germain - Day 1</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/st.-germain---day-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2010 19:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/st.-germain---day-1/</guid>
      <description>The trip started out somewhat inauspiciously. I had neglected to pack anything - Jenny packed all the kids&amp;rsquo; stuff as well as mine, but there was still a pile of things that I needed to take care of the morning of our departure. My parents, Blaine, and Brett along with respective lady friends of each of theirs joined us the day prior to celebrate mom and dad&amp;rsquo;s 39th wedding anniversary by going to IrishFest in Milwaukee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>St. Germain - Day 2</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/st.-germain---day-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2010 19:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/st.-germain---day-2/</guid>
      <description>Day 2 was a lazy day. The weather was beautiful and sunny, so we did a lot of swimming and hanging out at the campsite. Along with your usual swimming, running, eating drinking, and sunshine activities, the following things stuck out:
 Quin introduced the world to his &amp;ldquo;booty-butt.&amp;rdquo; Somewhere along the line he picked up the term &amp;ldquo;booty&amp;rdquo; as a word for his bottom, but he never really dropped the &amp;ldquo;butt&amp;rdquo; part.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>St. Germain - Day 3</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/st.-germain---day-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2010 19:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/st.-germain---day-3/</guid>
      <description>Jenny&amp;rsquo;s parents stayed with us last night, so Ethan went to sleep at Jacob&amp;rsquo;s cabin with the Abholds. That didn&amp;rsquo;t last too long, unfortunately. At about 1:30 we heard somebody talking to us through our window - it was Micky telling us that Jacob had gotten sick and that Ethan was now feeling sick, so she was returning him to us for the night. So much for that idea&amp;hellip;
By morning, Ethan was feeling fine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vacation 2010 - April 9 - 10, Driving</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/vacation-2010---april-9---10-driving/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2010 19:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/vacation-2010---april-9---10-driving/</guid>
      <description>We drove&amp;hellip; A lot&amp;hellip;
We left mom and dad&amp;rsquo;s place by 7:15. After a Starbucks run to keep the monster in the passenger&amp;rsquo;s seat happy, and a stop at the gas station for some gas and an energy drink (to keep the van and the monster in the driver&amp;rsquo;s seat happy), we got out of town by 7:45.
Not much to talk about here - we lunched at a Dairy Queen in Gallup New Mexico after passing through our first timezone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vacation 2010 - April 8, Apache Junction</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/vacation-2010---april-8-apache-junction/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2010 18:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/vacation-2010---april-8-apache-junction/</guid>
      <description>We started the day off again with a run through the Usery Recreational Area. This time we knew where we were going, but that didn&amp;rsquo;t make it any less exciting. We saw three hares (I believe that&amp;rsquo;s what they were) and a roadrunner. Jenny was attacked by a cactus which waylaid us for a few minutes, but overall it was a nice run.
After spending several days with Quin, he seems to be getting smarter all the time!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vacation 2010 - April 7, Apache Junction</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/vacation-2010---april-7-apache-junction/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2010 18:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/vacation-2010---april-7-apache-junction/</guid>
      <description>It was nice to be somewhere that we didn&amp;rsquo;t have to be running all the time! To celebrate, Jenny and I went for a run!!! I had made it out in Denver for a quick 3 miler, but Jenny wanted to get out, so we went to the map and found somewhere that &amp;ldquo;looked like it had trails.&amp;rdquo; After driving for about 10 minutes, we found a trailhead at the Usery Recreation Area and parked.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vacation 2010 - April 6, Sedona and Apache Junction</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/vacation-2010---april-6-sedona-and-apache-junction/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2010 00:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/vacation-2010---april-6-sedona-and-apache-junction/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m writing this three days later, so there is a serious possibility that these memories will be stale&amp;hellip; Oh well, maybe I&amp;rsquo;ll get some comments from my wife and parents to help fill in the blanks.
Quinny got up early this morning! 5:00 AM. A 5PM afternoon nap of 90 minutes didn&amp;rsquo;t help us out here at all. We tried to push him over to Grandpa and Grandma&amp;rsquo;s room right away, but he didn&amp;rsquo;t want to have much to do with that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vacation 2010 - April 5, The Grand Canyon</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/vacation-2010---april-5-the-grand-canyon/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2010 23:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/vacation-2010---april-5-the-grand-canyon/</guid>
      <description>Busy day, this one. We woke up after &amp;ldquo;sleeping in&amp;rdquo; until 6:00 at the Hampton Inn in Flagstaff, AZ. Very nice hotel, reasonably priced, with a nice rooms, decent continental breakfast, and most importantly, a POOL!!! After Quin woke up, he and I went downstairs for some fruit, cereal, and juice. Jenny and Ethan joined us shortly afterwards. After we were sufficiently fed, we got into our swimming suits and took in some much deserved swimming.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vacation 2010 - April 4, Driving...</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/vacation-2010---april-4-driving.../</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2010 00:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/vacation-2010---april-4-driving.../</guid>
      <description>OK, I&amp;rsquo;m a little out of order. Bear with me. April 4, Easter Sunday, was a day of driving. I was actually able to get out of bed and get out for a 3.4 mile run in the crisp Denver morning (41 degrees but sunny). Running in Denver is nice and not so nice. Nice because they have so many running trails and there are so many cute girls that are generally out exercising as well (even when it is cold).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grand canyon</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/grand-canyon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2010 12:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/grand-canyon/</guid>
      <description>Holy crap it&amp;rsquo;s windy!!! Short post for now. Jenny and Ethan are out looking at the little Colorado river gorge about 15 miles east of the south rim park of the grand canyon. It&amp;rsquo;s not too cold out but I bet the wind is gusting up to 50 mph. It&amp;rsquo;s so bad that it tipped over 2 portapotties.
Quinny is napping. We left him in the car to start with but then felt guilty so now I&amp;rsquo;m hanging out with him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vacaton 2010 Leg 1</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/vacaton-2010-leg-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Apr 2010 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/vacaton-2010-leg-1/</guid>
      <description>Vacation 2010 Leg 1 So I&amp;rsquo;m trying a couple of new things this time around. I&amp;rsquo;ve recently identified that I require an ipad in order to survive. In order to prepare myself I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to post my vacation blog entirely from my iPhone. We&amp;rsquo;ll see how long this lasts. I think I may be too old to learn to thumb type and ignore basic punctuation and spelling rules, but I suppose time will tell.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vacation 2009 - Evil River Part II</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/vacation-2009---evil-river-part-ii/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2009 16:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/vacation-2009---evil-river-part-ii/</guid>
      <description>Here it is, the big vacation update! Of course, it&amp;rsquo;s been a month since we went, so the memories have already started to fade, but I&amp;rsquo;ve uploaded some pictures to our photo gallery and the site&amp;rsquo;s slideshow is now showing them. Hopefully this gives a better idea of how the vacation went. To see all of the pictures in the album, either click on the slideshow, or try this link here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One Rough Vacation</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/one-rough-vacation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2008 19:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/one-rough-vacation/</guid>
      <description>This past weekend marked one of the most trying vacations we&amp;rsquo;ve had as a family. In fact, it was one of the most trying 24 hours we&amp;rsquo;ve ever had as a complete family. Let me explain&amp;hellip;
We rented a condo in Wisconsin Dells this past weekend with Aimee and Steve (Jenny&amp;rsquo;s sister) and Tim and Laura, and their respective children, all of whom range in age from 6 months to 2 years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Trip Home</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-trip-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2008 21:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-trip-home/</guid>
      <description>The Trip Home At 6:30 we got up &amp;ldquo;officially.&amp;rdquo; Jenny had packed the night before so we could maximize our sleep, but Quin had different ideas. By 7:30 we were showered and ready to go. A bellman picked us up at our room and took us to the &amp;ldquo;Common House&amp;rdquo; for checkout. Here we were actually able to check our bags onto the airplane and get our boarding passes. This Magical Express thing was really nice!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disney Day 5</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/disney-day-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2008 21:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/disney-day-5/</guid>
      <description>Morning Swim Finally, our last day at the parks. It&amp;rsquo;s been a pretty eventful week. A bit tiring, but definitely memorable. Today we had reservations at EPCOT early, 4:45, so we planned on spending the day there again. There was a lot at this park that we haven&amp;rsquo;t yet done. Also, mom and dad really like the world showcase, so there seemed plenty to do for the entire family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disney Day 4</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/disney-day-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2008 22:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/disney-day-4/</guid>
      <description>Late Start Quin was up during the night and we were getting tired, so we slept in a little bit this morning. Jenny and I got out for a run around the 1.4 mile running path that goes around the resort (we went twice around), we gave the kids baths, then we grabbed a leisurely breakfast at the Shutters food court at our resort. It was a good jumping off point for the rest of the day, which we planned on spending at Animal Kingdom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disney Day 3</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/disney-day-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2008 21:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/disney-day-3/</guid>
      <description>Magic Kingdom Part II Today we decided to try something a little different. Rather than sleeping in and dealing with the crowds of people, we thought we&amp;rsquo;d leave a little early in hopes of getting on some more rides in less confined areas. So we took off early for the bus (OK, I think we still got on the bus around 9:00) and headed for the Magic Kingdom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disney Day 2</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/disney-day-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2008 22:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/disney-day-2/</guid>
      <description>Good Night&amp;rsquo;s Sleep Our first night in the hotel was blissfully uneventful. My biggest worry coming to this resort with an infant was that he would be up and unconsolable in the night and he would wake people up. Turns out I had nothing to worry about all along. In fact, I would say that Quin probably slept better at the hotel than he does at home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disney Day 1</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/disney-day-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2008 22:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/disney-day-1/</guid>
      <description>A Note on These Posts I&amp;rsquo;m doing these posts a little out of sequence. I&amp;rsquo;ve written notes as things happened, but I&amp;rsquo;m going back and filling in the blanks as I get time to write them. At times it may seem a bit disjointed, so please forgive me. The dates will be posted as though they occurred on the days in which the events actually occurred, however they will not be written or posted on those actual days.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>