<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Vacation on The Hydrant</title>
    <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/tags/vacation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Vacation on The Hydrant</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2018 21:00:53 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://dogsbuttbrew.com/tags/vacation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Spring Break 2018 - Day One</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/03/spring-break-2018---day-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2018 21:00:53 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/03/spring-break-2018---day-one/</guid>
      <description>AM As we suspected, and as is typical, we were up way too early. Mireille woke up around 7:00 the first time, Quinton followed about 7:30. While Mireille was able to fall back to sleep for a bit, Quinton was screaming for food by 8:00, so we were up! We left Ethan to sleep while the rest of us went down to one of the dozen or so restaurants the hotel had to offer for a nice buffet breakfast.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spring Break 2018 - The Drive</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/03/spring-break-2018---the-drive/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 22:29:27 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/03/spring-break-2018---the-drive/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Are we going to the hotel tonight?&amp;rdquo; This is the question repeated at least nightly for the last two weeks by our youngest, Mireille. For some reason she just loves hotels! I think it has something to do with the swimming pools. Perhaps she just likes to travel! At any rate, it had been a constant anthem for the last several weeks - &amp;ldquo;are we going to the hotel?&amp;rdquo;
The day before we left, we dropped the &amp;ldquo;Flex-car&amp;rdquo; off at Rack Attack to get rails and a luggage rack installed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Colorado Adventure Series - Snow Mountain Ranch Day 4</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/08/colorado-adventure-series---snow-mountain-ranch-day-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2017 17:52:46 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/08/colorado-adventure-series---snow-mountain-ranch-day-4/</guid>
      <description>Day 4 Today started out much the same as the last. I got up &amp;ldquo;early&amp;rdquo; and headed out for a quick run around the campus. The main difference today was that Ethan decided he would come with me! He&amp;rsquo;s training for soccer and was supposed to run 5 miles over the weekend. He decided that 3.2 at 9000 feet was a rough equivalent of 5 at 5280, which I&amp;rsquo;m inclined to agree with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Colorado Adventure Series - Snow Mountain Ranch Day 3</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/08/colorado-adventure-series---snow-mountain-ranch-day-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2017 16:52:46 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/08/colorado-adventure-series---snow-mountain-ranch-day-3/</guid>
      <description>Day 3 Day three started out later than day 2. With nothing really pushing us out of bed, the room slept in. I got up &amp;ldquo;early&amp;rdquo; around 7:00 or so and circumnavigated the property on a &amp;ldquo;run&amp;rdquo; of sorts. Not sure you can really call it a run. Jogging occured, but a lot of walking also occurred. It was very brisk to start the day, at only 36 degF, and a bit of fog made it a little spooky, but it was good to get out and about and get the blood pumping earlyish.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Colorado Adventure Series - Snow Mountain Ranch Day 2</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/08/colorado-adventure-series---snow-mountain-ranch-day-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2017 21:52:46 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/08/colorado-adventure-series---snow-mountain-ranch-day-2/</guid>
      <description>Day 2 Our first full day of vacation! Today is exciting because it will be most of our first time whitewater rafting. We were to be in Kremmling, about 45 miles away, by 8:30 for our half day whitewater rafting adventure. So we set an alarm for 6:30, which was fine with everybody considering we were all in bed early the night before, got dressed, had breakfast at the cafeteria, and headed west on 40 to the bustling metropolis of Kremmling via Granby.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Colorado Adventure Series - Snow Mountain Ranch Day 1</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/08/colorado-adventure-series---snow-mountain-ranch-day-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2017 20:52:46 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/08/colorado-adventure-series---snow-mountain-ranch-day-1/</guid>
      <description>Prelude When we first moved to Colorado two years ago, we made a point of being &amp;ldquo;tourists in our own state.&amp;rdquo; It seems so often that we live somewhere and never really get to experience it like somebody who visits. Life always seems to catch up with us. Lord Soccer demands attention, work, school, the house&amp;hellip; It&amp;rsquo;s a never ending cycle of demands on our time. So we&amp;rsquo;ve tried to keep it more fresh here in Colorado, since there is so much to see out here (despite there not being any measurable amount of recreational water anywhere out here).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Colorado Adventure Series - Crested Butte</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/08/colorado-adventure-series---crested-butte/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2016 21:38:05 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/08/colorado-adventure-series---crested-butte/</guid>
      <description>A couple of weeks ago, friends of ours from Wisconsin contacted us and asked if we wanted to spend some time with them in Crested Butte. They have a condo there that they were going to be visiting, and we decided it would be fun to check it out. I have to say, I&amp;rsquo;m glad we did.
Crested Butte is quite a long drive from our home. At about 4.5 hours, it&amp;rsquo;s by far the furthest we&amp;rsquo;ve traveled for this summer&amp;rsquo;s adventures, but we couldn&amp;rsquo;t pass up the opportunity to check it out.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>