<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Technology on The Hydrant</title>
    <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/categories/technology/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Technology on The Hydrant</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Mar 2018 12:26:58 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://dogsbuttbrew.com/categories/technology/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>New Website</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/03/new-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Mar 2018 12:26:58 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/03/new-website/</guid>
      <description>I know, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t look any different. That&amp;rsquo;s sort of the beauty of this story. I&amp;rsquo;m going to warn you, if you normally come here for my amusing anecdotes about my kids, or perhaps to be regaled about my home improvement exploits, this story will probably seem somewhat dull. However, I owe this entry to the greater technological community, as there might be somebody, somewhere, that thinks even a little bit like me and are trying to do something similar to what I&amp;rsquo;m trying to do.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Theme!!!</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/08/new-theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2016 19:04:39 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/08/new-theme/</guid>
      <description>You may have noticed something new when you browsed here today. No, I didn&amp;rsquo;t adopt another kid&amp;hellip; I didn&amp;rsquo;t have to shovel 12 inches of snow&amp;hellip; It&amp;rsquo;s a new theme for the website! I&amp;rsquo;m sure you are as excited as I am about the change&amp;hellip; Doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter - this is my blog, and I can put whatever I want here.
This theme is awhile in the making. I&amp;rsquo;ve been doing web development for probably 17 years (well, I&amp;rsquo;ve been pretending to do it for that long - much of that time has been dedicated to managing web developers, but let&amp;rsquo;s not split hairs), and in the time I&amp;rsquo;ve been doing it, it has changed mightily.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The &#34;Hack&#34; Font</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/02/the-hack-font/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2016 10:53:23 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/02/the-hack-font/</guid>
      <description>Sorry, no cute stories about Quinton and the funny things he says today. No interesting tales about Ethan and his quest to become a driver one day in the next year or so&amp;hellip; Today I thought I&amp;rsquo;d take an aside and post a public service announcement on the &amp;ldquo;Hack&amp;rdquo; font.
Why do you care? You likely do not. However, if you&amp;rsquo;ve found this post and are still reading, let me tell you why I like Hack.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Blog Home</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/new-blog-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Nov 2015 10:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/new-blog-home/</guid>
      <description>Announcing (DogsButtBrew.com)[http://dogsbuttbrew.com]! It&amp;rsquo;s with some degree of excitement that I announce that I am retiring e-and-quin.blogspot.com. Over the years, the Blogger platform has served me well. It has captured many memories that I enjoy reading and re-reading.
No, I&amp;rsquo;m not giving up blogging. In fact, I&amp;rsquo;m doubling down on it! I&amp;rsquo;m just giving up on Blogger. As I said, it has served me well, but my interests have moved on.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Now With Comments</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/11/now-with-comments/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2015 10:12:59 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/11/now-with-comments/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;re here, great! I&amp;rsquo;m not sure how you found it because I haven&amp;rsquo;t yet linked the old blog to this one, nor have I done any advertisement or anything (I probably won&amp;rsquo;t ever advertise).
There will be a larger series on how the new blog was constructed and some of the technical ins and outs, but I wanted to quickly mention that the blog is soft-launched, and today I added the ability to comment using Discus, a SaaS based commenting and discuussion platform.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
