<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Technology on The Hydrant</title>
    <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/categories/technology/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Technology on The Hydrant</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Mar 2018 12:26:58 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://dogsbuttbrew.com/categories/technology/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>New Website</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/03/new-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Mar 2018 12:26:58 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/03/new-website/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I know, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t look any different. That&amp;rsquo;s sort of the beauty of this story. I&amp;rsquo;m going to warn you, if you normally come here for my amusing anecdotes about my kids, or perhaps to be regaled about my home improvement exploits, this story will probably seem somewhat dull. However, I owe this entry to the greater technological community, as there might be somebody, somewhere, that thinks even a little bit like me and are trying to do something similar to what I&amp;rsquo;m trying to do. And if they are a little like me, they will systematically hack their way through problems using Google, and maybe this article will show up and help them.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Theme!!!</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/08/new-theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2016 19:04:39 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/08/new-theme/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;You may have noticed something new when you browsed here today. No, I didn&amp;rsquo;t adopt another kid&amp;hellip; I didn&amp;rsquo;t have to shovel 12 inches of snow&amp;hellip; It&amp;rsquo;s a new theme for the website! I&amp;rsquo;m sure you are as excited as I am about the change&amp;hellip; Doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter - this is my blog, and I can put whatever I want here.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This theme is awhile in the making. I&amp;rsquo;ve been doing web development for probably 17 years (well, I&amp;rsquo;ve been pretending to do it for that long - much of that time has been dedicated to managing web developers, but let&amp;rsquo;s not split hairs), and in the time I&amp;rsquo;ve been doing it, it has changed mightily. In the early years, you had to do literally everything yourself. And in an environment that didn&amp;rsquo;t match up with many of the desktop or server environments (that being HTML/JavaScript/CSS), it wasn&amp;rsquo;t always pretty.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The &#34;Hack&#34; Font</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/02/the-hack-font/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2016 10:53:23 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/02/the-hack-font/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Sorry, no cute stories about Quinton and the funny things he says today.&#xA;No interesting tales about Ethan and his quest to become a driver one day&#xA;in the next year or so&amp;hellip; Today I thought I&amp;rsquo;d take an aside and post a public&#xA;service announcement on the &lt;a href=&#34;http://sourcefoundry.org/hack/&#34;&gt;&amp;ldquo;Hack&amp;rdquo; font&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Why do you care? You likely do not. However, if you&amp;rsquo;ve found this post and are&#xA;still reading, let me tell you why I like Hack.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Blog Home</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/new-blog-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Nov 2015 10:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/new-blog-home/</guid>
      <description>&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-KFjLHzL29sY/Vj4gEO98FEI/AAAAAAAAsUQ/N2Zq2OahBYM/s1600/woodcut_dogs_transparent.png&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;announcing-dogsbuttbrewcomhttpdogsbuttbrewcom&#34;&gt;Announcing (DogsButtBrew.com)[http://dogsbuttbrew.com]!&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s with some degree of excitement that I announce that I am retiring e-and-quin.blogspot.com. Over the years, the Blogger platform has served me well. It has captured many memories that I enjoy reading and re-reading.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;No, I&amp;rsquo;m not giving up blogging. In fact, I&amp;rsquo;m doubling down on it! I&amp;rsquo;m just giving up on Blogger. As I said, it has served me well, but my interests have moved on. I wanted something that I could have better control over, something I could call my own. Oh, and I already owned the DogsButtBrew.com domain name and was paying for hosting&amp;hellip; That site was in desperate need of a refresh. Combine that with a need to rejuvenate the blog, and you have the relaunched (DogsButtBrew.com)[http://dogsbuttbrew.com]&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Now With Comments</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/11/now-with-comments/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2015 10:12:59 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/11/now-with-comments/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;re here, great! I&amp;rsquo;m not sure how you found it because I haven&amp;rsquo;t yet&#xA;linked the old blog to this one, nor have I done any advertisement or anything&#xA;(I probably won&amp;rsquo;t ever advertise).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There will be a larger series on how the new blog was constructed and some of&#xA;the technical ins and outs, but I wanted to quickly mention that the blog&#xA;is soft-launched, and today I added the ability to comment using&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://disqus.com/&#34;&gt;Discus&lt;/a&gt;, a SaaS based commenting and discuussion&#xA;platform. Please test it out and contact me with any problems you see. It&amp;rsquo;s sort&#xA;of &amp;ldquo;in beta&amp;rdquo; right now (not Disqus, but my usage of it).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
