<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>DIY on The Hydrant</title>
    <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/categories/diy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in DIY on The Hydrant</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2018 09:36:02 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://dogsbuttbrew.com/categories/diy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Next Renovation</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/02/the-next-renovation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2018 09:36:02 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/02/the-next-renovation/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s been awhile since we&amp;rsquo;ve done any major remodeling work to our house (yeah, right!), so it was time for us to embark on our next gigantic project. The thought was that we would do both upstairs bathrooms at more or less the same time. The kid&amp;rsquo;s bathroom was supposed to be &amp;ldquo;easy&amp;rdquo; since I was going to leave the shower pretty much alone, just update the fixtures and the shower head, but concentrate mostly on the floor, toilet, and vanity. Our master bathroom was going to be a little more involved, new toilet, floor, and entirely new shower save for the shower pan. Well, plans changed&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suburban Archeologist</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/10/suburban-archeologist/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2017 08:42:44 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/10/suburban-archeologist/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Not an interesting update for those that are looking for news on my adorable and smart children, but something I&amp;rsquo;m documenting for posterity, and for my own purposes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We do quite a lot of home improvement. I&amp;rsquo;ve always been the type that likes to try something on my own before calling a professional in to do it correctly and quickly. Last weekend, a couple of long running &amp;ldquo;curiosity&amp;rdquo; type projects finally had some major movement, which, since I&amp;rsquo;m kind of a dork, made me pretty excited!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Logitech K810 Reset</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/07/logitech-k810-reset/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2017 08:26:10 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/07/logitech-k810-reset/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I have been using the same external keyboard for my last three Macs, an excellent little Bluetooth keyboard from Logitech called the &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.logitech.com/en-us/product/bluetooth-illuminated-keyboard-k810&#34;&gt;Logitech K810&lt;/a&gt;. It&amp;rsquo;s meant to be a keyboard for a Windows machine, but it works perfectly well for my Mac as well as my various iDevices.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This morning when I came in to start working for the day, I found the keyboard had lost its mind! None of the keys worked properly. When I&amp;rsquo;d press Alt (which I have mapped to Command), it would turn the volume up. If I tried the Alt on the right side of the space bar, it would bring up the Print dialog. Things just weren&amp;rsquo;t quite right.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Driver Out There</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/06/new-driver-out-there/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2017 14:52:46 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/06/new-driver-out-there/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As of Monday, June 26, the world has a new driver. Ethan passed his driver&amp;rsquo;s test last Friday and made it official with the DMV (and our insurance agent) on Monday. It was actually a nice thing today. It&amp;rsquo;s Bike to Work day here in Denver, so I rode my bike in. About 2 miles from home, one of my tires popped, and I didn&amp;rsquo;t have a repair kit with me. It was 7:00, but since he now has a license, I was able to save a marriage by having the 16 year old come and pick me up so I could repair the tire and continue on to work. Already that insurance money is paying dividends!!!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summer is here!</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/06/summer-is-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 14:52:46 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/06/summer-is-here/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Summer is finally upon us. Last week was a full week without school, except for Mireille, but that&amp;rsquo;s daycare - even though she calls it school. The temperatures as of last Thursday definitely represented a shift into the ungodly hot area, though in Denver, if you can find shade, you are in good shape since the humidity is very comfortable. As a family we are definitely settling in more and more as the years have gone by.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Happy Mother&#39;s Day</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/05/happy-mothers-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2017 11:04:40 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/05/happy-mothers-day/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Happy Mother&amp;rsquo;s Day to my kids&amp;rsquo; mom, and of course my wife, who luckily happen to be the same person! This year we celebrated by going to a brunch at one of our favorite places, Bull and Bush Brewpub! It&amp;rsquo;s a difficult thing to get all of our kids both out of the house and behaving in a public place, but for the most part they held it together through brunch.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bathroom Remodel</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/02/bathroom-remodel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2017 08:26:10 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/02/bathroom-remodel/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Our house was built in the 80s, 1982 to be exact. Many, if not most things have not really been touched since then. Sure, fresh paint has been applied to the walls and carpet occasionally replaced, but the &amp;ldquo;bones&amp;rdquo; of the house have remained unchanged for the last 35 years.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;That changed immediately when we moved in almost 2 years ago. It started with windows, moved to the kitchen (which is still awesome, btw), moved on to doors, and now has passed to the biggest thorn remaining on the first floor, the bathroom.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>October 2016 - Big Update!</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/10/october-2016-big-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2016 19:39:06 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/10/october-2016-big-update/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s October! October has been a busy month, but what month hasn&amp;rsquo;t been, really. So it&amp;rsquo;s been awhile since there&amp;rsquo;s been an update of much substance. So, while my family answers the door to greet and treat Halloween visitors in full costume, I thought I would take a few minutes (or 60) and update the world on the goings on in the Grady Household.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;adoption---complete&#34;&gt;Adoption - Complete&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;rsquo;t have to restate how much work and waiting it&amp;rsquo;s been to complete this, our second adoption. It&amp;rsquo;s been long. This past Friday, though, we hit a big milestone. Mireille had her day in court, and she is now officially adopted in the United States, meaning she if officially a Grady! I wish that meant we were all done! But alas, this is yet another milestone. It marks our ability to complete more paperwork, and pay out more money for interesting new bureaucratic processes. But, it is a reason to celebrate, at least for the fact that this part of the process has come to a close.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>There, I fixed it - plumbing edition</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/12/there-i-fixed-it-plumbing-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2015 07:27:08 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/12/there-i-fixed-it-plumbing-edition/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;One of these days I will get around to posting the epic project that we&amp;rsquo;ve&#xA;undertaken of redoing our kitchen. It&amp;rsquo;s been about 4 months in the making and&#xA;we&amp;rsquo;re hitting the final stretch! Last week the countertops were installed&#xA;so we finally got our new sink installed. Unfortunately, the countertop guys&#xA;don&amp;rsquo;t do plumbing, so that&amp;rsquo;s my job!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I had budgeted three trips to the hardware store, and I was right on the&#xA;money! The problems I had to deal with in this particular plumbing experience&#xA;were as follows:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bike Hangar Idea</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/11/bike-hangar-idea/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2015 20:02:33 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/11/bike-hangar-idea/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Thought I would put this out there as I had never thought of this before.&#xA;We needed to hang our bikes in the garage. I didn&amp;rsquo;t really want to spend too&#xA;much money on hardware, so we just got the cheap hooks that you can get at&#xA;Home Depot - they were like $1.50 each. I typically don&amp;rsquo;t like using those&#xA;hooks because it&amp;rsquo;s a pain to find studs to drill and put them into, and then&#xA;when you do, it rarely lines up with the thing you want to hang.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Kitchen Discovery</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/11/a-kitchen-discovery/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2015 20:55:58 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/11/a-kitchen-discovery/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re redoing our kitchen right now. I have a long post queued up for some time&#xA;in the near future to go through some of the experience and show pictures. It&amp;rsquo;s&#xA;been fun, but it&amp;rsquo;s also been interesting.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Last weekend we finally got to the point where we could take out our old&#xA;lower cabinets and replace them with the new ones. The plan was to demolish&#xA;on Saturday and install on Sunday. For the most part this went off without&#xA;a hitch.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
