<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>adoption on The Hydrant</title>
    <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/tags/adoption/</link>
    <description>Recent content in adoption on The Hydrant</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2016 19:39:06 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://dogsbuttbrew.com/tags/adoption/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>October 2016 - Big Update!</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/10/october-2016-big-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2016 19:39:06 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/10/october-2016-big-update/</guid>
      <description>It&#39;s October! October has been a busy month, but what month hasn&#39;t been, really. So it&#39;s been awhile since there&#39;s been an update of much substance. So, while my family answers the door to greet and treat Halloween visitors in full costume, I thought I would take a few minutes (or 60) and update the world on the goings on in the Grady Household.
Adoption - Complete I don&#39;t have to restate how much work and waiting it&#39;s been to complete this, our second adoption.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two Days on the Hill</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/02/two-days-on-the-hill/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2016 10:15:09 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/02/two-days-on-the-hill/</guid>
      <description>Preamble I briefly considered titling this &amp;ldquo;Mr. Grady Goes to Washington,&amp;rdquo; but I didn&#39;t like it for a couple of reasons. First, I don&#39;t really think of myself as Mr. Grady. And more importantly, I have never really seen the movie, and I hate giving false information.
This is a story about a number of things&amp;hellip; Adoption, politics, travel, weather&amp;hellip; Hold on to your seats, and grab some NoDoze. This might get boring!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>She&#39;s Coming Home!!!</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/02/shes-coming-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2016 07:59:33 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/02/shes-coming-home/</guid>
      <description>Riding to my Red Eye     Dulles Airport     Empty International Arrival Terminal     UA 951 from Brussels     At at DGM, Ironic Lunch     The Wait is Excruciating     The Plane has Landed!     Busiest Time of Day     She&amp;#39;s Here!     Confused?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DRC Update</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/01/drc-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2016 08:04:12 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/01/drc-update/</guid>
      <description>So&amp;hellip; There are a couple of updates, but we&#39;re still stuck.
The US sent a delegation of congressmen to the DRC to talk specifically about this issue. As has become typical, the DRC responded with things that we want to hear. I won&#39;t go into details, but I wanted to document, for posterity, the letter I wrote to my congressmen in Colorado. I&#39;ve been interacting with their offices for the past couple of months and have a fairly good rapport going with my contacts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adoption Woes</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/11/adoption-woes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2015 10:22:35 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/11/adoption-woes/</guid>
      <description>If you&#39;ve known us for any amount of time, you know that we are, and have been in the process of adopting from the Democratic Republic of Congo for the past 3 years. It has been a long, LONG process.
TL;DR; Last month, the Congolese government has dashed our hopes of completing this adoption in the near timeframe. It is questionable if we will ever be able to complete it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skype with Mireille</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/10/skype-with-mireille/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2015 09:53:21 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/10/skype-with-mireille/</guid>
      <description>We got to Skype with Mireille this morning. It&#39;s always bittersweet talking with her. On the one hand, you want to make sure you keep in touch so she at least has some sort of connection, but on another hand it just sort of hurts to talk with her. When we talk with her, we are reminded of the situation that we&#39;re in, whereas other times we can sort of ignore it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Congo Children&#39;s Fund</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/congo-childrens-fund/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2015 10:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/congo-childrens-fund/</guid>
      <description>This won&#39;t really benefit Mireille, but a family in much the same situation we are in has started a fund to help bring food to orphans in need in Kinshasa. We&#39;re planning on doing some fund raising to help this organization. Despite your feelings on international adoption, it&#39;s hard to disagree with helping children to get nutritious food and water.
Please consider donating.
http://www.congochildrensfund.org
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pre Adoptive and a chink in the armor</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/pre-adoptive-and-a-chink-in-the-armor/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2008 07:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/pre-adoptive-and-a-chink-in-the-armor/</guid>
      <description>It&#39;s official as of Monday afternoon, we are a pre-adoptive family. On Monday, both birth parents were given one last opportunity to choose to parent Quin. The birth mother showed up and gave up her right to do so, and the birth father did not answer the attempts to contact him. That&#39;s an important step for us! That means that there shouldn&#39;t be any bad Lifetime movies written about our situation any time soon.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>