<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ethan on The Hydrant</title>
    <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/tags/ethan/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ethan on The Hydrant</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 14:43:30 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://dogsbuttbrew.com/tags/ethan/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Best Mother So Far</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2023/06/best-mother-so-far/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 14:43:30 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2023/06/best-mother-so-far/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;One of the best parts of being a parent, in my estimation, is watching my kids&amp;rsquo; sense of humor develop. Early on, it&amp;rsquo;s at once fun and annoying to watch them try new things out and see what type of reaction they get. The annoying part comes with things like the constant use of the word &amp;ldquo;diarhea&amp;rdquo; that Mireille currently thinks is funny. The fun part, though, is seeing Ethan tell his grandmother, who had recently burst a blood vessel in her eye, that she could potentially remediate it with a quick trip to the Halloween Store.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>College - Year 2</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/09/college-year-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2020 09:03:44 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/09/college-year-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Ahh, COVID. I guess life goes on, or we try to do so, anyway. Ethan, after spending the last 5+ months at home (bonus Ethan time for us!) has now completed his transfer to Colorado State University and we have moved him into his dwelling for the upcoming school year! Even though this is Ethan&amp;rsquo;s second year of school, this year seemed almost worse in some ways than moving him in last year. Last year he was going to Regis, which on a good traffic day was only about a 30 minute drive from home. He had access to the city bus and train system to get him home whenever he liked, and we were pretty &amp;ldquo;comfortable&amp;rdquo; with the school. Not to mention, after last summer, we were kind of ready for him to leave (sorry Ethan)! This year he will be attending a big state school which we haven&amp;rsquo;t had an opportunity to really visit or connect with it at all due to the pandemic. Also, it&amp;rsquo;s a bit further away, 90 minutes in good traffic. Given all that, it just &lt;em&gt;felt&lt;/em&gt; different. Quinton seemed to actually care and notice that it was happening this time around. At one point he asked Jenny and I in an accusatory way why we weren&amp;rsquo;t more upset about Ethan leaving! It was kind of nice having him around for the last 5-6 months&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big Update on Grady Kids</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/01/big-update-on-grady-kids/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2020 09:25:40 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/01/big-update-on-grady-kids/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s a broken record on this blog, but it&amp;rsquo;s again been a LONG time since I&amp;rsquo;ve done anything. There is definitely an ebb and flow to my state of mind that really dictates how much I observe of the world around me, and around the end of the year is a time of reflection for lots of people. So here it goes&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This post is going to read mostly as a Quinton post. It&amp;rsquo;s not that I don&amp;rsquo;t love my other kids, he&amp;rsquo;s just at a point where the things he does crack me up more than what I&amp;rsquo;m observing from my other kids right now. Ethan, Mireille, forgive me!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>College</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/08/college/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2019 20:24:15 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/08/college/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Yesterday, I had to mow my own lawn. Actually I wasn&amp;rsquo;t even that sad about that - it only takes about an hour to really do a number on my lawn. I do the mowing, of course, along with regular mower maintenance. Then I get the trimmer out and move the infringing grass back off of the cement walkways and what-not. Heck, I even took the time to fertilize. It was all done while I walked, contemplating what had just happened. A life event. A first. My indentured lawn-mower had left home and went to college!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adult Child</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/08/adult-child/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2019 13:18:08 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/08/adult-child/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Is that a contradiction? I suppose it doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter - that is what we have now. Ethan, as of last Friday, is considered by this society to be &amp;ldquo;an adult.&amp;rdquo; He is now able to drin&amp;hellip; Well, he can rent a ca&amp;hellip; Hmm&amp;hellip; He can be drafted, and he can vote, and if he were to do something bad, he can be punished like the hardened adult criminal that he would undoubtedly be.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moab</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/11/moab/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2018 19:58:19 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/11/moab/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-trip&#34;&gt;The Trip&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Moab. Or as Mireille would pronounce it, Mo-Ab. Small city of 5000 some people in Southeast Utah, the land of Mormons, backwards liquor laws, and some spectacular natural landscapes. Since we&amp;rsquo;ve moved to the west we&amp;rsquo;ve always looked for a reason to get out here to take in these sights. Thanks to some early travel by Mom and Pop Grady, having come through Denver the weekend prior for Thanksgiving day festivities, we finally had our opportunity to check it out over the Thanksgiving day weekend, figuring it wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be quite as busy or quite as hot as it would in the peak months.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mireille the Observer</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/11/mireille-the-observer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 10:10:26 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/11/mireille-the-observer/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Mireille is far and away the most observant of our children. Ethan&amp;rsquo;s not bad - far better than myself. Quinton, well, he and I are about in the same boat, and it&amp;rsquo;s not a good boat. Mireille will notice just about anything, even if it seems inconsequential. For example, Jenny occasionally colors her hair, but in a subtle way such that color blind me will not notice. Mireille does, though. The other day, Jenny swapped out the pulls on our dressers in our room, and the first thing Mireille said when she walked in the room was &amp;ldquo;when did you get new ones of these?&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2018 Boy&#39;s Trip - Day 2</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/07/2018-boys-trip-day-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 20:50:03 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/07/2018-boys-trip-day-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;day-2&#34;&gt;Day 2&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We started the day slowly, as any good boy&amp;rsquo;s trip would. Since we didn&amp;rsquo;t go to bed until later, we slept in until after 8:00. I sort of wanted to get going, so I got up and started cooking half of our 2 pounds of bacon and a dozen eggs. The smell was enough to wake Ethan up by 8:30, mainly because the apartment was so full of smoke that I think he started suffocating. No matter, he was up.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2018 Boy&#39;s Trip</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/07/2018-boys-trip/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2018 20:29:30 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/07/2018-boys-trip/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;day-1&#34;&gt;Day 1&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here we sit at 521 Elm St. in historic Leadville, CO, our VRBO for the weekend. Ethan, Quinton, and I are doing our first &amp;ldquo;boy&amp;rsquo;s weekend.&amp;rdquo; It was hard leaving Jenny and Mireille behind, but we stayed the course and are going through with it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The trip up here was rougher than expected. Traffic out of Denver to the mountains via I70 was somehow worse than it normally would be when we are coming up to ski, but we persevered. We even took a slight detour going over Loveland Pass, a route that we normally cut short by 30 minutes by going through the Eisenhower tunnel, but this weekend is about adventure and doing things that we wouldn&amp;rsquo;t normally be able to do when the girls are around!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christmas with the Tibbetts</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/02/christmas-with-the-tibbetts/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2018 10:50:09 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/02/christmas-with-the-tibbetts/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We live in Colorado. Our families, by and large, still dwell in places throughout the Midwest. Year after year this generates some degree of conflict, particularly when it comes time for celebrating the holidays. For this holiday season, we celebrated Grady Christmas on the ever traditional weekend of the first weekend of November. For the Tibbett holiday celebration, then, we coordinated an early January celebration. Actually, it was planned to coincide with my 45th birthday, because who wouldn&amp;rsquo;t want to travel to the frigid midwest to stay in remote, rural Wisconsin with his in-laws on their 45th birthday!!!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A perfect parent&#39;s weekend...</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/09/a-perfect-parents-weekend.../</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2017 09:38:40 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/09/a-perfect-parents-weekend.../</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This was a couple of weeks ago now, so it&amp;rsquo;s not as fresh in my mind as it was when it happened, but the event was important enough that I think it warrants documentation. You see, this was Mireille&amp;rsquo;s fifth birthday, her second in the United States.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For the weeks leading up to September 9, Mireille has been asking on a regular basis about her birthday party. She really wanted to have a party, with a bounce castle, and a cake, and presents! Hopefully she wasn&amp;rsquo;t disappointed. The only thing we didn&amp;rsquo;t really have was a cake, but we had a whole bunch of cupcakes! She didn&amp;rsquo;t seem too impressed, though, because it wasn&amp;rsquo;t a cake!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Driver Out There</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/06/new-driver-out-there/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2017 14:52:46 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/06/new-driver-out-there/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As of Monday, June 26, the world has a new driver. Ethan passed his driver&amp;rsquo;s test last Friday and made it official with the DMV (and our insurance agent) on Monday. It was actually a nice thing today. It&amp;rsquo;s Bike to Work day here in Denver, so I rode my bike in. About 2 miles from home, one of my tires popped, and I didn&amp;rsquo;t have a repair kit with me. It was 7:00, but since he now has a license, I was able to save a marriage by having the 16 year old come and pick me up so I could repair the tire and continue on to work. Already that insurance money is paying dividends!!!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summer is here!</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/06/summer-is-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 14:52:46 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/06/summer-is-here/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Summer is finally upon us. Last week was a full week without school, except for Mireille, but that&amp;rsquo;s daycare - even though she calls it school. The temperatures as of last Thursday definitely represented a shift into the ungodly hot area, though in Denver, if you can find shade, you are in good shape since the humidity is very comfortable. As a family we are definitely settling in more and more as the years have gone by.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2016 - The Year in Review - First Trimester</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/12/2016-the-year-in-review-first-trimester/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2016 18:55:09 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/12/2016-the-year-in-review-first-trimester/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I can remember one year when we did the traditional &amp;ldquo;Holiday Letter.&amp;rdquo; It was the year that we were in the process of trying to adopt Quinton, so we were &amp;ldquo;marketing ourselves&amp;rdquo; to our family and friends that year. Looking back, it was a fun letter to do, even if it was not necessary from the salesman side of house. I thought it would be fun to condense 2016 into a bit of a letter to our family (thank you both of my readers) and so that future versions of ourselves might enjoy reading it as well. So, here it goes!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethan Driving Lessons</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/07/ethan-driving-lessons/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2016 21:27:19 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/07/ethan-driving-lessons/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s fun having somebody to drive you around, I&amp;rsquo;m finding. Since getting his permit, Ethan has logged a little over 5 hours of driving of the 50 that he needs to log by June next year in order to obtain his driver&amp;rsquo;s license. When he started driving, and after seeing the number of hours he would have to drive, I told him that there were over 300 breweries in Colorado, and the way he was going to learn how to drive was to take me to as many of them as he could&amp;hellip; Last night he told me that it was time to drive, and that I should grab my Pub Pass and we would stop for a beer somewhere. Man, that kid knows how to convince me!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Happy 15th Birthday, Ethan!</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/05/happy-15th-birthday-ethan/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2016 07:42:46 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/05/happy-15th-birthday-ethan/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s not often that I blog about our oldest son, Ethan. He&amp;rsquo;s not cute and&#xA;little anymore. He doesn&amp;rsquo;t say stupid things innocently so that I can have&#xA;poignant teaching moments with him&amp;hellip; Well, he doesn&amp;rsquo;t do that as often, and&#xA;he would probably take exception to me announcing them to the world now that&#xA;he&amp;rsquo;s all social media savvy and all.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Ethan has grown into quite the young man. Though he is only 15, he has already&#xA;learned many of life&amp;rsquo;s most important lessons, mainly the ones about treating&#xA;others as you would want to be treated - he excels at that. He has adjusted&#xA;famously to having his life uprooted, moved to a new state, and started a&#xA;high school where the lunchroom staff is larger than the entire population of&#xA;his old school.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thanksgiving, Colorado Style</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/12/thanksgiving-colorado-style/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2015 07:44:26 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/12/thanksgiving-colorado-style/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Our first major holiday in Colorado is my favorite of all holidays, Thanksgiving!&#xA;While it&amp;rsquo;s difficult to not be able to spend it with family, we were able to&#xA;make good memories of it by spending it in the Mountains at a ski resort. Hopefully&#xA;this is something we will make a tradition out of, because it was a lot of fun!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We went up on Wednesday and left a little early in hopes of beating the traffic&#xA;into the mountains. One thing you will hear from people that live in Colorado is&#xA;that going into the mountains, while awesome, is severely compromised by the&#xA;traffic on I70. At only 2 lanes for a long ways, many, MANY resorts to&#xA;service by that road, and unpredictable weather, it can be tricky to navigate.&#xA;We were lucky and made it up in the basic standard, about 90 minutes from our&#xA;house (maybe a little more, but it was in that general timeframe).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6 years ago today...</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/6-years-ago-today.../</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2014 07:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/6-years-ago-today.../</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It was Saturday. I don&amp;rsquo;t remember many of the details of the day, unfortunately, but what I do remember is that we got the call that the birth mother had finally completed the harrowing experience of giving birth to who would come to be our child through the institution of domestic adoption. Over the years we&amp;rsquo;ve found that we&amp;rsquo;ve been given the gift of a wonderful, healthy, smart, and strong boy with whom we get to spend time with, learn from, be perplexed and frustrated by, and love on a day to day basis. It&amp;rsquo;s been a wild ride and I can&amp;rsquo;t wait to find out what&amp;rsquo;s next!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sweet Vacation - Alabama</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/sweet-vacation---alabama/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2013 22:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/sweet-vacation---alabama/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;home-at-last&#34;&gt;Home at last!&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Strange way to start a blog about our vacation to Alabama, but I ended up not really writing during the vacation - something I&amp;rsquo;m sure I&amp;rsquo;ll regret in the end as I&amp;rsquo;m sure there is some level of excruciating detail that I will miss out on by not doing this in real time, but in the end I&amp;rsquo;m sure it will save you, dear reader, from the droning on that would undoubtedly result from a real-time, blow-by-blow that I would have otherwise forced you to endure.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Four Eyes!</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/four-eyes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2013 08:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/four-eyes/</guid>
      <description>&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;http://4.bp.blogspot.com/-mM6Rp1_z-EA/URURO35uGlI/AAAAAAAACd8/2YEHZclLe7s/s1600/EthanGlasses.jpeg&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;n has finally succumb to the fates of his genes, or I suppose since we&amp;rsquo;re (yes, that was intentional) learning about heredity in science right now, the alleles that he&amp;rsquo;s been gifted from Jenny and I, and has gotten glasses. His prescription is very mild - he only needs them for class, pretty much, not for sports or basically anything else. But it has begun. Later this year we will probably be putting him in braces (for his teeth, not his legs). Get in line, ladies!!!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Halloween Update</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/halloween-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2012 21:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/halloween-update/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;adoption&#34;&gt;Adoption&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s all begun again. Jenny and I have started pursuing another adoption, this time an international one through the Democratic Republic of Congo (formerly Zaire). So far much has been the same as last time around - filling out paperwork, background checks, talking about my feelings - fun stuff. We&amp;rsquo;re getting to the point where we will be having a social worker come to the house to interview us, so we were explaining to Quinton what we were doing. Jenny explained it to him that he was going to have a new brother. He looked very confused and concerned and asked her, &amp;ldquo;is Ethan leaving?&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Little Triathetes</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/my-little-triathetes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Aug 2012 20:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/my-little-triathetes/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Last weekend was the annual &amp;ldquo;Tri-ing for Children&amp;rsquo;s Triathlon,&amp;rdquo; a weekend long set of triathlons to benefit Children&amp;rsquo;s Hospital here in town. Jenny and I were both signed up to do the sprint triathlon, a 1/4 mile swim, 15 mile bike, then 3.1 mile run. We&amp;rsquo;ve done it a few years in a row now, so that&amp;rsquo;s not what I&amp;rsquo;m writing about - this year we decided to let our kids participate in the kid&amp;rsquo;s event on the Saturday prior to the adult races.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Little Quinny</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/little-quinny/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2012 21:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/little-quinny/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Have you ever heard the &amp;ldquo;Little Johnny&amp;rdquo; jokes? For several reasons, I have a feeling that they might one day be replaced by &amp;ldquo;Little Quinny&amp;rdquo; jokes. Here&amp;rsquo;s an example of one - Little Johnny was in class learning his ABCs. The teacher was asking the class to name something with each letter of the alphabet in order. Little Johnny raised his hand for each letter, but she kept skipping him thinking that he would say something bad, like &amp;ldquo;ass&amp;rdquo; for A and &amp;ldquo;butt&amp;rdquo; for B. Finally, she had gotten all the way to R. Little Johnny dutifully raised his hand while nobody else did. She figured, &amp;ldquo;what could he say that is naughty that starts with R?&amp;rdquo; So she called on Little Johnny. Little Johnny immediately said, &amp;ldquo;Rats!&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Oh, that&amp;rsquo;s nice,&amp;rdquo; the teacher said, relieved. &amp;ldquo;No, Rats, with big penises!&amp;rdquo; Little Johnny followed up immediately&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Happy Memorial Day!</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/happy-memorial-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 21:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/happy-memorial-day/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We had the opportunity to travel to Spread Eagle, WI near Iron Mountain, MI for Memorial Day this year. A friend of ours works for a company that owns a &amp;ldquo;cabin&amp;rdquo; on a lake up there, which they allow their employees to rent by the week during the year. When say cabin, I mean a 5 bedroom, 4000 square foot, modern home that is situated on a lake up north. So we joined 3 other families up there for the weekend.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Happy Mother&#39;s Day</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/happy-mothers-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 May 2012 21:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/happy-mothers-day/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;My boys really don&amp;rsquo;t think much, normally, before a Hallmark Holiday like Mother&amp;rsquo;s Day. Last night, however, Ethan asked me (discretely) what mom&amp;rsquo;s favorite breakfast was. I told him that she liked an egg over easy with toast. He nodded, then said that he&amp;rsquo;d like to make that for her in the morning.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So this morning, Quin (and I, I suppose) woke up a little after 6:00. He watched Garfield while I watched the inside of my eyelids for an hour more. Around 7:45, I heard Jenny stirring, watching TV in the bedroom. After another 15 minutes, I went upstairs to wake up my tweenager who had only 10 hours of sleep at that point, and told him it was time. He asked me what to do, and I told him. While Ethan was frying the egg, Quin made and buttered toast. Ethan got the egg just right on the first try, impressively! Quin then put a carnation in his teeth and carried the plate while Ethan poured some orange juice in a glass and delivered it to mom for mother&amp;rsquo;s day! I have no idea how it tasted, but Jenny ate it all up, so either it tasted fine, or she is just a good mom - I suppose it could be both&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Westward Expansion</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/westward-expansion/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2012 07:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/westward-expansion/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I had an interesting experience as a parent last night and had to share it with the world, because that&amp;rsquo;s what we do in the day and age of over sharing&amp;hellip; Ethan has a test in Social Studies today. They are covering early history of the United states, from Washington&amp;rsquo;s presidency through the war of 1812. As an aside, I make a way better fifth grader as a 39 year old than I ever did as a 10 year old&amp;hellip; That is to say that this information is way more interesting to me today than it ever was 30 years ago. So the way I quiz him is I go through and read the chapters while picking out what I think are key details of the chapters. To my delight, we were talking about Daniel Boone and the Westward Expansion, Louisiana Purchase, etc., and we got to a quote that is credited to DB himself when asked why he continued to move west until his dying day, which was (I&amp;rsquo;m paraphrasing), &amp;ldquo;I need some elbow room.&amp;rdquo; That, of course, made me think back to Saturday morning cartoon interludes from our friends at School House Rock. Since I had my laptop sitting right next to me, I quickly searched for the video and was rewarded with the 3 minutes and 10 seconds of goodness that I remembered. I quickly brought it up and let Ethan watch it. I now share it with you for nostalgia&amp;rsquo;s sake:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Potpourri</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/potpourri/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Mar 2012 22:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/potpourri/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-big-update&#34;&gt;The Big Update&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;First, for the prerequisite apology. My wife and my mother both have scolded me for not having an update out here for going on 2 months now, so here is the big update.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;quin-does-music&#34;&gt;Quin Does Music&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Over the last 2 months, Quin has put his musical skills on display. He enjoys listening to music on his CD player in his room - last night he told his babysitter all about the music player he had in his room with at least 10 CDs! He also told her that he had a really big bed. Something tells me that he is starting to develop his pickup lines early. Anyway, he loves listening to all kinds of music, but some of his favorites are &amp;ldquo;Sexy and I Know It&amp;rdquo; by LMFAO (he sings it &amp;ldquo;Sexxies and I Know It&amp;rdquo;) and &amp;ldquo;Moves Like Jagger&amp;rdquo; by Marroon 5, which Quin sings &amp;ldquo;Moves like Quinton.&amp;rdquo; His moves are not to be taken lightly. He very much enjoys doing &amp;ldquo;The Booty Dance&amp;rdquo; for us (sorry, I don&amp;rsquo;t have a video), particularly when Ethan is showing us some of his moves. More on that later.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>January update</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/january-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2012 20:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/january-update/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s tough for me to write today because my favorite group of millionaires lost to somebody else&amp;rsquo;s favorite group of millionaires in a game I was sure would go my millionaire&amp;rsquo;s way. Oh well, we must persevere!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s been a typical busy couple of weeks. Today was one of Ethan&amp;rsquo;s last functions as a Cub Scout, the Pinewood Derby. For most kids this is an exciting event, but for Ethan and I, we sort of dread it. Neither Ethan or I really understand what it takes to build a &amp;ldquo;good car.&amp;rdquo; Our cars generally make it to the end of the track, but rarely very fast, and always much slower than most other cars. After the first year of innocence where we thought we could possibly achieve a place, we settled into the common goal of not finishing last. Last year we only achieved that goal by 1 or 2 places, and that was in the overall results, not just within our den! So it wasn&amp;rsquo;t too shocking this year when Ethan told me that he didn&amp;rsquo;t even want to make a car. Since I&amp;rsquo;m a den leader, though, I was bullied into pressuring him into making a car, so we did, but we did the barest minimum of work on it. No cuts, he wrapped it in a car wrapper purchased from the local hobby shop, we sanded and polished the axles and wheels like we&amp;rsquo;ve heard you should, and finally finished up the car on Saturday night. It wasn&amp;rsquo;t much to look at, but it at least went straight!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Staying in Shape</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/staying-in-shape/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2011 19:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/staying-in-shape/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Four years ago I ran in my first organized race since I graduated from high school when I participated in a sprint level triathlon. Since then I got in shape, got out of shape, lost 30 pounds, and have been in pretty decent shape since then. I&amp;rsquo;ve also managed to run in a half marathon, 2-200 mile relays, a number of 5Ks, 10Ks, a 20K, trail runs, road runs, you name it. After all of these races, my last two have been the most enjoyable for me.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buyer Beware</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/buyer-beware/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2011 21:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/buyer-beware/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A couple of weeks ago I ran a Webelos Scout Camp for Ethan and his Cub Scout cohorts (I know, the scouts are an intolerant bunch, but that doesn&amp;rsquo;t have to affect Ethan&amp;rsquo;s learning - let&amp;rsquo;s keep this among adults, shall we). The camp was pretty enjoyable - the boys were tasked with setting up the tents and camp themselves, had to take part in meal prep and cleanup, etc. Part of each camp is doing some kind of craft. After observing how crazy the kids went for this Indian neck thing they made at the winter camp, I thought it would be fun to do some kind of craft where the kids could make something and take it home with them - something they could wear. I came across &amp;ldquo;Paracord Survival Bracelets&amp;rdquo; through my searching, which turned out to be right up their alley. A week or so before the camp, I practiced by making one for myself, then I showed Ethan how to do it. After about 5 minutes he had picked it up, and about 10 - 15 bracelets later, he had decided that he was going into business!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethan&#39;s 10th Birthday Party</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/ethans-10th-birthday-party/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2011 14:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/ethans-10th-birthday-party/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;My son is 10 years old! It&amp;rsquo;s tough really to get my head around that fact. I can only imagine what it is like for my parents to think about each year one of their aging children reaches another annual milestone.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;9 was a pretty good year. Ethan&amp;rsquo;s shown a lot of improvement in school, thanks to his mother&amp;rsquo;s constant prodding and encouragement, he&amp;rsquo;s begun to really shine at the piano, and is starting to show real promise at soccer. I&amp;rsquo;m not saying that he&amp;rsquo;s looking like he may be Pele one day, but considering our dismay at his total lack of competitiveness or energy in previous years, this year has been one of wonder! It&amp;rsquo;s hard not to have high, unreasonable expectations of your kids. Lord knows how badly we&amp;rsquo;ve screwed him up already. Well, I suppose we get pretty good contact with him for the next 8 years or so (man, is it that few?!?!!), hopefully we don&amp;rsquo;t mess it up even worse than we have&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ski Trip - Interlude</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/ski-trip---interlude/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2011 16:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/ski-trip---interlude/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;OK, I hope this goes away like almost all other things, because if it comes back and is something serious, I will look like a schmuck. But Ethan had his little spell with sickness yesterday, during which he thought he was going to throw up. He is a fan of the drama! Today, he has a low grade headache as far as I can tell, because he&amp;rsquo;s running around, tubing, and being a general 9 year old menace, but after sitting on the couch for 30 minutes drinking water and eating popcorn he started complaining of a headache again. He stood in the kitchen, looked at me, and said, &amp;ldquo;I hope this isn&amp;rsquo;t something serious. It probably is, though. I&amp;rsquo;ve had a headache for 2 days now - that&amp;rsquo;s not normal, dad!&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6 Feet of Air</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/6-feet-of-air/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2010 13:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/6-feet-of-air/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Ethan belongs to the ski club at school.  Last week we went skiing for the first time this year.  Since Alpine is close to some friends of ours, we were able to meet up with them and their two kids, one of which, Justin, is Ethan&amp;rsquo;s age.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Justin and Ethan were having a blast!  Justin snow boards, but Ethan skied.  Of course, as soon as he saw Justin snow boarding, he immediately wanted to try that.  Jenny tried to convince him that he would want to do that prior to us going, but he didn&amp;rsquo;t want to until he saw Justin doing it&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pre-puberty...</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/pre-puberty.../</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2010 07:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/pre-puberty.../</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;My relationship with my oldest son seems to be changing quite rapidly of late.  This morning after getting out of the shower I noticed a can of Axe body spray sitting on the sink intended for me.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Let me rewind a little bit - over the past couple of months it has become evident to us that we had &amp;ldquo;the stinky kid&amp;rdquo; in school.  Ethan would get into the car, or just walk near us, and you could certainly tell he was there!  Not wanting to be the parents with the stinky kid in school, we racked our brains to fix the problem.  We tried buying him deodorant, we tried making him scrub extra hard on his every other day shower, but nothing seemed to really be working.  Finally, fed up, Jenny laid down the law and mandated daily showers along with a strict regiment of male fragrances.  He was resistant at first, but eventually he came around, so now he is a daily showerer.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quick Hitters</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/quick-hitters/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2010 22:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/quick-hitters/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The other day we were at a party where we stayed pretty late.  On the way home, Ethan engaged us in interesting conversation, as always.  I can&amp;rsquo;t remember the exact context, but he asked something about somebody and if they were &amp;ldquo;a black.&amp;rdquo;  We told him that it was not appropriate to refer to somebody as &amp;ldquo;a black,&amp;rdquo; it could be insulting.  Instead he should use &amp;ldquo;black person,&amp;rdquo; or better yet, &amp;ldquo;African American.&amp;rdquo;  He took this in stride and continued on with his conversation.  After we got home, I was upstairs putting him to bed, when he asked me, &amp;ldquo;Dad, is it OK to call myself &amp;lsquo;a white?&amp;rsquo;  If I do that, am I insulting myself?&amp;rdquo;  I had to tell him that I honestly didn&amp;rsquo;t know&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lots of new words, and the Amish</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/lots-of-new-words-and-the-amish/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2010 10:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/lots-of-new-words-and-the-amish/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Quin&amp;rsquo;s been quite the learner the last few months.  I think since our vacation in April he&amp;rsquo;s been picking up an average of a couple new words a day.  He has his favorites, though.  My latest favorites are &amp;ldquo;nan&amp;rdquo; which means &amp;ldquo;dance,&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;nonut,&amp;rdquo; which means &amp;ldquo;donut.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Quin has a definite love of dancing.  He has figured out how to turn on various CD players and radios throughout the house, and once they are on, he will come and grab one of us to come and &amp;ldquo;nan.&amp;rdquo;  Today he figured out how to turn on Jenny&amp;rsquo;s iPod and was &amp;ldquo;nan&amp;quot;ing to that.  Not surprisingly, he&amp;rsquo;s the best dancer in the house.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Talks with Ethan.</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/talks-with-ethan./</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2010 13:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/talks-with-ethan./</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It sometimes frightens me to think what Ethan tells people about us. He and I are sitting in the car waiting for Jenny and mom to come out of a store and he&amp;rsquo;s telling me about how he and a girl from school have made up new words to a song that I had made up when I was a kid. Or was a parody to the tune of &amp;ldquo;this is it&amp;rdquo; by Huey Louis and the News called &amp;ldquo;Smell my Pits.&amp;rdquo;. I probably shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be telling him some of the things I tell him…&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>March Musings</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/march-musings/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2010 15:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/march-musings/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;On this eve of &amp;ldquo;the closest thing the Irish have to Christmas,&amp;rdquo; I&amp;rsquo;m sitting on my couch musing about my hopelessly silly kids.  Nature dictates that the oldest is silly like his dad, but nurture appears to have a strong influence on the youngest.  Too bad - we thought he had a chance!!!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We were out and about gathering materials for our latest home improvement project, built-in cabinets and a desk in our office (the wood floor was finished up two weeks ago).  After we finished getting some things at WalMart we came across some girl scouts selling cookies.  I have a soft spot for kids selling things, especially sweets, so I bought a box of Thanks-A-Lots (I think that makes 10 boxes this year).  Quin has a highly developed sweet tooth and immediately started saying one of his favorite words, &amp;ldquo;Cookie.&amp;rdquo;  We we opened up the box and all had one.  Not more than a minute later, Quin was again repeating &amp;ldquo;Cookie, cookie, cookie!&amp;rdquo;  Jenny thought he was palming it, or had just put it in his lap since very little time had passed and said to him, &amp;ldquo;no, you just had one.  Where is your cookie?&amp;rdquo;  Without missing a beat he leaned forward and opened his mouth and pointed to it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is that a Baby Ruth?</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/is-that-a-baby-ruth/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2010 21:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/is-that-a-baby-ruth/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I was traveling to Atlanta this past week, so Jenny and the boys were by themselves for three days!  It sounded like things were going pretty well, for the most part, until I was in the Hartfield Jackson Airport in Atlanta awaiting my boarding call to return home to Milwaukee.  That was when I received a call from Ethan.  &amp;ldquo;Dad,&amp;rdquo; he said, &amp;ldquo;what do you do when Quin poops in the bathtub?&amp;rdquo;  You see, I am the poop cleaner in our house.  If it manages to get into a diaper or into the toilet, Jenny has no issue dealing with it.  If, on the other hand, it ends up somewhere outside the &amp;ldquo;norm,&amp;rdquo; that&amp;rsquo;s when dad the poopman steps in.  Unfortunately, the poopman was 700 miles away and wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be back in time to take care of this situation.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No ni-ni...</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/no-ni-ni.../</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Feb 2010 20:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/no-ni-ni.../</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Quin is starting to talk quite a bit.  I&amp;rsquo;m happy to say that he is finally speaking in sentences!  Of course, most, if not all of his sentences are just telling us no to different things that we want him to do.  &amp;ldquo;No ni-ni.&amp;rdquo;  &amp;ldquo;No eat.&amp;rdquo;  &amp;ldquo;No Bath!&amp;rdquo;  I guess you have to start somewhere!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The other day, Ethan, Quin, and I were out to eat and had some time to burn before we went to swimming lessons, so we went to Best Buy.  We walked in past the DVDs.  I was looking at the Weeds Season 5 DVD with Marie Louise Parker on the front - Quin pointed at the cover and said, &amp;ldquo;Mommy!&amp;rdquo;  I thought that was pretty nice, because even though she&amp;rsquo;s older than Jenny, she&amp;rsquo;s quite good looking.  We then progressed further down the aisle when Quin picked out another movie where he pointed at Brad Pitt and said, &amp;ldquo;Daddy.&amp;rdquo;  Smart boy!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Year</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/new-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2010 20:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/new-year/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Happy New Year!  In the name of New Year&amp;rsquo;s Resolutions, I&amp;rsquo;ve resolved to blog on a more regular basis this year!  I&amp;rsquo;ve found that blogging is nice on several levels.  It allows people who care to follow along with what is going on with our lives (or ignore it, which is nice as well).  This is important right now since my parents have moved to Arizona for the remainder of this winter and will be grandchild starved for 3 months!  But more than that, it allows us to go back years later and see what we were doing now.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kickles and Hillbillies</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/kickles-and-hillbillies/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2009 23:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/kickles-and-hillbillies/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Of course my wife reminded me of some things I forgot&amp;hellip;  If only she knew how to blog!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The other day Ethan and I were driving to Soccer when we passed a section of road we frequently pass.  On one side of the road is a pretty steep, tree-covered hill with a couple of houses on top.  Ethan asked me, matter of factly, if the people living there were hillbillies.  To be honest, I was laughing to myself, but calmly collected myself before explaining that they were not hillbillies.  I was a little surprised that I was unable to come up with a really good description of a hillbilly without referencing Deliverance&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vacation 2009 - Evil River Part II</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/vacation-2009---evil-river-part-ii/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2009 16:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/vacation-2009---evil-river-part-ii/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Here it is, the big vacation update!  Of course, it&amp;rsquo;s been a month since we went, so the memories have already started to fade, but I&amp;rsquo;ve uploaded some pictures to our photo gallery and the site&amp;rsquo;s slideshow is now showing them.  Hopefully this gives a better idea of how the vacation went.  To see all of the pictures in the album, either click on the slideshow, or try &lt;a href=&#34;http://picasaweb.google.com/grady.mke/EagleRiver2009#&#34;&gt;this link here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kissing Cousins</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/kissing-cousins/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2009 20:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/kissing-cousins/</guid>
      <description>&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;http://3.bp.blogspot.com/_5WpZdqukbMw/Snoy-qksCYI/AAAAAAAAAlg/E2_67qhpaRs/s1600/IMG_2016.JPG&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;kissing-cousins&#34;&gt;Kissing Cousins&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;These pictures are from awhile ago, but I thought they were cute enough to post anyway!!!  This is a picture of Quinton kissing his cousin.  Man, he&amp;rsquo;s really going for it!  OK, they are second cousins once removed, or third cousins or something (you&amp;rsquo;d have to ask Blaine for the exact designation), so that&amp;rsquo;s probably OK in most You can tell they are from awhile ago as they were for Jodi&amp;rsquo;s baby shower - and they&amp;rsquo;ve already had the baby!!!  Man, I just don&amp;rsquo;t &amp;lsquo;blog enough&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cub Scout Camp</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/cub-scout-camp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jul 2009 21:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/cub-scout-camp/</guid>
      <description>&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;http://2.bp.blogspot.com/_5WpZdqukbMw/Slqcv5kSjBI/AAAAAAAAAkg/Fv2sqELj6x0/s1600/DSC_0157.jpg&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;cub-scout-camp&#34;&gt;Cub Scout Camp&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Last week, Ethan and I attended Cub Scout day camp for our second year.  This year we went on the 3 day camp.  Camp started at 9:00 AM and went until 4:00 PM.  Besides the mosquitoes, it was a bona-fide blast for both of us.  Ethan was able to do all sorts of different activities, including archery (which is is very good at), mini-golf (which he is not so good at), highlander games, knight&amp;rsquo;s quest, etc.  For me, it was a good opportunity for me to see Ethan interact with other kids and adults and how he did in the different physical and social situations.  Let me tell you, if you ever find yourself annoyed at your child, spend some time with other people&amp;rsquo;s children - like 18 of them.  You will quickly appreciate your own!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pets...</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/pets.../</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2009 21:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/pets.../</guid>
      <description>&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;http://1.bp.blogspot.com/_5WpZdqukbMw/SictHSdKNhI/AAAAAAAAAgw/HdHdUmmBbb0/s1600/IMG_5644.jpg&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Quinton and Ethan&amp;rsquo;s, well, all of our pet Barley passed away on Monday.  Two weeks ago she suffered what appears to be a slipped disc in her back.  Her back legs quickly became disabled, and over the course of the next two weeks she lost control of her bladder and bowels.  She was almost nine years old.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The kids really loved her.  Quin probably moreso than Ethan, though she&amp;rsquo;s been a fixture in our house since Ethan has been around.  Quinton just loved her, despite the fact that he tried to kick her on occasion and pulled her hair, all of which she handled without complaint.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sesame Street</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/sesame-street/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2009 20:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/sesame-street/</guid>
      <description>&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;http://3.bp.blogspot.com/_5WpZdqukbMw/SgOXAKs1UcI/AAAAAAAAAgI/tThmBRMUb_I/s1600/DSC_0128.jpg&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Lots has happened since the last time you were updated on my two favorite kids.  Ethan and Quin&amp;rsquo;s only remaining great-grandmother passed away, Ethan received his first communion, and Quin has had his first ride on the lawnmower&amp;hellip;  Let&amp;rsquo;s begin.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To set the table, I used to watch video blogs on the mac while I was feeding Quin last year.  It was nice because I was able to control them with the remote control while I used my other hand to hold the bottle.  One of my favorite blogs is College Humor.  The video I happened to be watching that day was titled &amp;ldquo;Pot Cookie Monster&amp;rdquo; about a cookie monster like the one from Sesame Street but instead of regular cookies, he liked pot cookies&amp;hellip;  Here is the video&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 S&#39;s for Ethan</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/3-ss-for-ethan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2009 21:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/3-ss-for-ethan/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s been awhile since I&amp;rsquo;ve updated this site on my favorite 7-year old.  Ethan&amp;rsquo;s been doing quite a bit lately, now in the home stretch of his 2nd grade year, about to receive his first communion.  But why the title &amp;ldquo;3 S&amp;rsquo;s for Ethan?&amp;rdquo;  Really it all stems from a sad little game I play with my brain when I&amp;rsquo;m trying to remember something.  I figure my brain can only remember 3 things at a time, and then only if I name them interestingly.  In this case, I came up with three things I wanted to write about for Ethan, and I managed to make them all conform to some word starting with S.  Let&amp;rsquo;s begin:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2009 Update</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/2009-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2009 21:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/2009-update/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Happy New Year!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I hope you all had a wonderful 2008 and are ready to endure what is sure to be an interesting and trying 2009.  I have mailed a &amp;ldquo;2008 Year in Review&amp;rdquo; to some of you, those that I knew could take it (it&amp;rsquo;s a 30 minute video of our family).  If you would like one of your own and did not receive one, please e-mail me and I will be happy to send one out to you.  Now, on to the updates.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>General Update</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/general-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2008 12:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/general-update/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;ethan&#34;&gt;Ethan&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We had Ethan&amp;rsquo;s parent-teacher conference yesterday.  He is doing very well in School, mostly thanks to Jenny.  She works with him constantly on his school work as well as reading, basic math and the like.  It&amp;rsquo;s a lot of work, but it is apparently paying off.  While in the conference we were able to read some of Ethan&amp;rsquo;s stories and reports that he&amp;rsquo;s been writing up.  I plan on posting a couple of them to this blog in the near future.  One of them which is hilarious is his essay on what he would do if he were president.  He is clearly a democrat in the making, let&amp;rsquo;s just put it that way.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s the best state fair...</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/its-the-best-state-fair.../</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2008 22:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/its-the-best-state-fair.../</guid>
      <description>&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;http://1.bp.blogspot.com/_5WpZdqukbMw/SKOiYD93ssI/AAAAAAAAAOg/54-FRJW_uHk/s1600/IMG_4576.JPG&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Last week, Quin got to partake in his first State Fair.  He &amp;ldquo;fared&amp;rdquo; pretty well, though I&amp;rsquo;m not sure it was entirely his cup of tea just yet.  Ethan had a blast, at least for the most part.  We started out by getting a wrist band and going on the rides.  This is really the first year where Ethan was ready to go on the &amp;ldquo;big kids&amp;rdquo; rides.  Unfortunately we were there with Micky and her kids, and they aren&amp;rsquo;t quite ready.  Not to worry, we split up for an hour and allowed Ethan to go on several rides by himself, and he had a blast.  He even got to go on the bumper cars while I talked with a couple of Chicago guys waiting for their kids.  The only things he was not able to go on were the rides that had a 52 inch height limit.  Apparently he isn&amp;rsquo;t quite 50 inches yet.  Guess the NBA isn&amp;rsquo;t necessarily in his future!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethan the Triathlete</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/ethan-the-triathlete/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2008 20:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/ethan-the-triathlete/</guid>
      <description>&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;http://2.bp.blogspot.com/_5WpZdqukbMw/SHqq0gOrcmI/AAAAAAAAAKo/7auCkSsTX6M/s1600/IMG_4458.JPG&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This past weekend was the Pewaukee Sprint Triathlon.  I ran in this event last year along with a team that we had assembled known as &amp;ldquo;Big Sky Multisport.&amp;rdquo;  We had our own jerseys and a whole bunch of people.  Ethan was so impressed when he came to watch!  He wanted to be &amp;ldquo;on my team.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This year we did it again, and they have a kid&amp;rsquo;s event.  So I ordered Ethan a jersey and he competed in the kid&amp;rsquo;s triathlon.  Well, it was actually a duathlon this year since we&amp;rsquo;ve had so much rain this summer that the lake where we swim is closed with algae problems&amp;hellip;  At any rate, Ethan is now offiially a Big Sky Multisport member.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A rough 36 hours...</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/a-rough-36-hours.../</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2008 21:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/a-rough-36-hours.../</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It all started out innocently enough.  We were going to church on Sunday morning, after which Ethan was supposed to attend a birthday party for a girl in his class.  While in the &amp;ldquo;gathering place&amp;rdquo; after mass, Ethan was horsing around with a buddy of his when his head got bumped and one of his loose teeth started bleeding.  On came the waterworks!  He insisted that he was in no shape to go to the party.  We drove to where we were going to meet to discuss with hosts, one of who was a dentist no less, all the while Ethan was crying in the back seat.  Luckily for us, the party was postponed due to inclement weather.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The &#39;Forest&#39; is strong with this one...</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-forrest-is-strong-with-this-one.../</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2008 20:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-forrest-is-strong-with-this-one.../</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;birthday-boy&#34;&gt;Birthday Boy&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;May 17th was Ethan&amp;rsquo;s 7th birthday.  To celebrate, we invited the boys from his class to join us at the YMCA for some cake, games, and swimming.  Unfortunately, Ethan has only 5 boys in his class, including himself.  Even more unfortunate, one of the boys didn&amp;rsquo;t show up, so there were only 4 boys there.  Actually, that ended up being lucky for us as boys are crazy!  The spent the bulk of their time wrestling and smashing into one another.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Superheroes</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/superheroes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2008 20:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/superheroes/</guid>
      <description>&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;http://4.bp.blogspot.com/_5WpZdqukbMw/SB5k_9bcA9I/AAAAAAAAAGU/l1FNe50mduc/s1600/250px-Spider-girl-continues.jpg&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s not secret, Ethan is a HUGE superhero fan.  He loves all things Spider-man, Superman (to a lesser degree), Batman, Fast Guy, who he now knows as The Flash, you name it.  He even thinks Ghost Rider and Blade are cool.  On Friday, he had a book fair at school where he become the proud new owner of a Spider-man encyclopedia.  It is a book that has many of the characters from the Spider-man universe, gives a brief dossier on the character, and shows a picture.  He was very excited to show me &amp;ldquo;Spider-girl&amp;rdquo; from the book.  In fact, he told me that he &lt;em&gt;had&lt;/em&gt; Spider-girl in his collection!  He rushed upstairs and grabbed his most European looking Spider-man action figure (he has very many), brought it down, and showed me, explaining, &amp;ldquo;see, dad, this is Spider-girl.  She doesn&amp;rsquo;t have very big boobs, but it&amp;rsquo;s definitely her!&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One Rough Vacation</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/one-rough-vacation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2008 19:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/one-rough-vacation/</guid>
      <description>&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;http://3.bp.blogspot.com/_5WpZdqukbMw/SBkSC9bcA8I/AAAAAAAAAGM/igMQ-L4p3s4/s1600/IMG_4175.JPG&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This past weekend marked one of the most trying vacations we&amp;rsquo;ve had as a family.  In fact, it was one of the most trying 24 hours we&amp;rsquo;ve ever had as a complete family.  Let me explain&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We rented a condo in Wisconsin Dells this past weekend with Aimee and Steve (Jenny&amp;rsquo;s sister) and Tim and Laura, and their respective children, all of whom range in age from 6 months to 2 years.  The weather in Wisconsin had been wonderful, until this weekend.  Friday night on the drive up we witnessed gale force winds along with tsunami strength rain.  Apparently there was a tornado in one of the areas through which we drove!  Not to worry.  The resort we were staying at had indoor facilities which we fully intended to utilize.  Despite the weather, Friday night went off without a hitch.  Everybody got up there safely and the sleeping arrangements were more than adequate.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Trip Home</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-trip-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2008 21:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-trip-home/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-trip-home&#34;&gt;The Trip Home&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;At 6:30 we got up &amp;ldquo;officially.&amp;rdquo;  Jenny had packed the night before so we could maximize our sleep, but Quin had different ideas.  By 7:30 we were showered and ready to go.  A bellman picked us up at our room and took us to the &amp;ldquo;Common House&amp;rdquo; for checkout.  Here we were actually able to check our bags onto the airplane and get our boarding passes.  This Magical Express thing was really nice!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disney Day 5</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/disney-day-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2008 21:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/disney-day-5/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;morning-swim&#34;&gt;Morning Swim&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Finally, our last day at the parks.  It&amp;rsquo;s been a pretty eventful week.  A bit tiring, but definitely memorable.  Today we had reservations at EPCOT early, 4:45, so we planned on spending the day there again.  There was a lot at this park that we haven&amp;rsquo;t yet done.  Also, mom and dad really like the world showcase, so there seemed plenty to do for the entire family.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We woke up late again today.  It was a bit of a rough night with Quin.  He had been very good all week up until, and for the most part including tonight.  This time, though, he was up a little bit in the night, not awake, but fussing.  It made it a bit difficult to get really good sleep.  Ethan didn&amp;rsquo;t have any troubles, though, which was all that really mattered.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disney Day 4</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/disney-day-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2008 22:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/disney-day-4/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;late-start&#34;&gt;Late Start&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Quin was up during the night and we were getting tired, so we slept in a little bit this morning.  Jenny and I got out for a run around the 1.4 mile running path that goes around the resort (we went twice around), we gave the kids baths, then we grabbed a leisurely breakfast at the Shutters food court at our resort.  It was a good jumping off point for the rest of the day, which we planned on spending at Animal Kingdom.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disney Day 3</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/disney-day-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2008 21:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/disney-day-3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;http://4.bp.blogspot.com/_5WpZdqukbMw/R_LqYVNK-QI/AAAAAAAAAEk/Pok-0lG43m8/s1600/Disney-0.jpg&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;magic-kingdom-part-ii&#34;&gt;Magic Kingdom Part II&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Today we decided to try something a little different.  Rather than sleeping in and dealing with the crowds of people, we thought we&amp;rsquo;d leave a little early in hopes of getting on some more rides in less confined areas.  So we took off early for the bus (OK, I think we still got on the bus around 9:00) and headed for the Magic Kingdom.  If you&amp;rsquo;ve never been to Disney, the Magic Kingdom is one of those parks that you can spend days and days in, so our two half days really didn&amp;rsquo;t do it justice, but it would have to do.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disney Day 2</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/disney-day-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2008 22:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/disney-day-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;http://1.bp.blogspot.com/_5WpZdqukbMw/R_Gl51NK-MI/AAAAAAAAAEE/ew70iD9dw4A/s1600/Disney-1.jpg&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;good-nights-sleep&#34;&gt;Good Night&amp;rsquo;s Sleep&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our first night in the hotel was blissfully uneventful.  My biggest worry coming to this resort with an infant was that he would be up and unconsolable in the night and he would wake people up.  Turns out I had nothing to worry about all along.  In fact, I would say that Quin probably slept better at the hotel than he does at home.  That is most likely because we were so close by and it was easy to get up to tend to him.  Either way, it worked out well and I had nothing to complain about.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disney Day 1</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/disney-day-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2008 22:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/disney-day-1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;a-note-on-these-posts&#34;&gt;A Note on These Posts&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m doing these posts a little out of sequence.  I&amp;rsquo;ve written notes as things happened, but I&amp;rsquo;m going back and filling in the blanks as I get time to write them.  At times it may seem a bit disjointed, so please forgive me.  The dates will be posted as though they occurred on the days in which the events actually occurred, however they will not be written or posted on those actual days.  Please adjust your expectations accordingly.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pre Adoptive and a chink in the armor</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/pre-adoptive-and-a-chink-in-the-armor/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2008 07:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/pre-adoptive-and-a-chink-in-the-armor/</guid>
      <description>&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;http://1.bp.blogspot.com/_5WpZdqukbMw/R9p2hOE88AI/AAAAAAAAADA/_sFiG--CP4I/s1600/IMG_3793.JPG&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s official as of Monday afternoon, we are a pre-adoptive family.  On Monday, both birth parents were given one last opportunity to choose to parent Quin.  The birth mother showed up and gave up her right to do so, and the birth father did not answer the attempts to contact him.  That&amp;rsquo;s an important step for us!  That means that there shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be any bad Lifetime movies written about our situation any time soon.  Now, we&amp;rsquo;re still not the official parents of Quin, still only the foster parents.  The adoption agency is now the legal guardian of Quin and all major medical decisions and travel plans must now be arranged through them.  We will also have three home visits from the agency to make sure things are going well.  After Quin has been with us for 6 months, the agency will file for a court date in Waukesha to make the adoption official.  At that time we will get a birth certificate and have the ability to apply for a social security number.  As you can guess, we&amp;rsquo;re very happy about this step.  It is a major one!  We feel very fortunate given all that could have happened.  Jenny was in contact with an adoptive family who had been selected only to have the birth parents change their minds just before the child was born.  I&amp;rsquo;ve also heard stories recently about people who were going through the legal risk period only to have the birth grandmother decide she was going to care for the child three days prior to the termination of parental rights hearing.  She went through the trouble of having her daughter declared unfit to parent so she became the legal guardian.  Needless to say, we feel very fortunate and blessed.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Loose teeth and doctor&#39;s visits</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/loose-teeth-and-doctors-visits/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2008 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/loose-teeth-and-doctors-visits/</guid>
      <description>&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;http://3.bp.blogspot.com/_5WpZdqukbMw/R8zJpT97TNI/AAAAAAAAACw/61RYCJQsjyI/s1600/IMG_3748.JPG&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Today, Quin is 16 days old.  Almost like his golden birthday in days!  Jenny had to go in to work today, so Quin and I worked from home, and let me tell you, he does better work than some of the interns I&amp;rsquo;ve had!  I fed him once at 7:00, then he didn&amp;rsquo;t want to eat again until around noon (my mistake as I got lost in e-mails for awhile).  After that, he slept again until Jenny got him around 3:00, so like I said, he probably did more good (or less bad) than some of the interns I&amp;rsquo;ve had.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skiing on Mount Olympia</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/skiing-on-mount-olympia/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2008 18:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/skiing-on-mount-olympia/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Ethan and I had a wonderful boy&amp;rsquo;s day today.  Jenny took Quin up to meet his aunts in the Dells while celebrating their mom&amp;rsquo;s birthday.  Since it was a rare beautiful day, Ethan and I decided to go skiing at our local &amp;ldquo;mountain.&amp;rdquo;  Really it&amp;rsquo;s a recovered garbage dump, I think&amp;hellip;  It&amp;rsquo;s definitely not a mountain, but it&amp;rsquo;s close.  The last time Ethan skied was last year in the U.P. and he did really well.  Today was no different.  He hasn&amp;rsquo;t forgotten much from his time in ski school.  The early going was a little rough.  He had some control problems and was a little timid of the rope tow.  But after two times down the hill, he was going up the rope himself and starting to be a bit of a daredevil.  He was doing a little more &amp;ldquo;french fries&amp;rdquo; and less &amp;ldquo;pizza&amp;rdquo; than I&amp;rsquo;m comfortable with.  We were there for two hours, each time Ethan would say, &amp;ldquo;one more time down,&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;five more times down.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First Tooth...</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/first-tooth.../</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2006 22:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/first-tooth.../</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s been fun the last few weeks.  Ethan still is getting green slips at school, but he still tells us about it each time.  He also is learning his letters very well and is very good with numbers.  Jenny and I are both very proud of his schoolwork.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Tonight was the annual Harvest Dance at school.  The gym had a bouncy castle and a bunch of games.  We spent nearly 2 hours there.  Ethan decided he wanted to go as a Power Ranger just in case one of his friends was there who was also a Power Ranger.  The best thing that happened, though, was Ethan lost his first tooth right there in the gym.  This tooth has been loose for weeks already.  A few weeks ago, Jenny and I discovered a new tooth growing in behind his baby teeth.  We, being inexperienced first time parents, took him to the dentist who told us to just let nature take its course.  I&amp;rsquo;ve been continually hounding him to keep wiggling it, hoping that the sure bet of braces could be avoided at least with this first lost tooth.  He has been afraid of having anybody touch it except for him, and he hasn&amp;rsquo;t been that good at wiggling it either.  Last night I even tried playing a modified college drinking game with him saying that each time the word &amp;ldquo;bear&amp;rdquo; was used in the movie &amp;ldquo;Brother Bear,&amp;rdquo; he should wiggle his tooth.  Tonight, his worries and ours were finally put to rest.  After putting a jaw breaker in his mouth, Ethan found that the tooth had finally worked its way out of its position.  There was blood all over in his mouth.  He opened up, and I did the final severing of the last pieces of tissue.  Jenny had a tissue that she gave to him.  Surprisingly, he didn&amp;rsquo;t mind having all that blood in his mouth at all.  In fact, I think he kind of enjoyed it.  It didn&amp;rsquo;t hurt or anything, he told me.  On the way out to the bathroom to clean up, he had to stop by the registration table to inform the ladies working there that he had just lost a tooth.  The rest of the evening he went up to each kid he knew and smiled at them, pointing at his newly vacant spot in his mouth.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Long time...</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/long-time.../</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2006 22:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/long-time.../</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;OK, it&amp;rsquo;s been quite awhile again, but I thought the time was right to update some of Ethan&amp;rsquo;s stats on this site.  Really what forced me to do it was some of the things Ethan said to me tonight.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;First thing&amp;rsquo;s first, Ethan has an adult tooth coming in behind his existing baby teeth on the bottom of his mouth.  Jenny and I don&amp;rsquo;t really know anything about this, so we took him to the dentist.  He has a very loose tooth that is about to be replaced by this much larger one, but it is not out yet, and the new tooth appears to be hindered by another not loose tooth on the other side.  Luckily the dentist said everything looks OK.  He seemed to be a bit concerned that he was getting these teeth already since his mouth is not big enough to accommodate these new teeth, but at least we&amp;rsquo;re OK for now.  In the mean time, Ethan is very excited to have the tooth fairy just around the corner.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The things kids will say...</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-things-kids-will-say.../</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2006 16:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-things-kids-will-say.../</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;first-joke&#34;&gt;First joke&amp;hellip;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Ethan told me his first real joke the other day.  Here it is&amp;hellip;  &amp;ldquo;Why is the corn stalk mad?  -Because people are always pulling on their ears!&amp;rdquo;  Of course he followed this up with &amp;ldquo;Why is the bear mad?  -Because people are always pulling their hair!&amp;rdquo;  So maybe he doesn&amp;rsquo;t have that great of a sense of humor&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;clowns&#34;&gt;Clowns&amp;hellip;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It was Jenny&amp;rsquo;s birthday a last week.  Ethan and I were outside waiting for her to go roller blading.  While we were waiting, I started talking to Ethan about Jenny&amp;rsquo;s birthdy present.  Here&amp;rsquo;s how the conversation went down.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 Years Old</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/5-years-old/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2006 08:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/5-years-old/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;My baby is 5 years old!  This year&amp;rsquo;s birthday was particularly fun.  Not only was he really looking forward to his birthday, but he was looking forward to his parties as well.  So far Ethan&amp;rsquo;s had 2 parties.  The first was on his birthday, last Wednesday.  We had the Abholds, the Witte&amp;rsquo;s, and the Kelchen&amp;rsquo;s over for supper and cake.  Ethan loved all of his presents he got there.  Then, last weekend, we went up to Minneapolis to have a joint birthday party for Ethan and Bryce with the Grady&amp;rsquo;s.  Also very fun.  Jenny and I bought him a Rescue Hero Hyperjet, which is this huge carrier ship looking toy that Ethan loves.  He loves it so much that we had to put it in the van and cart it all over the midwest this weekend!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wisconsin Dells</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/wisconsin-dells/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2006 20:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/wisconsin-dells/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We took our annual trip to Wisconsin Dells last weekend.  We met the Hupperts, friends of ours from Seattle who now live in Baldwin, WI, at the Wilderness Resort for the evening.  Ted and Sue have two little boys, Teddy, who is 3.5, and Charlie, who is 1.5.  Ethan had a very good time with Teddy this time.  He gets along with kids younger than him very well.  Ethan is getting braver and braver as he gets older, but he is still a bit scared of certain things.  He had no problems going down all of the kids&amp;rsquo; slides, even the big ones.  I was even able to get him to go on a family tube ride one time.  It was pretty dark inside the ride, though.  After the ride he told me, &amp;ldquo;that wasn&amp;rsquo;t so scary.&amp;rdquo;  So I asked if he wanted to go again, to which he promptly replied &amp;ldquo;No!&amp;rdquo;  It was a fun weekend.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Four Year-Old Wisdom</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/four-year-old-wisdom/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2006 21:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/four-year-old-wisdom/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Nothing very long today.  I just have some nuggets from the past couple of days that are worth sharing.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Yesterday we were driving back from KFC and Ethan could smell some of the food.  He mentioned something about how good the food smelled and then said, &amp;ldquo;Mmm, the sweet smell of french fries!&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Then, today we were outside changing the oil in the lawn mower, and Ethan turned to me and said, &amp;ldquo;Dad, if you eat fire, then you will fart fire, and your tongue will be on fire, too.&amp;rdquo;  I guess I never thought of it&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parent-Teacher Conferences</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/parent-teacher-conferences/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2006 09:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/parent-teacher-conferences/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We had our second parent-teacher conference with Ethan&amp;rsquo;s teacher, Mrs. Matyas yesterday.  This conference went much better than the first conference.  Apparently Ethan is progressing very well and doing a wonderful job in school.  He still needs work on his fine motor skills, but he at least knows enough to raise his hand before he talks.  I guess he still loves to tell stories.  In fact, he tells everybody that he is going to have a baby sister.  Unfortunately, Jenny is not pregnant, so that is just not true&amp;hellip;  I guess he is the only kid in class that is an only child, and that makes him feel left out sometimes.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethan Update</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/ethan-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2006 18:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/ethan-update/</guid>
      <description>&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;http://photos1.blogger.com/blogger/3969/624/640/IMG_1899.jpg&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Nothing special today.  I just wanted to jot some random thoughts down about Ethan so that they wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be lost.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The other day Ethan asked me, &amp;ldquo;Dad, is Jesus stronger than Superman?&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Ethan has quite an affinity for his &amp;ldquo;booty.&amp;rdquo;  The other day, he pulled his pants down in the back, exposing his plumber crack, and asked me, straight-faced, &amp;ldquo;has anybody seen my underwear?&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;He is very interested in babies and how they are made.  He is especially interested in how they get out of their mommy&amp;rsquo;s stomachs.  I told him I didn&amp;rsquo;t know but that he should ask Micky, our friend who is pregnant.  He told me that maybe the come out of their ears.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Last night, Ethan told me that poop comes from your brain.  Not sure how he came up with that one.  Everybody knows that&amp;rsquo;s where boogers come from, not poop.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboy Ethan</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/cowboy-ethan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2006 18:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/cowboy-ethan/</guid>
      <description>&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;http://photos1.blogger.com/blogger/3969/624/640/IMG_1862.jpg&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Funny Sayings</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/funny-sayings/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2006 20:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/funny-sayings/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I can&amp;rsquo;t remember the exact context, but the other day Ethan was saying some pretty funny stuff.  He was talking about liking something or not liking something (what, I can&amp;rsquo;t remember), and a couple of minutes into it he said, &amp;ldquo;I changed my mind, I like it.  &lt;strong&gt;I must be out of my mind.&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Today we took Ethan to the Curious George movie.  Jenny and I both liked it, although it doesn&amp;rsquo;t have as much to enjoy for adults as do some other recent &amp;ldquo;children&amp;rsquo;s&amp;rdquo; movies.  Will Ferrel is just a funny, funny guy.  I would laugh just watching him drink coffee.  He stars as the voice of Ted, George&amp;rsquo;s human friend.  Very cute movie.  I recommend it for any child over the age of 3 (and I think they were all there today).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pajama Day</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/pajama-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2006 07:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/pajama-day/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Ethan is so excited.  Today he gets to wear his pajamas to school.  When I told him, the first thing he asked me was, &amp;ldquo;is everybody going to wear them?&amp;rdquo;  After I told him yes, it was full steam ahead.  He picked out the pajamas he wanted, made us wash them, and picked out some slippers.  This morning he told me that he didn&amp;rsquo;t want any milk on his cereal so he didn&amp;rsquo;t get his jammies wet&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Little snot...</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/little-snot.../</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2006 12:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/little-snot.../</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Wow, has my son turned into a little snot all of a sudden.  If this is what it&amp;rsquo;s like to have teen-agers, I want no part of it.  I know, I know, those are much worse!  I&amp;rsquo;m not sure what happened, but since I picked him up from school today he has been quite a little snot.  He started by informing me that I&amp;rsquo;m not the boss, and that he didn&amp;rsquo;t like me anymore.  I asked him why, and he told me that he didn&amp;rsquo;t like the things I said to him&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First Birthday Party</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/first-birthday-party/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2005 08:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/first-birthday-party/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Ethan had his first non-family birthday party on Sunday.  It was for Robert Dent, a boy from his daycare, who was turning five.  They had the party at M&amp;amp;M Gymnastics in New Berlin and it involved doing some tumbling and eating pizza.  Looked like fun.  Mostly, though, it reminded me how old Ethan was getting.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Ethan also got to spend the day with our friends Micky and Tim on Saturday as Jenny and I had to go to a wedding.  Apparently he was a very good boy, and even helped Micky setup her Christmas village.  We were happy to hear that he was a good boy since it is always difficult to leave your child with friends and have them remain your friends for too long.  He was very excited to go to their house, but for a strange reason.  Jenny bought Ethan a shirt and tie for his upcoming Christmas concert.  The shirt came with a tie, and she also bought him another, more Christmas-looking tie to go with it, so he had two ties.  He was really excited to have a tie, but one of them was quite a bit too small for him.  So he decided that Jacob, Micky and Tim&amp;rsquo;s 2 year old son, would like to have a tie as well.  Ethan wore his tie over there, on a t-shirt, and apparently spent the better part of the first hour over there trying to convince Jacob that he should wear the other tie.  Jacob did not agree, so Tim ended up having to wear the tie&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Ghost with One Black Eye</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-ghost-with-one-black-eye/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2005 16:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-ghost-with-one-black-eye/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Ethan told me a story today.  He asked me, &amp;ldquo;Daddy, do you want to hear a scary story?&amp;rdquo;  I of course said I did.  After which I was delighted to hear the story of the ghost with one black eye.  What impressed me the most was his sense of theatrics while telling the story.  He had different voices that he would use for the different characters, and whenever he was getting to a &amp;ldquo;scary&amp;rdquo; part, he would whisper very quietly.  It was one of the best stories I&amp;rsquo;ve ever heard, though I&amp;rsquo;m not sure I could ever retell it as well as I heard it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mission Accomplished</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/mission-accomplished/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2005 19:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/mission-accomplished/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I’m sure I’ve been more proud of Ethan, but I can’t remember when.  Tonight Ethan showed me that he can snap his fingers.  About a week ago he showed me that he could whistle…  I think it was a couple of weeks ago that he had asked me on separate occasions how to whistle and how to snap your fingers.  I showed him what I knew, but ultimately, it is hard to teach somebody how to do something like that.  I told him to keep practicing, and he did.  He practiced, and practiced, and practice.  The payoff started about a week ago with whistling, when he finally figured out the right aperture for his mouth to make a sound.  Now, a week later, he is whistling tunes.  Then tonight, he finally figured out to snap his fingers.  I think he may have gotten some encouragement from his Grandma Grady, but he did it.  He said he wanted to do it, he couldn’t at first, but he kept at it until he finally did it!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Physical Achievements</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/physical-achievements/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2005 20:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/physical-achievements/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In the past couple of days, Ethan has started doing a couple of remarkable things (in my opinion).  He has a pair of roller blades that he got from our friends Maylee and Jason last Christmas.  A couple of days ago he decided he was going to put them on, and now he&amp;rsquo;s skating all over the house.  It&amp;rsquo;s really fun to watch him skate from wall to table to stairs all over the first floor.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First Snow</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/first-snow/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2005 09:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/first-snow/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Yesterday marked the first snow of the season.  Unlike most years when it snows for the first time, this snow stayed on the ground.  Ethan was so excited this morning to see snow.  His eyes lit up and he exclaimed that &amp;ldquo;it&amp;rsquo;s almost Christmas!&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Funny Things</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/funny-things/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2005 14:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/funny-things/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Ethan has been saying some funny things, lately.  First, since it&amp;rsquo;s been Halloween season, he has seen the Grim Reaper walking around on TV and on the streets.  He has been calling him the &amp;ldquo;Grim Reefer&amp;rdquo; however.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The other funny thing he has done lately is to sing the song Tootsie Roll.  There&amp;rsquo;s just something funny about a 4 year old singing &amp;ldquo;Let me see your tootsie role&amp;rdquo; to me&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kalahari in the Dells</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/kalahari-in-the-dells/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2005 22:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/kalahari-in-the-dells/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We went to Wisconsin Dells with the Abholds on Thursday afternoon. My parents obtained a free night stay since they were treated badly at the Kalahari. They gave us the free night stay, so we traded it in for $129 off of a suite. Not a bad deal.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you’re not familiar with the Kalahari, it is a huge hotel and conference center with a large indoor and outdoor water park attached. We’ve taken Ethan to this water park in the past when my parents were staying there, but this is the first time we’ve stayed there ourselves. The first thing we did when we got there, then, was to put our swimsuits on and head over to the water park. Ethan’s first order of business was to run around like a crazy person in the wave pool. This kept him occupied for a half an hour or so, but soon he decided we had to explore the other regions of the water park. After a minimal amount of searching, we found the kid’s area with an immense rain structure surrounded by fiberglass animals and water slides. Now this was fun. Ethan started out going down the smaller slides and playing around the fiberglass animals. After awhile he discovered a slightly bigger slide that he was happy to go down for quite awhile. All the while Ethan was vaguely aware of some bigger slides on the other side of the structure.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Happy Halloween</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/happy-halloween/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2005 19:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/happy-halloween/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m going to call this year Ethan&amp;rsquo;s first Halloween.  Sure he has had four other Halloweens, but this one was special.  It was the first time that he actively participated and enjoyed himself.  He is growing so fast it is unbelievable, and I don&amp;rsquo;t mean he is getting tall.  Instead of being afraid to go to any of the houses, he actively pointed out the houses that he wanted to go to based on what kind of candy he thought they would have.  In fact, he had been scouting the houses out for the week leading up to the day.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
