<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>funny on The Hydrant</title>
    <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/tags/funny/</link>
    <description>Recent content in funny on The Hydrant</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 09:47:40 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://dogsbuttbrew.com/tags/funny/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Sex... Explained...</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/04/sex...-explained.../</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 09:47:40 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/04/sex...-explained.../</guid>
      <description>Over the past several nights, in the midst of our Corona Quarantine, Quinton and I have started watching the show Locke and Key on Netflix together. It&amp;rsquo;s a nice time for the two of us to hang out, watch a pretty well done, suspenseful show together, and have some interesting banter and conversation as a matter of course. Last night, the episode was a little shorter than normal, and to be honest, our sleeping routines are starting to trend later on either end of the sleep equation, so after our episode was done, the next thing Netflix recommended for me to watch was a show called Sex Explained.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Dead Cat Saga</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/09/the-dead-cat-saga/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2019 14:51:03 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/09/the-dead-cat-saga/</guid>
      <description>A couple of weekends ago, Quinton and I, on a whim, went outside to play catch with a baseball. It&amp;rsquo;s sort of odd that we would do that. Most of Quin&amp;rsquo;s time at home involves playing XBox, and most of my time involves yelling at Quinton about playing XBox, but on this occassion we both decided to do something a little different.
Flash back to earlier that morning, upon waking up I saw that our doorbell camera had gone off a couple of times during the night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quin Said a Bad Word</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/05/quin-said-a-bad-word/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 13:18:08 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/05/quin-said-a-bad-word/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s graduation week. I have a longer, more sentimental post that I&amp;rsquo;m working through, but I had to jot this one down quickly before it was lost to history. Since it is graduation week, we have family that have started arriving to help Ethan celebrate and to help remind us how old we are.
Last night, my parents, Ethan and his girlfriend Rachel, and Jenny and I were sitting around the table just talking about different things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mireille the Investigator</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/11/mireille-the-investigator/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 19:58:19 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/11/mireille-the-investigator/</guid>
      <description>I couldn&amp;rsquo;t find my toothbrush this morning. That may not sound that strange, but I have one of those big Sonicare toothbrushes that would seem very difficult to lose. In fact, where my toothbrush was supposed to be, Jenny&amp;rsquo;s had taken its place, a similar Sonicare but different color.
I had no idea where it could be. Initially I blamed Jenny for hiding it on me. She came home angry last night for reasons unknown, and was argumentative.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Catching Up</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/09/miscellaneous-catching-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Sep 2018 08:52:45 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/09/miscellaneous-catching-up/</guid>
      <description>It’s been awhile on a couple of these, so I figured I should jot them down before time erodes them from my memory.
This first story has been getting good traction in my friend and colleague circles. Before I can tell the story, I need to tee it up a little bit. Quinton is obviously a black male being raised among “the whites.” From time to time that causes some conflict in him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The First Snow of the Year</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/11/the-first-snow-of-the-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2016 09:31:29 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/11/the-first-snow-of-the-year/</guid>
      <description>Last week it snowed in Denver for the first time this season. It&amp;rsquo;s a mixed bag out here for snow. People don&amp;rsquo;t really care for it in the city, like most places, but love when it happens in the mountains, where it is supposed to be. My kids certainly love it, at least the first snow.
Mireille has been saying &amp;ldquo;snow&amp;rsquo;s coming?&amp;rdquo; since about August when Jenny showed her some snow boots she could wear.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Bloggable Offense</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/11/a-bloggable-offense/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2016 09:22:02 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/11/a-bloggable-offense/</guid>
      <description>Quinton loves his iPad, and he loves video games. Those are his leisure time activities, which is a funny thing to say, leisure time for an 8 year old! What he really loves to do is to enjoy both of them at the same time, which is something we try to limit for various reasons. It also presents itself as an opportunity for us when dolling out discipline.
Last week, Quinton had some egregious issue for which he had to be punished.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Sh!tty Morning</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/03/a-shtty-morning/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2016 07:40:04 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/03/a-shtty-morning/</guid>
      <description>Mireille&amp;rsquo;s been home with us for two weeks today. Many of you are probably looking for some post that goes through that in some detail. This is not that post. I&amp;rsquo;m working up a larger post, but interestingly, going from two to three kids, and having that new kid be 3.5 years old, well, it changes how you can spend your time. Ah, material for another post. This post deals with an acute familial incident that happened to involve the entire family in one way or another&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Mission Viejo Elementary Football League</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/01/the-mission-viejo-elementary-football-league/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2016 08:08:47 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/01/the-mission-viejo-elementary-football-league/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m pretty sure I posted about Quinton&amp;rsquo;s recent obsession with Football in a prior post or two. If not, let me just say that Quinton has fallen HARD for football and all things about it. It&amp;rsquo;s to the point where he will actually put down his iPad (gasp) and ask me to turn on a football game when he knows one will be on. If you know Quinton, you know that is not something to take lightly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kids these days</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/12/kids-these-days/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2015 11:21:28 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/12/kids-these-days/</guid>
      <description>Most days are pretty much the same. I get up at 5:30, shower, get Ethan up at 6:00, make breakfast for us, then leave around 6:30 to get him to School. After that I&amp;rsquo;m not sure what typically happens as Jenny just takes care of it. Well, last week I had the opportunity to walk Quinton to school because Ethan had final exams and would be getting done around the time Quinton would normally be going to school.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quinton&#39;s Snowboard</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/11/quintons-snowboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Nov 2015 21:44:52 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/11/quintons-snowboard/</guid>
      <description>We are first year Coloradoans, so we are behaving like them. We purchased season ski passes, even though it is next to impossible to get into the mountains due to all the traffic. We are in the process of upgrading all of our equipment because no Coloradoan would be caught dead with the 10 year old skis that we have!
Since we are planning on going to the mountains for our first trip over Thanksgiving, we needed to get some equipment for Quinton and Ethan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Kitchen Discovery</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/11/a-kitchen-discovery/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2015 20:55:58 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/11/a-kitchen-discovery/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;re redoing our kitchen right now. I have a long post queued up for some time in the near future to go through some of the experience and show pictures. It&amp;rsquo;s been fun, but it&amp;rsquo;s also been interesting.
Last weekend we finally got to the point where we could take out our old lower cabinets and replace them with the new ones. The plan was to demolish on Saturday and install on Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quinton&#39;s Christmas List</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/11/quintons-christmas-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2015 08:38:04 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/11/quintons-christmas-list/</guid>
      <description>Jenny had Quinton write a letter to Santa. Since he was also typing a thank you letter to his grandparents on my e-mail, he decided to e-mail his letter to Santa this year. I came across it in my drafts folder and found it amusing.
 dear santa i want a ps vita a dirt bike a soccer ball a trampoline football gear mostly a dirt bike and a ps vita and halo 5 and ps 4 and 100 dollars and a golden retreiver.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>