<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Bathroom on The Hydrant</title>
    <link>https://gradymke.github.io/dbb-blog/tags/bathroom/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Bathroom on The Hydrant</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2017 14:52:46 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://gradymke.github.io/dbb-blog/tags/bathroom/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>New Driver Out There</title>
      <link>https://gradymke.github.io/dbb-blog/post/2017/06/new-driver-out-there/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2017 14:52:46 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gradymke.github.io/dbb-blog/post/2017/06/new-driver-out-there/</guid>
      <description>As of Monday, June 26, the world has a new driver. Ethan passed his driver&amp;rsquo;s test last Friday and made it official with the DMV (and our insurance agent) on Monday. It was actually a nice thing today. It&amp;rsquo;s Bike to Work day here in Denver, so I rode my bike in. About 2 miles from home, one of my tires popped, and I didn&amp;rsquo;t have a repair kit with me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summer is here!</title>
      <link>https://gradymke.github.io/dbb-blog/post/2017/06/summer-is-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 14:52:46 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gradymke.github.io/dbb-blog/post/2017/06/summer-is-here/</guid>
      <description>Summer is finally upon us. Last week was a full week without school, except for Mireille, but that&amp;rsquo;s daycare - even though she calls it school. The temperatures as of last Thursday definitely represented a shift into the ungodly hot area, though in Denver, if you can find shade, you are in good shape since the humidity is very comfortable. As a family we are definitely settling in more and more as the years have gone by.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Mother&#39;s Day</title>
      <link>https://gradymke.github.io/dbb-blog/post/2017/05/happy-mothers-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2017 11:04:40 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gradymke.github.io/dbb-blog/post/2017/05/happy-mothers-day/</guid>
      <description>Happy Mother&amp;rsquo;s Day to my kids&amp;rsquo; mom, and of course my wife, who luckily happen to be the same person! This year we celebrated by going to a brunch at one of our favorite places, Bull and Bush Brewpub! It&amp;rsquo;s a difficult thing to get all of our kids both out of the house and behaving in a public place, but for the most part they held it together through brunch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bathroom Remodel</title>
      <link>https://gradymke.github.io/dbb-blog/post/2017/02/bathroom-remodel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2017 08:26:10 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gradymke.github.io/dbb-blog/post/2017/02/bathroom-remodel/</guid>
      <description>Our house was built in the 80s, 1982 to be exact. Many, if not most things have not really been touched since then. Sure, fresh paint has been applied to the walls and carpet occasionally replaced, but the &amp;ldquo;bones&amp;rdquo; of the house have remained unchanged for the last 35 years.
That changed immediately when we moved in almost 2 years ago. It started with windows, moved to the kitchen (which is still awesome, btw), moved on to doors, and now has passed to the biggest thorn remaining on the first floor, the bathroom.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>