<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Reclaimeds on The Hydrant</title>
    <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Reclaimeds on The Hydrant</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2015 10:10:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Congo Children&#39;s Fund</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/congo-childrens-fund/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2015 10:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/congo-childrens-fund/</guid>
      <description>This won&amp;rsquo;t really benefit Mireille, but a family in much the same situation we are in has started a fund to help bring food to orphans in need in Kinshasa. We&amp;rsquo;re planning on doing some fund raising to help this organization. Despite your feelings on international adoption, it&amp;rsquo;s hard to disagree with helping children to get nutritious food and water.
Please consider donating.
http://www.congochildrensfund.org
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Big, Fat, and Stupid</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/big-fat-and-stupid/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2014 10:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/big-fat-and-stupid/</guid>
      <description>A couple of weeks ago I got an e-mail from an old co-worker who still worked at my old place of employment. It was a complimentary e-mail, fairly light in nature, which made it all the more mysterious why the e-mail header on my iPad read, &amp;ldquo;To: Big, Fat, and Stupid - From: &amp;lt;name omitted&amp;gt;&amp;rdquo;. Hmm&amp;hellip; I asked him why that was what he had called me in his address book and he claimed innocense.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>6 years ago today...</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/6-years-ago-today.../</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2014 07:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/6-years-ago-today.../</guid>
      <description>It was Saturday. I don&amp;rsquo;t remember many of the details of the day, unfortunately, but what I do remember is that we got the call that the birth mother had finally completed the harrowing experience of giving birth to who would come to be our child through the institution of domestic adoption. Over the years we&amp;rsquo;ve found that we&amp;rsquo;ve been given the gift of a wonderful, healthy, smart, and strong boy with whom we get to spend time with, learn from, be perplexed and frustrated by, and love on a day to day basis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Couple of Quick Updates</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/couple-of-quick-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2013 16:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/couple-of-quick-updates/</guid>
      <description>We just got back from a vacation in our nation&amp;rsquo;s capital. This post is not about that, however, but I wanted to warn you that an update&amp;rsquo;s coming about that in the coming days/weeks.
A couple of quick ones, though. First, Ethan has had a couple of milestones in the last few weeks. As a seventh grader, Ethan decided he was going to run for his school&amp;rsquo;s student council as the vice president.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#39;Cause I like to party...</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/cause-i-like-to-party.../</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jan 2013 20:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/cause-i-like-to-party.../</guid>
      <description>I have a running joke with the boys. Any time they ask me a question that begs me to define reasons for behavior, I like to answer, &amp;ldquo;&amp;lsquo;cause I like to party.&amp;rdquo; It&amp;rsquo;s a brilliant quote from Talladega Nights - if you&amp;rsquo;re not familiar, check it out here:
  Anyway, like most things I&amp;rsquo;d prefer they didn&amp;rsquo;t, both boys have started using it in daily conversations, with improving timing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Catching up with Quinton</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/catching-up-with-quinton/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2011 20:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/catching-up-with-quinton/</guid>
      <description>Neither Jenny nor I are very good about creating content for a baby book. In fact, I know I could not tell you where either of my children&amp;rsquo;s baby books are - perhaps in the top of our closet collecting dust. To capture memories, though, I&amp;rsquo;ve turned to this &amp;lsquo;blog. It worked out pretty well with Ethan so far, and Quinton has been no different. This post, then, is going to be some quick hitters to get into Quinton&amp;rsquo;s virtual baby book.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Buyer Beware</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/buyer-beware/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2011 21:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/buyer-beware/</guid>
      <description>A couple of weeks ago I ran a Webelos Scout Camp for Ethan and his Cub Scout cohorts (I know, the scouts are an intolerant bunch, but that doesn&amp;rsquo;t have to affect Ethan&amp;rsquo;s learning - let&amp;rsquo;s keep this among adults, shall we). The camp was pretty enjoyable - the boys were tasked with setting up the tents and camp themselves, had to take part in meal prep and cleanup, etc. Part of each camp is doing some kind of craft.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ethan&#39;s 10th Birthday Party</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/ethans-10th-birthday-party/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2011 14:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/ethans-10th-birthday-party/</guid>
      <description>My son is 10 years old! It&amp;rsquo;s tough really to get my head around that fact. I can only imagine what it is like for my parents to think about each year one of their aging children reaches another annual milestone.
9 was a pretty good year. Ethan&amp;rsquo;s shown a lot of improvement in school, thanks to his mother&amp;rsquo;s constant prodding and encouragement, he&amp;rsquo;s begun to really shine at the piano, and is starting to show real promise at soccer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adventures in Potty Training - again</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/adventures-in-potty-training---again/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2011 21:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/adventures-in-potty-training---again/</guid>
      <description>Boy, a week makes a big difference. As of today, Quin is a week without diapers (while conscious). Last Saturday, Quin finally decided that he really, REALLY wanted to wear his light-up shoes all the time. He woke up on Saturday morning and told me, &amp;ldquo;daddy, I want my light-up shoes.&amp;rdquo; I told him that he had to wear underwear if he wanted to do that, and he thought that was OK.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dancing Quin</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/dancing-quin/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2010 10:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/dancing-quin/</guid>
      <description>This video is hilarious, I think. Obviously there must be some degree of nature going on here as nobody of the non-adopted persuasion in our family can dance like this&amp;hellip;
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>6 Feet of Air</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/6-feet-of-air/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2010 13:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/6-feet-of-air/</guid>
      <description>Ethan belongs to the ski club at school. Last week we went skiing for the first time this year. Since Alpine is close to some friends of ours, we were able to meet up with them and their two kids, one of which, Justin, is Ethan&amp;rsquo;s age.
Justin and Ethan were having a blast! Justin snow boards, but Ethan skied. Of course, as soon as he saw Justin snow boarding, he immediately wanted to try that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmastime</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/christmastime/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2010 19:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/christmastime/</guid>
      <description>Wow, it&amp;rsquo;s been a long time again! I hope to post multiple times this week to get caught up. So much to talk about!
Well, it started a few weeks ago with Quin getting sick. The sickness eventually spread throughout the house but Quin got it first. The poor guy was just listless, throwing up, no fever, but sick. Every time he threw up over the course of several hours he just did it over the bucket, no crying or anything.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baby Driver</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/baby-driver/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2010 23:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/baby-driver/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;They call him baby driver.&amp;rdquo; My dad used to sing that song to us when we were young. I don&amp;rsquo;t know if I ever heard the real version, but I remember it almost as well as him saying &amp;ldquo;wake up and piss, the world&amp;rsquo;s on fire.&amp;rdquo; Anyway, I digress&amp;hellip;
It&amp;rsquo;s been a busy spring here at the Grady house. So busy, in fact, that we really haven&amp;rsquo;t had time to do any yard work besides the required lawn cutting so far.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cub Scout Camp</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/cub-scout-camp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jul 2009 21:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/cub-scout-camp/</guid>
      <description>Cub Scout Camp Last week, Ethan and I attended Cub Scout day camp for our second year. This year we went on the 3 day camp. Camp started at 9:00 AM and went until 4:00 PM. Besides the mosquitoes, it was a bona-fide blast for both of us. Ethan was able to do all sorts of different activities, including archery (which is is very good at), mini-golf (which he is not so good at), highlander games, knight&amp;rsquo;s quest, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 S&#39;s for Ethan</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/3-ss-for-ethan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2009 21:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/3-ss-for-ethan/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been awhile since I&amp;rsquo;ve updated this site on my favorite 7-year old. Ethan&amp;rsquo;s been doing quite a bit lately, now in the home stretch of his 2nd grade year, about to receive his first communion. But why the title &amp;ldquo;3 S&amp;rsquo;s for Ethan?&amp;rdquo; Really it all stems from a sad little game I play with my brain when I&amp;rsquo;m trying to remember something. I figure my brain can only remember 3 things at a time, and then only if I name them interestingly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Birthdays and Readers</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/birthdays-and-readers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2009 19:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/birthdays-and-readers/</guid>
      <description>Quin and Ethan have been busy folks as of late. Quin went and turned one and we barely even acknowledged it! Well, digitally anyway. In true Grady boy fashion, Quin celebrated his birthday not once, not twice, but three separate times so that he could cover all his bases. Our favorite celebration was the one we had at our house with just our little family, though. It was the first time Quin really got to dig into some chocolate cake, and boy do I think he was impressed!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2009 Update</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/2009-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2009 21:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/2009-update/</guid>
      <description>Happy New Year!
I hope you all had a wonderful 2008 and are ready to endure what is sure to be an interesting and trying 2009. I have mailed a &amp;ldquo;2008 Year in Review&amp;rdquo; to some of you, those that I knew could take it (it&amp;rsquo;s a 30 minute video of our family). If you would like one of your own and did not receive one, please e-mail me and I will be happy to send one out to you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Big Strides</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/big-strides/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2008 21:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/big-strides/</guid>
      <description>Quin has learned the fine art of movement. He still doesn&amp;rsquo;t really &amp;ldquo;crawl,&amp;rdquo; necessarily, but he lilts along like an army man. Actually he looks a little like Igor would look if he crawled. Since he&amp;rsquo;s been in motion, he&amp;rsquo;s bee quite happy and quite a handful. I don&amp;rsquo;t remember if Ethan got into as much when he was younger, but Quin really likes to get into everything!
Unfortunately, Quin&amp;rsquo;s also been sick for the last week or so.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Catching up.</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/catching-up./</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2008 19:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/catching-up./</guid>
      <description>I know that I&amp;rsquo;m getting behind because my wife has told me that I&amp;rsquo;m in trouble because of how infrequently I blog. I didn&amp;rsquo;t even know she knew I had a blog&amp;hellip; Oh well&amp;hellip;
Quin&amp;rsquo;s doing great! He&amp;rsquo;s 7 months old now and is quite mobile. No, he still doesn&amp;rsquo;t (really) crawl, but has developed a rolling technique that enables him to get pretty much wherever he wants to go. He&amp;rsquo;s also started to try out the &amp;ldquo;all fours&amp;rdquo; thing by getting up on his knees and lunching towards things that are slightly out of his reach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ethan the Triathlete</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/ethan-the-triathlete/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2008 20:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/ethan-the-triathlete/</guid>
      <description>This past weekend was the Pewaukee Sprint Triathlon. I ran in this event last year along with a team that we had assembled known as &amp;ldquo;Big Sky Multisport.&amp;rdquo; We had our own jerseys and a whole bunch of people. Ethan was so impressed when he came to watch! He wanted to be &amp;ldquo;on my team.&amp;rdquo;
This year we did it again, and they have a kid&amp;rsquo;s event.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dexterity</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/dexterity/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2008 20:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/dexterity/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m just sitting here doing some scout stuff and Quin is sitting right next to me in one of his bouncy chairs. What&amp;rsquo;s different than normal is that he is grabbing *everything* within reach. He has access to a bunch of toys within reach and he is studying each one of them intently. This is a first for him and quite exciting for us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A rough 36 hours...</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/a-rough-36-hours.../</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2008 21:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/a-rough-36-hours.../</guid>
      <description>It all started out innocently enough. We were going to church on Sunday morning, after which Ethan was supposed to attend a birthday party for a girl in his class. While in the &amp;ldquo;gathering place&amp;rdquo; after mass, Ethan was horsing around with a buddy of his when his head got bumped and one of his loose teeth started bleeding. On came the waterworks! He insisted that he was in no shape to go to the party.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Big Update</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/big-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2008 08:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/big-update/</guid>
      <description>Quin is 9 weeks old now!!! We&amp;rsquo;ve had a good couple of weeks with him so I thought I&amp;rsquo;d share with the lot of you.
First off, he&amp;rsquo;s now eating about 5 ounces at a time every 4 hours. Unfortunately, he&amp;rsquo;s still doing that at night as well. Although, some nights he&amp;rsquo;s been known to go 6 or more hours between feedings, and when he does wake up to eat, he&amp;rsquo;s very good about going back to sleep promptly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disney Day 5</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/disney-day-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2008 21:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/disney-day-5/</guid>
      <description>Morning Swim Finally, our last day at the parks. It&amp;rsquo;s been a pretty eventful week. A bit tiring, but definitely memorable. Today we had reservations at EPCOT early, 4:45, so we planned on spending the day there again. There was a lot at this park that we haven&amp;rsquo;t yet done. Also, mom and dad really like the world showcase, so there seemed plenty to do for the entire family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disney Day 4</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/disney-day-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2008 22:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/disney-day-4/</guid>
      <description>Late Start Quin was up during the night and we were getting tired, so we slept in a little bit this morning. Jenny and I got out for a run around the 1.4 mile running path that goes around the resort (we went twice around), we gave the kids baths, then we grabbed a leisurely breakfast at the Shutters food court at our resort. It was a good jumping off point for the rest of the day, which we planned on spending at Animal Kingdom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disney Day 3</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/disney-day-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2008 21:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/disney-day-3/</guid>
      <description>Magic Kingdom Part II Today we decided to try something a little different. Rather than sleeping in and dealing with the crowds of people, we thought we&amp;rsquo;d leave a little early in hopes of getting on some more rides in less confined areas. So we took off early for the bus (OK, I think we still got on the bus around 9:00) and headed for the Magic Kingdom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disney Day 2</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/disney-day-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2008 22:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/disney-day-2/</guid>
      <description>Good Night&amp;rsquo;s Sleep Our first night in the hotel was blissfully uneventful. My biggest worry coming to this resort with an infant was that he would be up and unconsolable in the night and he would wake people up. Turns out I had nothing to worry about all along. In fact, I would say that Quin probably slept better at the hotel than he does at home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disney Day 1</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/disney-day-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2008 22:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/disney-day-1/</guid>
      <description>A Note on These Posts I&amp;rsquo;m doing these posts a little out of sequence. I&amp;rsquo;ve written notes as things happened, but I&amp;rsquo;m going back and filling in the blanks as I get time to write them. At times it may seem a bit disjointed, so please forgive me. The dates will be posted as though they occurred on the days in which the events actually occurred, however they will not be written or posted on those actual days.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bringing Quin home</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/bringing-quin-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2008 18:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/bringing-quin-home/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday we got the call that Quin was going to be discharged from the hospital. It was going to be later in the day, so we took Ethan out of school around 12:30 and headed over to the hospital. When we walked into the nursery, we were surprised to find two doctors circumcising Quin. We thought that had happened already in the morning! Well, it was somewhat interesting to watch, but Ethan was not so impressed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 Years Old</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/5-years-old/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2006 08:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/5-years-old/</guid>
      <description>My baby is 5 years old! This year&amp;rsquo;s birthday was particularly fun. Not only was he really looking forward to his birthday, but he was looking forward to his parties as well. So far Ethan&amp;rsquo;s had 2 parties. The first was on his birthday, last Wednesday. We had the Abholds, the Witte&amp;rsquo;s, and the Kelchen&amp;rsquo;s over for supper and cake. Ethan loved all of his presents he got there. Then, last weekend, we went up to Minneapolis to have a joint birthday party for Ethan and Bryce with the Grady&amp;rsquo;s.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ethan Update</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/ethan-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2006 18:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/ethan-update/</guid>
      <description>Nothing special today. I just wanted to jot some random thoughts down about Ethan so that they wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be lost.
 The other day Ethan asked me, &amp;ldquo;Dad, is Jesus stronger than Superman?&amp;rdquo; Ethan has quite an affinity for his &amp;ldquo;booty.&amp;rdquo; The other day, he pulled his pants down in the back, exposing his plumber crack, and asked me, straight-faced, &amp;ldquo;has anybody seen my underwear?&amp;rdquo; He is very interested in babies and how they are made.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cowboy Ethan</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/cowboy-ethan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2006 18:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/cowboy-ethan/</guid>
      <description>    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another Christmas Program</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/another-christmas-program/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2005 20:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/another-christmas-program/</guid>
      <description>Ethan had a second Christmas program this year, this time at his old school (daycare). At the daycare Christmas program, you can only watch your child sing because there just isn&amp;rsquo;t room for everybody to be in the LMR (large muscle room) at the same time.
Anyway, after Ethan&amp;rsquo;s portion of the program was done, we joined him, his classmates, and their parents in his room, the 4 1&amp;frasl;2 year old room for cookies and punch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Concert</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/christmas-concert/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2005 08:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/christmas-concert/</guid>
      <description>Last night was Ethan&amp;rsquo;s unofficial first Christmas concert as a &amp;ldquo;grade schooler.&amp;rdquo; He&amp;rsquo;s had a concert every year in daycare, but this is the first time he had an &amp;ldquo;audience.&amp;rdquo; Both sets of grandparents braved the 200 mile trek to see their grandson dance and &amp;ldquo;sing&amp;rdquo; Christmas songs with his classmates. It was a nice concert, held in the church with all the other kids in St. Bruno&amp;rsquo;s school, which includes kids through 8th grade.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Treasured Christmas Memory</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/a-treasured-christmas-memory/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2005 17:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/a-treasured-christmas-memory/</guid>
      <description>Life should be filled with more days like today. It was one of the most relaxing, yet fulfulling days I&amp;rsquo;ve had in quite awhile, and will not be soon forgotten.
It started out last night, really. The whole family went to Kohls to do a little &amp;ldquo;midnight&amp;rdquo; Christmas shopping. OK, it was actually about 7:30 when we went, but for all intents and purposes (from Ethan&amp;rsquo;s standpoint) it was close to midnight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Badger/Hawkeye Game</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/badgerhawkeye-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2005 21:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/badgerhawkeye-game/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday we went to the Badger/Hawkeye game, a thing we intend to do each year. Todd and Theresa, my uncle and aunt who live near Madison, offerred to watch Ethan for the day. He had a fine time, and the Hawkeyes won the game much to many a Madisonion&amp;rsquo;s chagrin. Ethan has always gotten along very well with Julia, the older of Todd&amp;rsquo;s two children, but lately he has been doing more and getting along very well with John, Julia&amp;rsquo;s younger brother.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/adventures-in-potty-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/adventures-in-potty-training/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ndash; title: &amp;ldquo;Adventures in Potty Training&amp;rdquo; date: 2011-03-20T21:06:00Z updated: 2011-03-20T21:24:32Z tags: [&amp;ldquo;Quin&amp;rdquo;]
categories: [&amp;ldquo;Family&amp;rdquo;,&amp;ldquo;OldBlog&amp;rdquo;] I hate potty training. Jenny does, too, for the record. We&amp;rsquo;re no good at it. We rarely stay at home long enough to actually get our children into a rhythm of going every so often, we constantly forget to ask, and, well, it&amp;rsquo;s just pretty convenient to not have to worry about one of the four bladders in our posse at any given time of day.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>