<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mireille on The Hydrant</title>
    <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/tags/mireille/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Mireille on The Hydrant</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2018 10:50:09 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://dogsbuttbrew.com/tags/mireille/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas with the Tibbetts</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/02/christmas-with-the-tibbetts/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2018 10:50:09 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/02/christmas-with-the-tibbetts/</guid>
      <description>We live in Colorado. Our families, by and large, still dwell in places throughout the Midwest. Year after year this generates some degree of conflict, particularly when it comes time for celebrating the holidays. For this holiday season, we celebrated Grady Christmas on the ever traditional weekend of the first weekend of November. For the Tibbett holiday celebration, then, we coordinated an early January celebration. Actually, it was planned to coincide with my 45th birthday, because who wouldn&amp;rsquo;t want to travel to the frigid midwest to stay in remote, rural Wisconsin with his in-laws on their 45th birthday!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thanksgiving 2017</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/12/thanksgiving-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2017 12:16:24 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/12/thanksgiving-2017/</guid>
      <description>Thanksgiving is literally my favorite holiday. I just love getting together with family and friends, cooking a delicious meal, eating said meal, just hanging out and napping with people. I think even more than Christmas, it is the most relaxing holiday out there!
This year, having already done the &amp;ldquo;Grady Christmas&amp;rdquo; several weeks earlier, our plan was to stay put for Thanksgiving. Luckily there are others in the greater Denver metropolitan area that are also too far away to spend the day with family, so they became our extended family for Thanksgiving.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A perfect parent&#39;s weekend...</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/09/a-perfect-parents-weekend.../</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2017 09:38:40 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/09/a-perfect-parents-weekend.../</guid>
      <description>This was a couple of weeks ago now, so it&amp;rsquo;s not as fresh in my mind as it was when it happened, but the event was important enough that I think it warrants documentation. You see, this was Mireille&amp;rsquo;s fifth birthday, her second in the United States.
For the weeks leading up to September 9, Mireille has been asking on a regular basis about her birthday party. She really wanted to have a party, with a bounce castle, and a cake, and presents!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mireille Funnies</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/09/mireille-funnies/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 11:52:46 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/09/mireille-funnies/</guid>
      <description>Jenny was talking to Mireille on Sunday about things that girls talk about. I wasn&amp;rsquo;t privvy to the details of the entire conversation, because that wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be appropriate - I&amp;rsquo;m a boy. One little nugget Jenny shared with me was when Mireille admitted to her, &amp;ldquo;I wish I was a unicorn. But I&amp;rsquo;m just Mireille&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;
Then, yesterday, our little Unicorn proved she listens and absorbs way more than she ever lets on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summer is here!</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/06/summer-is-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 14:52:46 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/06/summer-is-here/</guid>
      <description>Summer is finally upon us. Last week was a full week without school, except for Mireille, but that&amp;rsquo;s daycare - even though she calls it school. The temperatures as of last Thursday definitely represented a shift into the ungodly hot area, though in Denver, if you can find shade, you are in good shape since the humidity is very comfortable. As a family we are definitely settling in more and more as the years have gone by.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mireille&#39;s English Progression</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/05/mireilles-english-progression/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2017 15:18:41 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/05/mireilles-english-progression/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been over a year, and Mireille continues to grow and develop. Outside of some difficulties in identifying colors (something I can&amp;rsquo;t really fault her here) and a current disinterest in letters or numbers, she&amp;rsquo;s developing quite on par with what I would expect. She does continue to have some interesting phrases, usages, and interactions from time to time that merit documentation.
Recently she has started using a phrase whenever people do something that she really doesn&amp;rsquo;t understand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Potpourri</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/01/potpourri/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2017 17:02:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/01/potpourri/</guid>
      <description>As is typical now a days, I find myself delinquent in my posting. I blame my new job. Nothing more. Oh, and having three kids is hard. Not sure I&amp;rsquo;ve mentioned that. Still, they keep us on our toes, and I occasionally remember to write some of the remarkable things down that they do. The following is a small collection of the things I&amp;rsquo;ve remembered.
Mireille &amp;hellip;on language&amp;hellip; Mireille&amp;rsquo;s pronoun usage continues to improve, though her favorite pronoun continues to be &amp;ldquo;him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2016 - The Year in Review - First Trimester</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/12/2016---the-year-in-review---first-trimester/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2016 18:55:09 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/12/2016---the-year-in-review---first-trimester/</guid>
      <description>I can remember one year when we did the traditional &amp;ldquo;Holiday Letter.&amp;rdquo; It was the year that we were in the process of trying to adopt Quinton, so we were &amp;ldquo;marketing ourselves&amp;rdquo; to our family and friends that year. Looking back, it was a fun letter to do, even if it was not necessary from the salesman side of house. I thought it would be fun to condense 2016 into a bit of a letter to our family (thank you both of my readers) and so that future versions of ourselves might enjoy reading it as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The First Snow of the Year</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/11/the-first-snow-of-the-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2016 09:31:29 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/11/the-first-snow-of-the-year/</guid>
      <description>Last week it snowed in Denver for the first time this season. It&amp;rsquo;s a mixed bag out here for snow. People don&amp;rsquo;t really care for it in the city, like most places, but love when it happens in the mountains, where it is supposed to be. My kids certainly love it, at least the first snow.
Mireille has been saying &amp;ldquo;snow&amp;rsquo;s coming?&amp;rdquo; since about August when Jenny showed her some snow boots she could wear.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>October 2016 - Big Update!</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/10/october-2016---big-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2016 19:39:06 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/10/october-2016---big-update/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s October! October has been a busy month, but what month hasn&amp;rsquo;t been, really. So it&amp;rsquo;s been awhile since there&amp;rsquo;s been an update of much substance. So, while my family answers the door to greet and treat Halloween visitors in full costume, I thought I would take a few minutes (or 60) and update the world on the goings on in the Grady Household.
Adoption - Complete I don&amp;rsquo;t have to restate how much work and waiting it&amp;rsquo;s been to complete this, our second adoption.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mireille the Magician</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/10/mireille-the-magician/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2016 20:34:27 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/10/mireille-the-magician/</guid>
      <description>Quick one today. I need to document this, because it cracks me up. Lately Mireille has been doing magic tricks. Yes, you read that correctly - my four year old knows how to do magic tricks. Well, she knows a single trick, but she&amp;rsquo;s OK at it, and is working at it and trying to perfect it.
What she does is she takes an item and puts it in her hand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick Updates</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/10/quick-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2016 10:18:11 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/10/quick-updates/</guid>
      <description>After five days of adult vacation in New Orleans, Jenny and I were happy to be back with our kids, and probably a bit surprised that five days wasn&amp;rsquo;t quite enough to really decompress! Things went back to normal very quickly.
Mirielle gas been constantly about three things - now, trick or treating, and the party that she was going to yesterday. The snow things is pretty funny. I seem to remember her not liking it very much when it showed up last spring, but just about every day she will ask us, very seriously, &amp;ldquo;snow coming?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mireille&#39;s Birthday!</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/09/mireilles-birthday/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2016 08:39:35 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/09/mireilles-birthday/</guid>
      <description>Mireille on her Fourth Birthday   Our little girl turned four!!! This was a pretty special birthday for us. It&amp;rsquo;s the first one we got to celebrate with her! We have sent her gifts for each birthday in the Congo, but I&amp;rsquo;m pretty sure she hated all of those gifts. It was a weird thing - it&amp;rsquo;s very expensive to send stuff to the Congo, so we would just send one of our agency&amp;rsquo;s lawyers money and ask them to purchase something local for her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More English</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/08/more-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2016 09:19:33 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/08/more-english/</guid>
      <description>I was amused by these so I had to post them. Mireille is learning English really quickly. Not all is worthy of recording as most is mundane, but there are a few&amp;hellip;
She loves to eat! And she loves to try new food - but she doesn&amp;rsquo;t always like the food that she&amp;rsquo;s trying. When she happens to try something that she doesn&amp;rsquo;t like she says &amp;ldquo;I like this uh-uh.&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More English with Mireille</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/07/more-english-with-mireille/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2016 21:27:01 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/07/more-english-with-mireille/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been nearly 5 months now, and Mireille has really amped up her mastery of the English language. We recently went on vacation with the whole family to Wisconsin, so I had the opportunity to spend a lot of focused time with her. As the week went on, I started to see how she is systematically adding new words to her vocabulary all the time. First, she will point at something and ask you what it is (she says &amp;ldquo;Ques at?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life of a Single Father</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/06/life-of-a-single-father/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2016 21:43:24 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/06/life-of-a-single-father/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s 9:44 PM on Thursday evening. I&amp;rsquo;ve finally settled down to my computer and a bomber of my local&amp;rsquo;s double IPA. It&amp;rsquo;s the first time today that I&amp;rsquo;ve been able to sit without somebody demanding something or me having to be preparing something for somebody. You see, Jenny has been traveling for work since Monday morning, leaving me, a single father of three.
I&amp;rsquo;ve been a single father in the past.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ACHC Camp and English</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/06/achc-camp-and-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2016 07:58:48 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/06/achc-camp-and-english/</guid>
      <description>Last weekend we had to opportunity to go to the African-Caribbean Heritage Camp. It is one of a set of camps put on by an organization in town here that focuses on transracially formed families, specifically formed through adoption. Yeah, they have organizations for everything! We had been to the camp once before, two years ago, and enjoyed it so much that we decided to move to Denver!
Over the course of the two and a half days of camp we were all immersed with people in a very similar situation to our family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning English</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/05/learning-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2016 07:57:13 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/05/learning-english/</guid>
      <description>Mireille has been in the US for around 2 months now and by all accounts is doing pretty well. One thing that we constantly worry about is whether she is picking up English quickly enough. Of course we are on all these Facebook groups and we constantly hear about how much English people&amp;rsquo;s kids are picking up and Mireille has been a bit slow on that front. I tend to think many of those people are embellishing their stories quite a bit, but whatever - she is a strong willed girl and she&amp;rsquo;s going to speak Lingala, dammit!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mireille Quickies</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/04/mireille-quickies/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2016 08:30:03 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/04/mireille-quickies/</guid>
      <description>I have a couple of &amp;ldquo;novels&amp;rdquo; in the works. Sometimes I let those clog up the works when I should be doing smaller, more frequent updates. So this is one of those smaller, more frequent updates. I&amp;rsquo;m finding my available time much harder to come by with the addition of the third child. I&amp;rsquo;m sure that will normalize out at some point, right? Those with three or more kids, back me up here!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two Days on the Hill</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/02/two-days-on-the-hill/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2016 10:15:09 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/02/two-days-on-the-hill/</guid>
      <description>Preamble I briefly considered titling this &amp;ldquo;Mr. Grady Goes to Washington,&amp;rdquo; but I didn&amp;rsquo;t like it for a couple of reasons. First, I don&amp;rsquo;t really think of myself as Mr. Grady. And more importantly, I have never really seen the movie, and I hate giving false information.
This is a story about a number of things&amp;hellip; Adoption, politics, travel, weather&amp;hellip; Hold on to your seats, and grab some NoDoze. This might get boring!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>She&#39;s Coming Home!!!</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/02/shes-coming-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2016 07:59:33 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/02/shes-coming-home/</guid>
      <description>Riding to my Red Eye     Dulles Airport     Empty International Arrival Terminal     UA 951 from Brussels     At at DGM, Ironic Lunch     The Wait is Excruciating     The Plane has Landed!     Busiest Time of Day     She&amp;#39;s Here!     Confused?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DRC Update</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/01/drc-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2016 08:04:12 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/01/drc-update/</guid>
      <description>So&amp;hellip; There are a couple of updates, but we&amp;rsquo;re still stuck.
The US sent a delegation of congressmen to the DRC to talk specifically about this issue. As has become typical, the DRC responded with things that we want to hear. I won&amp;rsquo;t go into details, but I wanted to document, for posterity, the letter I wrote to my congressmen in Colorado. I&amp;rsquo;ve been interacting with their offices for the past couple of months and have a fairly good rapport going with my contacts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skype with Mireille</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/10/skype-with-mireille/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2015 09:53:21 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/10/skype-with-mireille/</guid>
      <description>We got to Skype with Mireille this morning. It&amp;rsquo;s always bittersweet talking with her. On the one hand, you want to make sure you keep in touch so she at least has some sort of connection, but on another hand it just sort of hurts to talk with her. When we talk with her, we are reminded of the situation that we&amp;rsquo;re in, whereas other times we can sort of ignore it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mireille</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/mireille/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2014 15:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/mireille/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m outing us to the world. Well, Jenny outed us on Facebook about a month ago, but this post makes it official - we are in the process of adopting a little girl from the Democratic Republic of Congo. In fact, we&amp;rsquo;ve been matched with our daughter for 18 months, and are in fact her legal parents by that country&amp;rsquo;s laws. In a very strange combination of power plays and international politics, however, we are unable to bring her home to the United States.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>