<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mireille on The Hydrant</title>
    <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/tags/mireille/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Mireille on The Hydrant</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 14:43:30 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://dogsbuttbrew.com/tags/mireille/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Best Mother So Far</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2023/06/best-mother-so-far/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 14:43:30 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2023/06/best-mother-so-far/</guid>
      <description>One of the best parts of being a parent, in my estimation, is watching my kids&amp;rsquo; sense of humor develop. Early on, it&amp;rsquo;s at once fun and annoying to watch them try new things out and see what type of reaction they get. The annoying part comes with things like the constant use of the word &amp;ldquo;diarhea&amp;rdquo; that Mireille currently thinks is funny. The fun part, though, is seeing Ethan tell his grandmother, who had recently burst a blood vessel in her eye, that she could potentially remediate it with a quick trip to the Halloween Store.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hair</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2023/05/hair/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 09:38:11 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2023/05/hair/</guid>
      <description>Hair is really important to my daughter. This is something I learned early on in her life with us. When she came to us from Congo, she had extensions in her hair and, though she coudln&amp;rsquo;t say anything in English, she conveyed very clearly that she liked them. She wasn&amp;rsquo;t very happy when we took them out a few days later (well, she wasn&amp;rsquo;t very happy about anything, really).&#xA;Over the years, she has been very vocal about wanting long hair and the types of things she would do with it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mary the Tooth Fairy</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/06/mary-the-tooth-fairy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 13:03:38 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/06/mary-the-tooth-fairy/</guid>
      <description>Parenting can be hard, obviously. And sometimes we (read I) don&amp;rsquo;t really live up to the challenge. I&amp;rsquo;m hoping this has happened to others&amp;hellip; The last time Mireille lost a tooth was in January. For Mireille, losing a tooth is a somewhat difficult exercise. For some reason, her teeth are very stubborn, and new teeth come up all over the place and don&amp;rsquo;t always displace the tooth they are supposed to replace!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mireille&#39;s Channel - Peace Out!</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/05/mireilles-channel-peace-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2020 09:03:58 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/05/mireilles-channel-peace-out/</guid>
      <description>For the vast majority of this blog&amp;rsquo;s audience (Hi mom and dad!), you probably don&amp;rsquo;t know much about the Youtube generation and what types of things go on here. I can&amp;rsquo;t say I know much more outside of what I observe from my children as they are interacting with these sites, but let me try to explain. In today&amp;rsquo;s day and age, being a &amp;ldquo;Youtuber&amp;rdquo; is an actual profession that people aspire towards.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mireille, the runner and COVID haircuts</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/04/mireille-the-runner-and-covid-haircuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Apr 2020 09:14:58 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/04/mireille-the-runner-and-covid-haircuts/</guid>
      <description>And it continues&amp;hellip;&#xA;I believe we are about 8 weeks in to this new reality now. Funny how initially I had all these ideas of things I would do &amp;ldquo;every day&amp;rdquo; during this situation. I was going to blog every day, that seemed like a funny and interesting idea. I was also going to draw something every day, which was fun for awhile, and I&amp;rsquo;ve continued it on a far less frequent basis, but I&amp;rsquo;m definitely not doing anything on a daily basis other than just living.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COVID Reality - Day 2-9</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/03/covid-reality-day-2-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 10:50:59 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/03/covid-reality-day-2-9/</guid>
      <description>COVID Reality Day 6 was the Grady&amp;rsquo;s breaking point. There was widespread dissent in the ranks, and those that are supposed to be even and get us through all this were SUPER crabby. Mireille had a big tantrum the likes that I haven&amp;rsquo;t seen in quite awhile, Quinton managed to squeek out some tears at some point, Ethan is cooped up and wants to see his friends and his girlfriend, and Jenny and I were basically not on speaking terms with one another most of the day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COVID Reality - Day 1</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/03/covid-reality-day-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 08:50:41 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/03/covid-reality-day-1/</guid>
      <description>Today is the first day of what I&amp;rsquo;m calling &amp;ldquo;COVID Reality.&amp;rdquo; In Colorado, while we aren&amp;rsquo;t ordered to &amp;ldquo;shelter in place,&amp;rdquo; anything that would be worthwhile leaving the house for has been closed down, most notably all sporting events, theaters, churches, restaurants, breweries, and bars. Oh, and schools. These closures are setup right now for 4 weeks. We&amp;rsquo;ll see how long it actually ends up being (I doubt shorter than 4 weeks).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big Update on Grady Kids</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/01/big-update-on-grady-kids/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2020 09:25:40 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/01/big-update-on-grady-kids/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s a broken record on this blog, but it&amp;rsquo;s again been a LONG time since I&amp;rsquo;ve done anything. There is definitely an ebb and flow to my state of mind that really dictates how much I observe of the world around me, and around the end of the year is a time of reflection for lots of people. So here it goes&amp;hellip;&#xA;This post is going to read mostly as a Quinton post.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Dead Cat Saga</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/09/the-dead-cat-saga/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2019 14:51:03 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/09/the-dead-cat-saga/</guid>
      <description>A couple of weekends ago, Quinton and I, on a whim, went outside to play catch with a baseball. It&amp;rsquo;s sort of odd that we would do that. Most of Quin&amp;rsquo;s time at home involves playing XBox, and most of my time involves yelling at Quinton about playing XBox, but on this occassion we both decided to do something a little different.&#xA;Flash back to earlier that morning, upon waking up I saw that our doorbell camera had gone off a couple of times during the night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Firsts, and a Conversation with Mireille</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/08/firsts-and-a-conversation-with-mireille/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 09:50:50 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/08/firsts-and-a-conversation-with-mireille/</guid>
      <description>Quinton started middle school this week. For some reason, middle school scares the hell out of me on behalf of my children. To boot, he&amp;rsquo;s been actively and heavily lobbying to be moved to the public school from our relatively more comfortable private school middle school situation. Well, he made pretty good arguments, so we relented, so now he has started school at Laredo Public Middle School, right next to where Ethan has spent his last 4 years at Smoky Hill.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quin Said a Bad Word</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/05/quin-said-a-bad-word/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 13:18:08 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/05/quin-said-a-bad-word/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s graduation week. I have a longer, more sentimental post that I&amp;rsquo;m working through, but I had to jot this one down quickly before it was lost to history. Since it is graduation week, we have family that have started arriving to help Ethan celebrate and to help remind us how old we are.&#xA;Last night, my parents, Ethan and his girlfriend Rachel, and Jenny and I were sitting around the table just talking about different things.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teeth, Hoops, and Firsts</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/04/teeth-hoops-and-firsts/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 09:38:11 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/04/teeth-hoops-and-firsts/</guid>
      <description>Mireille finally lost that first tooth! It was a few weeks ago, now. She was walking around the kitchen, and I asked her, like I had been every day for quite a few weeks, how her teeth were doing. Her two front teeth on the bottom were coming in behind the baby teeth. On that fateful night, one of them was finally loose enough that I felt confident enough to give it a little tug and evict it from its spot that the other tooth so badly wanted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Catching up to 2019</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/02/catching-up-to-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2019 17:00:42 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/02/catching-up-to-2019/</guid>
      <description>A new year&amp;hellip; It went and happened again, and again I find myself in the position of having a resolution of writing more. It seems a yearly concern, but here goes the latest attempt.&#xA;2018 was very kind to the Grady&amp;rsquo;s. Ethan wrecked a couple of cars, but has now had his latest one for over 6 months without incident (knock on wood). Brandon got a new (to me) car in the form of a 2017 Chevy Malibu - yeah, I can&amp;rsquo;t seem to break that mold.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moab</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/11/moab/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2018 19:58:19 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/11/moab/</guid>
      <description>The Trip Moab. Or as Mireille would pronounce it, Mo-Ab. Small city of 5000 some people in Southeast Utah, the land of Mormons, backwards liquor laws, and some spectacular natural landscapes. Since we&amp;rsquo;ve moved to the west we&amp;rsquo;ve always looked for a reason to get out here to take in these sights. Thanks to some early travel by Mom and Pop Grady, having come through Denver the weekend prior for Thanksgiving day festivities, we finally had our opportunity to check it out over the Thanksgiving day weekend, figuring it wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be quite as busy or quite as hot as it would in the peak months.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mireille the Investigator</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/11/mireille-the-investigator/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 19:58:19 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/11/mireille-the-investigator/</guid>
      <description>I couldn&amp;rsquo;t find my toothbrush this morning. That may not sound that strange, but I have one of those big Sonicare toothbrushes that would seem very difficult to lose. In fact, where my toothbrush was supposed to be, Jenny&amp;rsquo;s had taken its place, a similar Sonicare but different color.&#xA;I had no idea where it could be. Initially I blamed Jenny for hiding it on me. She came home angry last night for reasons unknown, and was argumentative.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mireille the Observer</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/11/mireille-the-observer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 10:10:26 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/11/mireille-the-observer/</guid>
      <description>Mireille is far and away the most observant of our children. Ethan&amp;rsquo;s not bad - far better than myself. Quinton, well, he and I are about in the same boat, and it&amp;rsquo;s not a good boat. Mireille will notice just about anything, even if it seems inconsequential. For example, Jenny occasionally colors her hair, but in a subtle way such that color blind me will not notice. Mireille does, though. The other day, Jenny swapped out the pulls on our dressers in our room, and the first thing Mireille said when she walked in the room was &amp;ldquo;when did you get new ones of these?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Catching Up</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/09/miscellaneous-catching-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Sep 2018 08:52:45 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/09/miscellaneous-catching-up/</guid>
      <description>It’s been awhile on a couple of these, so I figured I should jot them down before time erodes them from my memory.&#xA;This first story has been getting good traction in my friend and colleague circles. Before I can tell the story, I need to tee it up a little bit. Quinton is obviously a black male being raised among “the whites.” From time to time that causes some conflict in him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christmas with the Tibbetts</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/02/christmas-with-the-tibbetts/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2018 10:50:09 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/02/christmas-with-the-tibbetts/</guid>
      <description>We live in Colorado. Our families, by and large, still dwell in places throughout the Midwest. Year after year this generates some degree of conflict, particularly when it comes time for celebrating the holidays. For this holiday season, we celebrated Grady Christmas on the ever traditional weekend of the first weekend of November. For the Tibbett holiday celebration, then, we coordinated an early January celebration. Actually, it was planned to coincide with my 45th birthday, because who wouldn&amp;rsquo;t want to travel to the frigid midwest to stay in remote, rural Wisconsin with his in-laws on their 45th birthday!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thanksgiving 2017</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/12/thanksgiving-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2017 12:16:24 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/12/thanksgiving-2017/</guid>
      <description>Thanksgiving is literally my favorite holiday. I just love getting together with family and friends, cooking a delicious meal, eating said meal, just hanging out and napping with people. I think even more than Christmas, it is the most relaxing holiday out there!&#xA;This year, having already done the &amp;ldquo;Grady Christmas&amp;rdquo; several weeks earlier, our plan was to stay put for Thanksgiving. Luckily there are others in the greater Denver metropolitan area that are also too far away to spend the day with family, so they became our extended family for Thanksgiving.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A perfect parent&#39;s weekend...</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/09/a-perfect-parents-weekend.../</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2017 09:38:40 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/09/a-perfect-parents-weekend.../</guid>
      <description>This was a couple of weeks ago now, so it&amp;rsquo;s not as fresh in my mind as it was when it happened, but the event was important enough that I think it warrants documentation. You see, this was Mireille&amp;rsquo;s fifth birthday, her second in the United States.&#xA;For the weeks leading up to September 9, Mireille has been asking on a regular basis about her birthday party. She really wanted to have a party, with a bounce castle, and a cake, and presents!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mireille Funnies</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/09/mireille-funnies/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 11:52:46 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/09/mireille-funnies/</guid>
      <description>Jenny was talking to Mireille on Sunday about things that girls talk about. I wasn&amp;rsquo;t privvy to the details of the entire conversation, because that wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be appropriate - I&amp;rsquo;m a boy. One little nugget Jenny shared with me was when Mireille admitted to her, &amp;ldquo;I wish I was a unicorn. But I&amp;rsquo;m just Mireille&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;&#xA;Then, yesterday, our little Unicorn proved she listens and absorbs way more than she ever lets on.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summer is here!</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/06/summer-is-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 14:52:46 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/06/summer-is-here/</guid>
      <description>Summer is finally upon us. Last week was a full week without school, except for Mireille, but that&amp;rsquo;s daycare - even though she calls it school. The temperatures as of last Thursday definitely represented a shift into the ungodly hot area, though in Denver, if you can find shade, you are in good shape since the humidity is very comfortable. As a family we are definitely settling in more and more as the years have gone by.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mireille&#39;s English Progression</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/05/mireilles-english-progression/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2017 15:18:41 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/05/mireilles-english-progression/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been over a year, and Mireille continues to grow and develop. Outside of some difficulties in identifying colors (something I can&amp;rsquo;t really fault her here) and a current disinterest in letters or numbers, she&amp;rsquo;s developing quite on par with what I would expect. She does continue to have some interesting phrases, usages, and interactions from time to time that merit documentation.&#xA;Recently she has started using a phrase whenever people do something that she really doesn&amp;rsquo;t understand.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Potpourri</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/01/potpourri/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2017 17:02:48 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/01/potpourri/</guid>
      <description>As is typical now a days, I find myself delinquent in my posting. I blame my new job. Nothing more. Oh, and having three kids is hard. Not sure I&amp;rsquo;ve mentioned that. Still, they keep us on our toes, and I occasionally remember to write some of the remarkable things down that they do. The following is a small collection of the things I&amp;rsquo;ve remembered.&#xA;Mireille &amp;hellip;on language&amp;hellip; Mireille&amp;rsquo;s pronoun usage continues to improve, though her favorite pronoun continues to be &amp;ldquo;him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2016 - The Year in Review - First Trimester</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/12/2016-the-year-in-review-first-trimester/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2016 18:55:09 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/12/2016-the-year-in-review-first-trimester/</guid>
      <description>I can remember one year when we did the traditional &amp;ldquo;Holiday Letter.&amp;rdquo; It was the year that we were in the process of trying to adopt Quinton, so we were &amp;ldquo;marketing ourselves&amp;rdquo; to our family and friends that year. Looking back, it was a fun letter to do, even if it was not necessary from the salesman side of house. I thought it would be fun to condense 2016 into a bit of a letter to our family (thank you both of my readers) and so that future versions of ourselves might enjoy reading it as well.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The First Snow of the Year</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/11/the-first-snow-of-the-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2016 09:31:29 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/11/the-first-snow-of-the-year/</guid>
      <description>Last week it snowed in Denver for the first time this season. It&amp;rsquo;s a mixed bag out here for snow. People don&amp;rsquo;t really care for it in the city, like most places, but love when it happens in the mountains, where it is supposed to be. My kids certainly love it, at least the first snow.&#xA;Mireille has been saying &amp;ldquo;snow&amp;rsquo;s coming?&amp;rdquo; since about August when Jenny showed her some snow boots she could wear.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>October 2016 - Big Update!</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/10/october-2016-big-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2016 19:39:06 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/10/october-2016-big-update/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s October! October has been a busy month, but what month hasn&amp;rsquo;t been, really. So it&amp;rsquo;s been awhile since there&amp;rsquo;s been an update of much substance. So, while my family answers the door to greet and treat Halloween visitors in full costume, I thought I would take a few minutes (or 60) and update the world on the goings on in the Grady Household.&#xA;Adoption - Complete I don&amp;rsquo;t have to restate how much work and waiting it&amp;rsquo;s been to complete this, our second adoption.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mireille the Magician</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/10/mireille-the-magician/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2016 20:34:27 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/10/mireille-the-magician/</guid>
      <description>Quick one today. I need to document this, because it cracks me up. Lately Mireille has been doing magic tricks. Yes, you read that correctly - my four year old knows how to do magic tricks. Well, she knows a single trick, but she&amp;rsquo;s OK at it, and is working at it and trying to perfect it.&#xA;What she does is she takes an item and puts it in her hand.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quick Updates</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/10/quick-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2016 10:18:11 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/10/quick-updates/</guid>
      <description>After five days of adult vacation in New Orleans, Jenny and I were happy to be back with our kids, and probably a bit surprised that five days wasn&amp;rsquo;t quite enough to really decompress! Things went back to normal very quickly.&#xA;Mirielle gas been constantly about three things - now, trick or treating, and the party that she was going to yesterday. The snow things is pretty funny. I seem to remember her not liking it very much when it showed up last spring, but just about every day she will ask us, very seriously, &amp;ldquo;snow coming?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mireille&#39;s Birthday!</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/09/mireilles-birthday/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2016 08:39:35 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/09/mireilles-birthday/</guid>
      <description>Mireille on her Fourth Birthday Our little girl turned four!!! This was a pretty special birthday for us. It&amp;rsquo;s the first one we got to celebrate with her! We have sent her gifts for each birthday in the Congo, but I&amp;rsquo;m pretty sure she hated all of those gifts. It was a weird thing - it&amp;rsquo;s very expensive to send stuff to the Congo, so we would just send one of our agency&amp;rsquo;s lawyers money and ask them to purchase something local for her.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More English</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/08/more-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2016 09:19:33 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/08/more-english/</guid>
      <description>I was amused by these so I had to post them. Mireille is learning English really quickly. Not all is worthy of recording as most is mundane, but there are a few&amp;hellip;&#xA;She loves to eat! And she loves to try new food - but she doesn&amp;rsquo;t always like the food that she&amp;rsquo;s trying. When she happens to try something that she doesn&amp;rsquo;t like she says &amp;ldquo;I like this uh-uh.&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More English with Mireille</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/07/more-english-with-mireille/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2016 21:27:01 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/07/more-english-with-mireille/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been nearly 5 months now, and Mireille has really amped up her mastery of the English language. We recently went on vacation with the whole family to Wisconsin, so I had the opportunity to spend a lot of focused time with her. As the week went on, I started to see how she is systematically adding new words to her vocabulary all the time. First, she will point at something and ask you what it is (she says &amp;ldquo;Ques at?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Life of a Single Father</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/06/life-of-a-single-father/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2016 21:43:24 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/06/life-of-a-single-father/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s 9:44 PM on Thursday evening. I&amp;rsquo;ve finally settled down to my computer and a bomber of my local&amp;rsquo;s double IPA. It&amp;rsquo;s the first time today that I&amp;rsquo;ve been able to sit without somebody demanding something or me having to be preparing something for somebody. You see, Jenny has been traveling for work since Monday morning, leaving me, a single father of three.&#xA;I&amp;rsquo;ve been a single father in the past.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ACHC Camp and English</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/06/achc-camp-and-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2016 07:58:48 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/06/achc-camp-and-english/</guid>
      <description>Last weekend we had to opportunity to go to the African-Caribbean Heritage Camp. It is one of a set of camps put on by an organization in town here that focuses on transracially formed families, specifically formed through adoption. Yeah, they have organizations for everything! We had been to the camp once before, two years ago, and enjoyed it so much that we decided to move to Denver!&#xA;Over the course of the two and a half days of camp we were all immersed with people in a very similar situation to our family.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning English</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/05/learning-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2016 07:57:13 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/05/learning-english/</guid>
      <description>Mireille has been in the US for around 2 months now and by all accounts is doing pretty well. One thing that we constantly worry about is whether she is picking up English quickly enough. Of course we are on all these Facebook groups and we constantly hear about how much English people&amp;rsquo;s kids are picking up and Mireille has been a bit slow on that front. I tend to think many of those people are embellishing their stories quite a bit, but whatever - she is a strong willed girl and she&amp;rsquo;s going to speak Lingala, dammit!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mireille Quickies</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/04/mireille-quickies/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2016 08:30:03 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/04/mireille-quickies/</guid>
      <description>I have a couple of &amp;ldquo;novels&amp;rdquo; in the works. Sometimes I let those clog up the works when I should be doing smaller, more frequent updates. So this is one of those smaller, more frequent updates. I&amp;rsquo;m finding my available time much harder to come by with the addition of the third child. I&amp;rsquo;m sure that will normalize out at some point, right? Those with three or more kids, back me up here!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two Days on the Hill</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/02/two-days-on-the-hill/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2016 10:15:09 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/02/two-days-on-the-hill/</guid>
      <description>Preamble I briefly considered titling this &amp;ldquo;Mr. Grady Goes to Washington,&amp;rdquo; but I didn&amp;rsquo;t like it for a couple of reasons. First, I don&amp;rsquo;t really think of myself as Mr. Grady. And more importantly, I have never really seen the movie, and I hate giving false information.&#xA;This is a story about a number of things&amp;hellip; Adoption, politics, travel, weather&amp;hellip; Hold on to your seats, and grab some NoDoze. This might get boring!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>She&#39;s Coming Home!!!</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/02/shes-coming-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2016 07:59:33 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/02/shes-coming-home/</guid>
      <description>Riding to my Red Eye Dulles Airport Empty International Arrival Terminal UA 951 from Brussels At at DGM, Ironic Lunch The Wait is Excruciating The Plane has Landed! Busiest Time of Day She&amp;#39;s Here! Confused? Proof - in the U.S. Playing Dress-up And... Out. Playing with Mama Women, they be shoppin! Playing with Yaya Starting the Hair Restoration Project Left on the red-eye on Saturday night. Nothing open in the airport.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRC Update</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/01/drc-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2016 08:04:12 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/01/drc-update/</guid>
      <description>So&amp;hellip; There are a couple of updates, but we&amp;rsquo;re still stuck.&#xA;The US sent a delegation of congressmen to the DRC to talk specifically about this issue. As has become typical, the DRC responded with things that we want to hear. I won&amp;rsquo;t go into details, but I wanted to document, for posterity, the letter I wrote to my congressmen in Colorado. I&amp;rsquo;ve been interacting with their offices for the past couple of months and have a fairly good rapport going with my contacts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skype with Mireille</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/10/skype-with-mireille/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2015 09:53:21 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/10/skype-with-mireille/</guid>
      <description>We got to Skype with Mireille this morning. It&amp;rsquo;s always bittersweet talking with her. On the one hand, you want to make sure you keep in touch so she at least has some sort of connection, but on another hand it just sort of hurts to talk with her. When we talk with her, we are reminded of the situation that we&amp;rsquo;re in, whereas other times we can sort of ignore it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Great Congolese Caper - Day 8 - On the way home</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-great-congolese-caper---day-8---on-the-way-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2015 14:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-great-congolese-caper---day-8---on-the-way-home/</guid>
      <description>Kinshasa - Day 7 My last day. I feel bad, but I was looking forward to this in some ways. Over the last 5 days, Mireille has turned into a typical 2 year old, and taking care of 2 year olds is HARD! Particularly by yourself. Luckily, when you have nothing else to do, it makes it much easier. It&amp;rsquo;s much easier to completely invest in what the child is saying and doing, which I did - once I got done showering, washing the dishes, and packing (I&amp;rsquo;m such an adult).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Great Congolese Caper - Day 7 - Kinshasa</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-great-congolese-caper---day-7---kinshasa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2015 11:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-great-congolese-caper---day-7---kinshasa/</guid>
      <description>Kinshasa - Day 6 Getting down to it! Today I&amp;rsquo;m nervous again, but that hasn&amp;rsquo;t changed much from day 1 here, or day -2 for that matter.&#xA;Last night started out rough. Mireille was restless. She didn&amp;rsquo;t fall out of bed, but was up like 3 times up until about 1:00 AM. She didn&amp;rsquo;t cry or anything, but she got out of bed and asked me to hold her. After rocking her to sleep the other two times, I convinced her to just sleep in my bed with me the last time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Great Congolese Caper - Day 6 - Kinshasa</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-great-congolese-caper---day-6---kinshasa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2015 11:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-great-congolese-caper---day-6---kinshasa/</guid>
      <description>Kinshasa - Day 5 It&amp;rsquo;s a hotel day - all day at the hotel. It&amp;rsquo;s a good and a bad thing. Getting out would be nice simply to stave off the boredom, but it also allows for a very concentrated, focused time for just hanging out with your child - something I&amp;rsquo;m not sure I ever did so much with the boys, or at the very least don&amp;rsquo;t do it anymore…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Great Congolese Caper - Day 5 - Kinshasa and Surrounding Areas</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-great-congolese-caper---day-5---kinshasa-and-surrounding-areas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2015 09:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-great-congolese-caper---day-5---kinshasa-and-surrounding-areas/</guid>
      <description>Kinshasa - Day 4 Bad habits I&amp;rsquo;m already allowing my daughter to develop, because, hey, she&amp;rsquo;s under a lot of stress just hanging out with me. I hope I&amp;rsquo;m not setting myself up for bad things later:&#xA;Drinking soda - this is a big no-no for the sub-40ers in our household, but Mireille has already had soda every day I&amp;rsquo;ve been with her. She likes it. Not brushing her teeth - it&amp;rsquo;s difficult enough to get her to open her mouth for me, much less brush.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Great Congolese Caper - Day 3 - Kinshasa</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-great-congolese-caper---day-3---kinshasa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2015 08:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-great-congolese-caper---day-3---kinshasa/</guid>
      <description>Kinshasa - Day 2 After a rough night night, I managed to get up and get myself together by 9:00, when Papa John was schedule to show up so we could go grocery shopping. By the time he showed up, though, it was 10:30. Traffic… Common problem in Kinshasa! By then, we took off to ShopRite, a local, modern supermarket, where I purchased my groceries for the week. It was a little nerve wracking buying groceries for the week, let me tell you.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Great Congolese Caper - Day 4 - Kinshasa</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-great-congolese-caper---day-4---kinshasa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2015 08:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-great-congolese-caper---day-4---kinshasa/</guid>
      <description>Kinshasa - Day 3 Today, I met my daughter! Yes, I met her yesterday, but that version of Mireille was guarded, afraid, and sullen. She&amp;rsquo;s asleep now - hopefully for the night. Today we made very good progress, and I am beyond excited!&#xA;The morning started out not so well. I slept terribly last night, by that I mean I didn&amp;rsquo;t really sleep at all. I fell asleep around 10:00, but Mireille fell out of bed at 10:45, and I didn&amp;rsquo;t sleep after that.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Great Congolese Caper - Day 2 - Kinshasa</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-great-congolese-caper---day-2---kinshasa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2015 08:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-great-congolese-caper---day-2---kinshasa/</guid>
      <description>Kinshasa - Day 1 - Airport to the Hotel I was happy when I landed in Paris that I finally got a text message back from my guide, Papa John. That made me feel much more comfortable about landing in Kinshasa, seeing as how I’ve read many bad stories about the experience.&#xA;It is 6:30 local time on Sunday evening as I land, and it is completely dark already. Since I was in the middle of the plane, I didn’t get a good look at the landing, but what I could see, there didn’t seem to be too many lights.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Great Congolese Caper - Day 2 - Paris, France</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-great-congolese-caper---day-2---paris-france/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2015 08:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-great-congolese-caper---day-2---paris-france/</guid>
      <description>Paris - Charles De Gaul Airport I landed around 8:00 local time in Charles De Gaul Airport outside of Paris, France. For my first trip to France, it was a little underwhelming. I suppose it’s true what they say that you don’t really visit a country when you visit the airport…&#xA;After disembarking my flight, I followed the hallways and signage to where my next flight was taking off, Terminal 2E the K gates (I think).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Great Congolese Caper - Day 1 - In the Air</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-great-congolese-caper---day-1---in-the-air/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2015 08:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-great-congolese-caper---day-1---in-the-air/</guid>
      <description>Seat 9a to MSP Leg one is done. Yes, the easiest leg, but significant nonetheless. My seat wasn&amp;rsquo;t bad - I was on the window next to an older woman who didn&amp;rsquo;t take up too much room, so that was good.&#xA;Things I learned from this step of the journey:&#xA;My earbuds suck. So much so that I have already replaced them with some cheap on ear headphones so I don&amp;rsquo;t have to monkey with them the whole time on the next two flights.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Great Congolese Caper - Day 2 - In the Air</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-great-congolese-caper---day-2---in-the-air/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2015 08:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-great-congolese-caper---day-2---in-the-air/</guid>
      <description>Seat 33G to Kinshasa I&amp;rsquo;m Tired!&#xA;Despite there only being like 50 people in the gate area, this flight is completely full! I&amp;rsquo;m on the aisle in the middle section among the cattle again. The seat&amp;rsquo;s not bad, though there&amp;rsquo;s little leg room due to a heater or some box that is in my leg area. This is a cutting edge plane&amp;hellip; from the 90s. It has screens in each of the seatbacks that are touch sensitive (sort of) and retain the old 4:3 aspect ration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Great Congolese Caper - Day 1 - Milwaukee</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-great-congolese-caper---day-1---milwaukee/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2015 08:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-great-congolese-caper---day-1---milwaukee/</guid>
      <description>Saturday, 7-Feb-2015, Milwaukee, WI, USA So it begins… The trip I&amp;rsquo;ve been both dreading and anticipating has finally started. As I sit here in General Mitchell International Airport, I am anxious and hopeful at what the next week will bring.&#xA;We&amp;rsquo;re adopting a child from the Democratic Republic of Congo. Mireille is her name, and she is 2 and a half years old. She&amp;rsquo;s been our daughter by Congolese law for over 6 months, but politics and what appears to be corruption have prevented us from bringing her home to live with us in the U.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mireille</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/mireille/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2014 15:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/mireille/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m outing us to the world. Well, Jenny outed us on Facebook about a month ago, but this post makes it official - we are in the process of adopting a little girl from the Democratic Republic of Congo. In fact, we&amp;rsquo;ve been matched with our daughter for 18 months, and are in fact her legal parents by that country&amp;rsquo;s laws. In a very strange combination of power plays and international politics, however, we are unable to bring her home to the United States.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
