<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mireille on The Hydrant</title>
    <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/tags/mireille/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Mireille on The Hydrant</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 14:43:30 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://dogsbuttbrew.com/tags/mireille/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Best Mother So Far</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2023/06/best-mother-so-far/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 14:43:30 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2023/06/best-mother-so-far/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;One of the best parts of being a parent, in my estimation, is watching my kids&amp;rsquo; sense of humor develop. Early on, it&amp;rsquo;s at once fun and annoying to watch them try new things out and see what type of reaction they get. The annoying part comes with things like the constant use of the word &amp;ldquo;diarhea&amp;rdquo; that Mireille currently thinks is funny. The fun part, though, is seeing Ethan tell his grandmother, who had recently burst a blood vessel in her eye, that she could potentially remediate it with a quick trip to the Halloween Store.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hair</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2023/05/hair/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 09:38:11 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2023/05/hair/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hair is really important to my daughter. This is something I learned early on in her life with us. When she came to us from Congo, she had extensions in her hair and, though she coudln&amp;rsquo;t say anything in English, she conveyed very clearly that she liked them. She wasn&amp;rsquo;t very happy when we took them out a few days later (well, she wasn&amp;rsquo;t very happy about anything, really).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Over the years, she has been very vocal about wanting long hair and the types of things she would do with it. Jenny has done wonders caring for Mireille&amp;rsquo;s hair, but there&amp;rsquo;s just not much you can do with hair as curly as hers to make it long like she wanted it!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mary the Tooth Fairy</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/06/mary-the-tooth-fairy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 13:03:38 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/06/mary-the-tooth-fairy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Parenting can be hard, obviously. And sometimes we (read I) don&amp;rsquo;t really live up to the challenge. I&amp;rsquo;m hoping this has happened to others&amp;hellip; The last time Mireille lost a tooth was in January. For Mireille, losing a tooth is a somewhat difficult exercise. For some reason, her teeth are very stubborn, and new teeth come up all over the place and don&amp;rsquo;t always displace the tooth they are supposed to replace! So for a few of her teeth, I&amp;rsquo;ve tried my dad-best to extract them, only to end up in tears (both of us, actually), and she&amp;rsquo;s had to go to the dentist to get them out. That&amp;rsquo;s what had happened in January the last time she lost one!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mireille&#39;s Channel - Peace Out!</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/05/mireilles-channel-peace-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2020 09:03:58 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/05/mireilles-channel-peace-out/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;For the vast majority of this blog&amp;rsquo;s audience (Hi mom and dad!), you probably don&amp;rsquo;t know much about the Youtube generation and what types of things go on here. I can&amp;rsquo;t say I know much more outside of what I observe from my children as they are interacting with these sites, but let me try to explain. In today&amp;rsquo;s day and age, being a &amp;ldquo;Youtuber&amp;rdquo; is an actual profession that people aspire towards. There are some &amp;ldquo;internet famous&amp;rdquo; people that actually make not only a living, but millions of dollars a year just posting videos on Youtube. Some notable ones are PewDiePie and Rhett and Link, among others. Basically they post various things to Youtube, ranging from just recording themselves doing something mundane like playing video games, to full on productions in an almost talk show format, sort of like a more interactive PeeWee&amp;rsquo;s Playhouse.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mireille, the runner and COVID haircuts</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/04/mireille-the-runner-and-covid-haircuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Apr 2020 09:14:58 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/04/mireille-the-runner-and-covid-haircuts/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;And it continues&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I believe we are about 8 weeks in to this new reality now. Funny how initially I had all these ideas of things I would do &amp;ldquo;every day&amp;rdquo; during this situation. I was going to blog every day, that seemed like a funny and interesting idea. I was also going to draw something every day, which was fun for awhile, and I&amp;rsquo;ve continued it on a far less frequent basis, but I&amp;rsquo;m definitely not doing anything on a daily basis other than just living.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COVID Reality - Day 2-9</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/03/covid-reality-day-2-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 10:50:59 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/03/covid-reality-day-2-9/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;COVID Reality Day 6 was the Grady&amp;rsquo;s breaking point. There was widespread dissent in the ranks, and those that are supposed to be even and get us through all this were SUPER crabby. Mireille had a big tantrum the likes that I haven&amp;rsquo;t seen in quite awhile, Quinton managed to squeek out some tears at some point, Ethan is cooped up and wants to see his friends and his girlfriend, and Jenny and I were basically not on speaking terms with one another most of the day. We were on yelling terms, just not speaking terms. Today seems to be better. The saving grace is that it&amp;rsquo;s very nice outside - spring weather makes everything seem a little better.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COVID Reality - Day 1</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/03/covid-reality-day-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 08:50:41 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/03/covid-reality-day-1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Today is the first day of what I&amp;rsquo;m calling &amp;ldquo;COVID Reality.&amp;rdquo; In Colorado, while we aren&amp;rsquo;t ordered to &amp;ldquo;shelter in place,&amp;rdquo; anything that would be worthwhile leaving the house for has been closed down, most notably all sporting events, theaters, churches, restaurants, breweries, and bars. Oh, and schools. These closures are setup right now for 4 weeks. We&amp;rsquo;ll see how long it actually ends up being (I doubt &lt;em&gt;shorter&lt;/em&gt; than 4 weeks). So we&amp;rsquo;re getting to know our family better, for better or worse. I&amp;rsquo;m working from home, the kids are doing school from home, Ethan is doing college from home (they closed the campus for the rest of the year), and Jenny has had to take on the new jobs of teacher and principal in addition to Janitor, Laundress, and overall house CEO.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big Update on Grady Kids</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/01/big-update-on-grady-kids/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2020 09:25:40 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/01/big-update-on-grady-kids/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s a broken record on this blog, but it&amp;rsquo;s again been a LONG time since I&amp;rsquo;ve done anything. There is definitely an ebb and flow to my state of mind that really dictates how much I observe of the world around me, and around the end of the year is a time of reflection for lots of people. So here it goes&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This post is going to read mostly as a Quinton post. It&amp;rsquo;s not that I don&amp;rsquo;t love my other kids, he&amp;rsquo;s just at a point where the things he does crack me up more than what I&amp;rsquo;m observing from my other kids right now. Ethan, Mireille, forgive me!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Dead Cat Saga</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/09/the-dead-cat-saga/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2019 14:51:03 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/09/the-dead-cat-saga/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A couple of weekends ago, Quinton and I, on a whim, went outside to play catch with a baseball. It&amp;rsquo;s sort of odd that we would do that. Most of Quin&amp;rsquo;s time at home involves playing XBox, and most of my time involves yelling at Quinton about playing XBox, but on this occassion we both decided to do something a little different.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Flash back to earlier that morning, upon waking up I saw that our doorbell camera had gone off a couple of times during the night. I studied the pictures (since I&amp;rsquo;m too cheap to pay for video storage) to find a cat hanging around on our front stoop. Kind of strange, but whatever. Later that morning I took something out to the garbage and, upon rounding the corner to the front of the house, I was presented with some kind of bad smell. I chalked it up to needing the garbage taken away and went about my day.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Firsts, and a Conversation with Mireille</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/08/firsts-and-a-conversation-with-mireille/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 09:50:50 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/08/firsts-and-a-conversation-with-mireille/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Quinton started middle school this week. For some reason, middle school scares the hell out of me on behalf of my children. To boot, he&amp;rsquo;s been actively and heavily lobbying to be moved to the public school from our relatively more comfortable private school middle school situation. Well, he made pretty good arguments, so we relented, so now he has started school at Laredo Public Middle School, right next to where Ethan has spent his last 4 years at Smoky Hill.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quin Said a Bad Word</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/05/quin-said-a-bad-word/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 13:18:08 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/05/quin-said-a-bad-word/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s graduation week. I have a longer, more sentimental post that I&amp;rsquo;m working through, but I had to jot this one down quickly before it was lost to history. Since it is graduation week, we have family that have started arriving to help Ethan celebrate and to help remind us how old we are.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Last night, my parents, Ethan and his girlfriend Rachel, and Jenny and I were sitting around the table just talking about different things. It was nice. Quinton was in his room playing XBox and Mireille was kind of bouncing between the TV in the living room and upstairs. At one point, though, she came in and talked with all of us to ensure that she could tattle on her brother.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teeth, Hoops, and Firsts</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/04/teeth-hoops-and-firsts/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 09:38:11 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/04/teeth-hoops-and-firsts/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Mireille finally lost that first tooth! It was a few weeks ago, now. She was walking around the kitchen, and I asked her, like I had been every day for quite a few weeks, how her teeth were doing. Her two front teeth on the bottom were coming in behind the baby teeth. On that fateful night, one of them was finally loose enough that I felt confident enough to give it a little tug and evict it from its spot that the other tooth so badly wanted. She was tough - no crying or anything. I think she was a little sad that she didn&amp;rsquo;t lose it at school since they give you a cool necklace for your fallen chomper so you can take it home - she really wanted one of those necklaces!!! The other one never really got loose enough for me to pull, but the dentist did the deed a couple of weeks later with the help of some laughing gas and a little numbing medicine. I, sadly, wasn&amp;rsquo;t there to see it, but Jenny said she was pretty out of it. A little video would have been fun!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Catching up to 2019</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/02/catching-up-to-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2019 17:00:42 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/02/catching-up-to-2019/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A new year&amp;hellip; It went and happened again, and again I find myself in the position of having a resolution of writing more. It seems a yearly concern, but here goes the latest attempt.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;2018 was very kind to the Grady&amp;rsquo;s. Ethan wrecked a couple of cars, but has now had his latest one for over 6 months without incident (knock on wood). Brandon got a new (to me) car in the form of a 2017 Chevy Malibu - yeah, I can&amp;rsquo;t seem to break that mold. Hey, they&amp;rsquo;re nice cars!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moab</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/11/moab/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2018 19:58:19 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/11/moab/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-trip&#34;&gt;The Trip&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Moab. Or as Mireille would pronounce it, Mo-Ab. Small city of 5000 some people in Southeast Utah, the land of Mormons, backwards liquor laws, and some spectacular natural landscapes. Since we&amp;rsquo;ve moved to the west we&amp;rsquo;ve always looked for a reason to get out here to take in these sights. Thanks to some early travel by Mom and Pop Grady, having come through Denver the weekend prior for Thanksgiving day festivities, we finally had our opportunity to check it out over the Thanksgiving day weekend, figuring it wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be quite as busy or quite as hot as it would in the peak months.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mireille the Investigator</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/11/mireille-the-investigator/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 19:58:19 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/11/mireille-the-investigator/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I couldn&amp;rsquo;t find my toothbrush this morning. That may not sound that strange, but I have one of those big Sonicare toothbrushes that would seem very difficult to lose. In fact, where my toothbrush was supposed to be, Jenny&amp;rsquo;s had taken its place, a similar Sonicare but different color.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I had no idea where it could be. Initially I blamed Jenny for hiding it on me. She came home angry last night for reasons unknown, and was argumentative. Since I had brushed my teeth before she had gotten home, I immediately blamed her for hiding my toothbrush out of spite. However, she explained that she did not hide it, and I eventually believed her sincerity.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mireille the Observer</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/11/mireille-the-observer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 10:10:26 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/11/mireille-the-observer/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Mireille is far and away the most observant of our children. Ethan&amp;rsquo;s not bad - far better than myself. Quinton, well, he and I are about in the same boat, and it&amp;rsquo;s not a good boat. Mireille will notice just about anything, even if it seems inconsequential. For example, Jenny occasionally colors her hair, but in a subtle way such that color blind me will not notice. Mireille does, though. The other day, Jenny swapped out the pulls on our dressers in our room, and the first thing Mireille said when she walked in the room was &amp;ldquo;when did you get new ones of these?&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Catching Up</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/09/miscellaneous-catching-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Sep 2018 08:52:45 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/09/miscellaneous-catching-up/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It’s been awhile on a couple of these, so I figured I should jot them down before time erodes them from my memory.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This first story has been getting good traction in my friend and colleague circles. Before I can tell the story, I need to tee it up a little bit. Quinton is obviously a black male being raised among “the whites.” From time to time that causes some conflict in him. He really likes the idea of exploring black culture, but acknowledges that he doesn’t know much about it. One thing he likes to do to try to dip his toe into it is to listen to rap music. While there is a very deep collection of amazing rap songs, many, many of them delve into topics or language that is just a little rough to continually barrage the ears of our five year old, and ten year old as well.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christmas with the Tibbetts</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/02/christmas-with-the-tibbetts/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2018 10:50:09 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/02/christmas-with-the-tibbetts/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We live in Colorado. Our families, by and large, still dwell in places throughout the Midwest. Year after year this generates some degree of conflict, particularly when it comes time for celebrating the holidays. For this holiday season, we celebrated Grady Christmas on the ever traditional weekend of the first weekend of November. For the Tibbett holiday celebration, then, we coordinated an early January celebration. Actually, it was planned to coincide with my 45th birthday, because who wouldn&amp;rsquo;t want to travel to the frigid midwest to stay in remote, rural Wisconsin with his in-laws on their 45th birthday!!!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thanksgiving 2017</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/12/thanksgiving-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2017 12:16:24 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/12/thanksgiving-2017/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Thanksgiving is literally my favorite holiday. I just love getting together with family and friends, cooking a delicious meal, eating said meal, just hanging out and napping with people. I think even more than Christmas, it is the most relaxing holiday out there!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This year, having already done the &amp;ldquo;Grady Christmas&amp;rdquo; several weeks earlier, our plan was to stay put for Thanksgiving. Luckily there are others in the greater Denver metropolitan area that are also too far away to spend the day with family, so they became our extended family for Thanksgiving. On the menu was the traditional Thanksgiving faire, turkey, rolls, potatoes and gravy, stuffing, scalloped corn, pie (lots of pie), macaronni and cheese, gouda roll-ups, bean dip - you know, the traditional stuff! One of the reasons I like hosting so much is because I get to keep the leftovers, so I planned ahead. For the nine people that were at our meal we cooked 28 pounds of turkey!!!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A perfect parent&#39;s weekend...</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/09/a-perfect-parents-weekend.../</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2017 09:38:40 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/09/a-perfect-parents-weekend.../</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This was a couple of weeks ago now, so it&amp;rsquo;s not as fresh in my mind as it was when it happened, but the event was important enough that I think it warrants documentation. You see, this was Mireille&amp;rsquo;s fifth birthday, her second in the United States.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For the weeks leading up to September 9, Mireille has been asking on a regular basis about her birthday party. She really wanted to have a party, with a bounce castle, and a cake, and presents! Hopefully she wasn&amp;rsquo;t disappointed. The only thing we didn&amp;rsquo;t really have was a cake, but we had a whole bunch of cupcakes! She didn&amp;rsquo;t seem too impressed, though, because it wasn&amp;rsquo;t a cake!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mireille Funnies</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/09/mireille-funnies/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 11:52:46 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/09/mireille-funnies/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Jenny was talking to Mireille on Sunday about things that girls talk about. I wasn&amp;rsquo;t privvy to the details of the entire conversation, because that wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be appropriate - I&amp;rsquo;m a boy. One little nugget Jenny shared with me was when Mireille admitted to her, &amp;ldquo;I wish I was a unicorn. But I&amp;rsquo;m just Mireille&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Then, yesterday, our little Unicorn proved she listens and absorbs way more than she ever lets on. Since moving to Colorado we&amp;rsquo;ve had some difficulty adapting to the local colloqualisms. It&amp;rsquo;s not too different here, but the differences that do exist between here and Milwaukee are hard, particularly for adults. The one that seems most stubborn for Jenny and I is calling the last meal of the day dinner (CO) instead of supper (WI). Any time Jenny will say it in front of Maylee, she will make a big deal of correcting her. Just yesterday, Jenny and I were sitting on our newly completed deck with Mireille and discussing what we should do for supper. Mireille looked seriously at Jenny and said quietly, &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s dinner mom, not supper.&amp;rdquo; Maylee is so proud, and now I am double thinking anything I say in front of her.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summer is here!</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/06/summer-is-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 14:52:46 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/06/summer-is-here/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Summer is finally upon us. Last week was a full week without school, except for Mireille, but that&amp;rsquo;s daycare - even though she calls it school. The temperatures as of last Thursday definitely represented a shift into the ungodly hot area, though in Denver, if you can find shade, you are in good shape since the humidity is very comfortable. As a family we are definitely settling in more and more as the years have gone by.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mireille&#39;s English Progression</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/05/mireilles-english-progression/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2017 15:18:41 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/05/mireilles-english-progression/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s been over a year, and Mireille continues to grow and develop. Outside of some difficulties in identifying colors (something I can&amp;rsquo;t really fault her here) and a current disinterest in letters or numbers, she&amp;rsquo;s developing quite on par with what I would expect. She does continue to have some interesting phrases, usages, and interactions from time to time that merit documentation.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Recently she has started using a phrase whenever people do something that she really doesn&amp;rsquo;t understand. Not that she doesn&amp;rsquo;t understand what they are saying or doing, but doesn&amp;rsquo;t understand why a person would do that in the first place! As you can imagine, this is something that happens a lot with her American family, particularly her dense father and brothers. The phrase she attributes to this is, &amp;ldquo;What your problem is?&amp;rdquo; The look on her face is impossible to properly document, but it&amp;rsquo;s pretty hilarious any time she does it - funny enough that it hasn&amp;rsquo;t started bothering me quite yet.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Potpourri</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/01/potpourri/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2017 17:02:48 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/01/potpourri/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As is typical now a days, I find myself delinquent in my posting. I blame my new job. Nothing more. Oh, and having three kids is hard. Not sure I&amp;rsquo;ve mentioned that. Still, they keep us on our toes, and I occasionally remember to write some of the remarkable things down that they do. The following is a small collection of the things I&amp;rsquo;ve remembered.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;mireille&#34;&gt;Mireille&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;on-language&#34;&gt;&amp;hellip;on language&amp;hellip;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Mireille&amp;rsquo;s pronoun usage continues to improve, though her favorite pronoun continues to be &amp;ldquo;him.&amp;rdquo; The possessive form of her version of the &amp;ldquo;super pronoun&amp;rdquo; is &lt;strong&gt;him&amp;rsquo;s&lt;/strong&gt;. I don&amp;rsquo;t know where she heard the song, but the other day she started singing an adorable rendition of Sir Mix-A-Lot&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Baby Got Back,&amp;rdquo; or at least the beginning of it. Her&amp;rsquo;s, however, went like this.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2016 - The Year in Review - First Trimester</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/12/2016-the-year-in-review-first-trimester/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2016 18:55:09 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/12/2016-the-year-in-review-first-trimester/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I can remember one year when we did the traditional &amp;ldquo;Holiday Letter.&amp;rdquo; It was the year that we were in the process of trying to adopt Quinton, so we were &amp;ldquo;marketing ourselves&amp;rdquo; to our family and friends that year. Looking back, it was a fun letter to do, even if it was not necessary from the salesman side of house. I thought it would be fun to condense 2016 into a bit of a letter to our family (thank you both of my readers) and so that future versions of ourselves might enjoy reading it as well. So, here it goes!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The First Snow of the Year</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/11/the-first-snow-of-the-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2016 09:31:29 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/11/the-first-snow-of-the-year/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Last week it snowed in Denver for the first time this season. It&amp;rsquo;s a mixed bag out here for snow. People don&amp;rsquo;t really care for it in the city, like most places, but love when it happens in the mountains, where it is supposed to be. My kids certainly love it, at least the first snow.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Mireille has been saying &amp;ldquo;snow&amp;rsquo;s coming?&amp;rdquo; since about August when Jenny showed her some snow boots she could wear. When it finally snowed last week, I picked her up from school and the first thing she said was &amp;ldquo;it&amp;rsquo;s snowing!&amp;rdquo; As soon as we got home, she wormed her way into her snow pants, coat, boots, hat, and gloves and demanded that I come outside with her so she could play in the snow.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>October 2016 - Big Update!</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/10/october-2016-big-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2016 19:39:06 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/10/october-2016-big-update/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s October! October has been a busy month, but what month hasn&amp;rsquo;t been, really. So it&amp;rsquo;s been awhile since there&amp;rsquo;s been an update of much substance. So, while my family answers the door to greet and treat Halloween visitors in full costume, I thought I would take a few minutes (or 60) and update the world on the goings on in the Grady Household.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;adoption---complete&#34;&gt;Adoption - Complete&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;rsquo;t have to restate how much work and waiting it&amp;rsquo;s been to complete this, our second adoption. It&amp;rsquo;s been long. This past Friday, though, we hit a big milestone. Mireille had her day in court, and she is now officially adopted in the United States, meaning she if officially a Grady! I wish that meant we were all done! But alas, this is yet another milestone. It marks our ability to complete more paperwork, and pay out more money for interesting new bureaucratic processes. But, it is a reason to celebrate, at least for the fact that this part of the process has come to a close.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mireille the Magician</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/10/mireille-the-magician/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2016 20:34:27 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/10/mireille-the-magician/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Quick one today. I need to document this, because it cracks me up. Lately Mireille has been doing magic tricks. Yes, you read that correctly - my four year old knows how to do magic tricks. Well, she knows a single trick, but she&amp;rsquo;s OK at it, and is working at it and trying to perfect it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;What she does is she takes an item and puts it in her hand. Then she asks you to pick which hand it is in. When you do, she shows you, and typically it is in that hand. Then she will try to distract you while she puts the object in her pocket. Then the routine starts over - pick a hand&amp;hellip; This time she&amp;rsquo;ll open both, and lo and behold, it&amp;rsquo;s gone. She&amp;rsquo;ll even proclaim, &amp;ldquo;It gone!&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quick Updates</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/10/quick-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2016 10:18:11 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/10/quick-updates/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;After five days of adult vacation in New Orleans, Jenny and I were happy to be back with our kids, and probably a bit surprised that five days wasn&amp;rsquo;t quite enough to really decompress! Things went back to normal very quickly.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Mirielle gas been constantly about three things - now, trick or treating, and the party that she was going to yesterday. The snow things is pretty funny. I seem to remember her not liking it very much when it showed up last spring, but just about every day she will ask us, very seriously, &amp;ldquo;snow coming?&amp;rdquo; I think she mainly wants to wear her snow boots that she found in her closet. Having a girl is weird!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mireille&#39;s Birthday!</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/09/mireilles-birthday/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2016 08:39:35 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/09/mireilles-birthday/</guid>
      <description>&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/e-j3FvpALopCYntwuaiyc7wa4_Qm-mfhdj7qBx7BAAlLlglMH3tfmX92zOXM_ulob2HionFUDqtRyw=w1014-h1350-no&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h4&gt;Mireille on her Fourth Birthday&lt;/h4&gt; &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our little girl turned four!!! This was a pretty special birthday for us. It&amp;rsquo;s the first one we got to celebrate with her! We have sent her gifts for each birthday in the Congo, but I&amp;rsquo;m pretty sure she hated all of those gifts. It was a weird thing - it&amp;rsquo;s very expensive to send stuff to the Congo, so we would just send one of our agency&amp;rsquo;s lawyers money and ask them to purchase something local for her. Then they would give it to her and send us pictures. One year they got her this really creepy looking doll and she looked like she would rather play with mud than with that doll!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More English</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/08/more-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2016 09:19:33 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/08/more-english/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I was amused by these so I had to post them. Mireille is learning English really quickly. Not all is worthy of recording as most is mundane, but there are a few&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;She loves to eat! And she loves to try new food - but she doesn&amp;rsquo;t always like the food that she&amp;rsquo;s trying. When she happens to try something that she doesn&amp;rsquo;t like she says &amp;ldquo;I like this uh-uh.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More English with Mireille</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/07/more-english-with-mireille/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2016 21:27:01 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/07/more-english-with-mireille/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s been nearly 5 months now, and Mireille has really amped up her mastery of the English language. We recently went on vacation with the whole family to Wisconsin, so I had the opportunity to spend a lot of focused time with her. As the week went on, I started to see how she is systematically adding new words to her vocabulary all the time. First, she will point at something and ask you what it is (she says &amp;ldquo;Ques at?&amp;rdquo; which means &amp;ldquo;what&amp;rsquo;s that?&amp;rdquo;). Then you will tell her the name for that thing. Then she will repeat the name, but with a question inflection at the end of the name, forcing you to then repeat yourself. Finally, she will repeat the word, this time with statement inflection. The word isn&amp;rsquo;t always locked in at this point, but you can see it settling in for remembering.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Life of a Single Father</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/06/life-of-a-single-father/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2016 21:43:24 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/06/life-of-a-single-father/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s 9:44 PM on Thursday evening. I&amp;rsquo;ve finally settled down to my computer and&#xA;a bomber of my local&amp;rsquo;s double IPA. It&amp;rsquo;s the first time today that I&amp;rsquo;ve been&#xA;able to sit without somebody demanding something or me having to be preparing&#xA;something for somebody. You see, Jenny has been traveling for work since Monday&#xA;morning, leaving me, a single father of three.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve been a single father in the past. There&amp;rsquo;s something much more complicated&#xA;about being a single father now-a-days, however. Not only is it three kids,&#xA;which even though we&amp;rsquo;ve added only one child, the apparent number of children&#xA;seems to have risen exponentially. No, it&amp;rsquo;s not &lt;em&gt;just&lt;/em&gt; the third child, but the&#xA;fact that the third child is a three year old black girl! Let me explain.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ACHC Camp and English</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/06/achc-camp-and-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2016 07:58:48 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/06/achc-camp-and-english/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Last weekend we had to opportunity to go to the African-Caribbean&#xA;Heritage Camp. It is one of a set of camps put on by an organization in town&#xA;here that focuses on transracially formed families, specifically formed through&#xA;adoption. Yeah, they have organizations for everything! We had been to the camp&#xA;once before, two years ago, and enjoyed it so much that we decided to move to&#xA;Denver!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Over the course of the two and a half days of camp we were all immersed with&#xA;people in a very similar situation to our family. There were many speakers&#xA;and round tables which were both thought provoking and frustrating (mainly&#xA;the round tables), but in the end it was a great experience for our family to&#xA;be around other families that look just like ours. That just doesn&amp;rsquo;t happen&#xA;very often!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning English</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/05/learning-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2016 07:57:13 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/05/learning-english/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Mireille has been in the US for around 2 months now and by all accounts is doing&#xA;pretty well. One thing that we constantly worry about is whether she is picking&#xA;up English quickly enough. Of course we are on all these Facebook groups and&#xA;we constantly hear about how much English people&amp;rsquo;s kids are picking up and&#xA;Mireille has been a bit slow on that front. I tend to think many of those&#xA;people are embellishing their stories quite a bit, but whatever - she is a&#xA;strong willed girl and she&amp;rsquo;s going to speak Lingala, dammit!!!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mireille Quickies</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/04/mireille-quickies/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2016 08:30:03 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/04/mireille-quickies/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I have a couple of &amp;ldquo;novels&amp;rdquo; in the works. Sometimes I let those clog up the&#xA;works when I should be doing smaller, more frequent updates. So this is one&#xA;of those smaller, more frequent updates. I&amp;rsquo;m finding my available time much&#xA;harder to come by with the addition of the third child. I&amp;rsquo;m sure that will&#xA;normalize out at some point, right? Those with three or more kids, back me up&#xA;here!!!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two Days on the Hill</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/02/two-days-on-the-hill/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2016 10:15:09 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/02/two-days-on-the-hill/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;preamble&#34;&gt;Preamble&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I briefly considered titling this &amp;ldquo;Mr. Grady Goes to Washington,&amp;rdquo; but I didn&amp;rsquo;t&#xA;like it for a couple of reasons. First, I don&amp;rsquo;t really think of myself as&#xA;Mr. Grady. And more importantly, I have never really seen the movie, and I hate&#xA;giving false information.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is a story about a number of things&amp;hellip; Adoption, politics, travel, weather&amp;hellip;&#xA;Hold on to your seats, and grab some NoDoze. This might get boring!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>She&#39;s Coming Home!!!</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/02/shes-coming-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2016 07:59:33 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/02/shes-coming-home/</guid>
      <description>&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/8Cmk5RKPfdXpaITEv7XJyNfYnunG3NmosrbdGaL6hmNT8xmcfekDIwFpiTUXebs8netwE55Ia_lnrA=w960-h1280-no&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h4&gt;Riding to my Red Eye&lt;/h4&gt; &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/5aF5JNcVIg8S4rvaO79bFdIqBLGA_mYCLmNZe3qE_HhfIN0Yle6bJ_IQ_BaNU3Rt7DYd1Avu8uxjkA=w1830-h1372-no&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h4&gt;Dulles Airport&lt;/h4&gt; &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/LO3UXr1yK65hVk0Q7KT4ZkmBoFLyqGwVgfsN9TaPSxpoquee6pXACZhxRopLJo9ETWlIqcALK5XvMg=w1030-h1372-no&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h4&gt;Empty International Arrival Terminal&lt;/h4&gt; &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/I-TpkEc4M1Hcf9oRJUGd9E0AJ86Ok2jyM_jGiy-cn2oxIBcBfTVJ4pu6Du2sQExLK-0zVskY2sYxcw=w1830-h1372-no&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h4&gt;UA 951 from Brussels&lt;/h4&gt; &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/Zov87qb-27qil2rQQ-Bs8pcOE2rnyCz_lgO3s7MEa4KK8CtLCysnczJA5d8au9puQgczsIUvrt5ukA=w1030-h1372-no&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h4&gt;At at DGM, Ironic Lunch&lt;/h4&gt; &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/pULwNKpVhdF6v3e4MVWfMDR4LpmIS_vG712y3il8U98dPUp_pAZhM7mWODSD9cqxIUYDePngrWPGRQ=w750-h1334-no&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h4&gt;The Wait is Excruciating&lt;/h4&gt; &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/jvof0kJy-0WdJfXpVacQcv3Wad5_uGqSBjSqg-P0yZCiB949FdD47d-uw5yb7xWXwHjWSnhtKxitgw=w750-h1334-no&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h4&gt;The Plane has Landed!&lt;/h4&gt; &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/Oq_wZEZM9mUEzmD49xpEGgHsBAAZbUwMWqjnfEqxzXOBY8832uOsnT-gpPz9PcJgsT2IwbWkgQoJxw=w1030-h1372-no&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h4&gt;Busiest Time of Day&lt;/h4&gt; &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/zKDZBQ6_DyPykIbkGVJNqNaS9_GCQCqW_UA72WdY71xhPlUF4jlhLgfdYpzHR4pOgqu2ym6UQESxhg=w1030-h1372-no&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h4&gt;She&amp;#39;s Here!&lt;/h4&gt; &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/zQintpxRx8zj5NpvRDhAh0YUnfo1DR2586B3_hBFty7d10K8zCDrpsAANJ0jTL5sIX11Ou1qqfSaPw=w1030-h1372-no&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h4&gt;Confused?&lt;/h4&gt; &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/oDLo_MrcVdoQTTq2oN0mDOEKtjPmDcQcCwqx9DDMlM4sQboQKCkJlX6LY4rvUkq9Yk5vy88u5tYu-A=w960-h1280-no&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h4&gt;Proof - in the U.S.&lt;/h4&gt; &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/pmrnTNojliemaBuiEpFBycuntkbPIQ5QpDOVArbRS9WjIcLid1Fk7zHvlxnSPyWNxBLOElJsIYTf-Q=w1030-h1372-no&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h4&gt;Playing Dress-up&lt;/h4&gt; &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/v5plBg_Zj6namKB2EtbrBso03tHlqrF2v6nAbiaWebBi6LaVS0uV5AQYLh-CL7sDJ84URgqzzkuwKA=w1030-h1372-no&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h4&gt;And... Out.&lt;/h4&gt; &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/J2QYL2Va9P-TU_HqxF1a1Txbk0Pjh6UwJ2FUkjLrvaOC0mmvQAgToc87lvyxL4iqhEcWsP4ecm5I9w=w1830-h1372-no&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h4&gt;Playing with Mama&lt;/h4&gt; &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/mQXECZJiXoSzMQqp1qJGokFoswcbSSVCLg-Y_9qXsEmkJttXCW0xCXigQyAbSL7PcPMwnyA9RsJVjg=w1030-h1372-no&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h4&gt;Women, they be shoppin!&lt;/h4&gt; &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/hfMDCIc8_bLR7hh_qaZSLeMFkR0JVXYi6E3DMzPOGuA39cuAcWxcMAUaTMu5yN5Lsvkbhq0qDzfaKw=w1830-h1372-no&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h4&gt;Playing with Yaya&lt;/h4&gt; &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/kFLi3_pZq2O7j6fjv4eDbBYosc00XZ0WR5l318dTgPVfZhf23JO2YSrOfsK2WTheJj86YU4-gqr6wA=w1030-h1372-no&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h4&gt;Starting the Hair Restoration Project&lt;/h4&gt; &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Left on the red-eye on Saturday night.&#xA;Nothing open in the airport.&#xA;Arrived at Dulles at 4:00 AM.&#xA;Nothing open in the airport.&#xA;$25 cab ride to the hotel 7 miles away.&#xA;Couldn&amp;rsquo;t check me in.&#xA;I annoyed them into letting me check in early.&#xA;Napped for 2 hours.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRC Update</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/01/drc-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2016 08:04:12 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/01/drc-update/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;So&amp;hellip; There are a couple of updates, but we&amp;rsquo;re still stuck.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The US sent a delegation of congressmen to the DRC to talk specifically about&#xA;this issue. As has become typical, the DRC responded with things that we want&#xA;to hear. I won&amp;rsquo;t go into details, but I wanted to document, for posterity,&#xA;the letter I wrote to my congressmen in Colorado. I&amp;rsquo;ve been interacting with&#xA;their offices for the past couple of months and have a fairly good rapport&#xA;going with my contacts.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skype with Mireille</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/10/skype-with-mireille/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2015 09:53:21 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/10/skype-with-mireille/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We got to Skype with Mireille this morning. It&amp;rsquo;s always bittersweet talking&#xA;with her. On the one hand, you want to make sure you keep in touch so she at&#xA;least has some sort of connection, but on another hand it just sort of hurts&#xA;to talk with her. When we talk with her, we are reminded of the situation that&#xA;we&amp;rsquo;re in, whereas other times we can sort of ignore it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Great Congolese Caper - Day 8 - On the way home</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-great-congolese-caper---day-8---on-the-way-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2015 14:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-great-congolese-caper---day-8---on-the-way-home/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;kinshasa---day-7&#34;&gt;Kinshasa - Day 7&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My last day. I feel bad, but I was looking forward to this in some ways. Over the last 5 days, Mireille has turned into a typical 2 year old, and taking care of 2 year olds is HARD! Particularly by yourself. Luckily, when you have nothing else to do, it makes it much easier. It&amp;rsquo;s much easier to completely invest in what the child is saying and doing, which I did - once I got done showering, washing the dishes, and packing (I&amp;rsquo;m such an adult).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Great Congolese Caper - Day 7 - Kinshasa</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-great-congolese-caper---day-7---kinshasa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2015 11:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-great-congolese-caper---day-7---kinshasa/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;kinshasa---day-6&#34;&gt;Kinshasa - Day 6&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Getting down to it! Today I&amp;rsquo;m nervous again, but that hasn&amp;rsquo;t changed much from day 1 here, or day -2 for that matter.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Last night started out rough. Mireille was restless. She didn&amp;rsquo;t fall out of bed, but was up like 3 times up until about 1:00 AM. She didn&amp;rsquo;t cry or anything, but she got out of bed and asked me to hold her. After rocking her to sleep the other two times, I convinced her to just sleep in my bed with me the last time. That ended up working very well. She settled down and was completely out in short order. Her only requirement seemed to be that she had one foot touching me somewhere. That forced me to settle down and not be so uptight and nervous as well, so we both got a good night&amp;rsquo;s sleep.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Great Congolese Caper - Day 6 - Kinshasa</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-great-congolese-caper---day-6---kinshasa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2015 11:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-great-congolese-caper---day-6---kinshasa/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;kinshasa---day-5&#34;&gt;Kinshasa - Day 5&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s a hotel day - all day at the hotel. It&amp;rsquo;s a good and a bad thing. Getting out would be nice simply to stave off the boredom, but it also allows for a very concentrated, focused time for just hanging out with your child - something I&amp;rsquo;m not sure I ever did so much with the boys, or at the very least don&amp;rsquo;t do it anymore…&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Great Congolese Caper - Day 5 - Kinshasa and Surrounding Areas</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-great-congolese-caper---day-5---kinshasa-and-surrounding-areas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2015 09:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-great-congolese-caper---day-5---kinshasa-and-surrounding-areas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;kinshasa---day-4&#34;&gt;Kinshasa - Day 4&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Bad habits I&amp;rsquo;m already allowing my daughter to develop, because, hey, she&amp;rsquo;s under a lot of stress just hanging out with me. I hope I&amp;rsquo;m not setting myself up for bad things later:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Drinking soda - this is a big no-no for the sub-40ers in our household, but Mireille has already had soda every day I&amp;rsquo;ve been with her. She likes it.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Not brushing her teeth - it&amp;rsquo;s difficult enough to get her to open her mouth for me, much less brush. She has finally started using the toothbrush herself, but she does a terrible job at brushing…&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Holding her until she sleeps - I&amp;rsquo;m pretty sure I broke my boys of this habit prior to them being 30 months old. I actually think it could be developmental progress in that she&amp;rsquo;s regressing to a more infant state. My guess is that she didn&amp;rsquo;t get a lot of personal attention as an infant, and perhaps craves it now. I&amp;rsquo;m happy to provide it, though it is frustrating at times to try to set her down and sneak away before she wakes up. Raising a two year old is hard!&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Today started out fairly badly again in that I just cannot seem to get to sleep at a reasonable time! Despite only getting 2 hours the night before plus a 2 hour nap, I still could not fall asleep until after 4:00 AM local time (9:00 Central, coincidentally). I imagine by the time I leave I will have adjusted better to the time change - just in time to screw it up again. At least there I will have full access to my modern diversions and drugs.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Great Congolese Caper - Day 3 - Kinshasa</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-great-congolese-caper---day-3---kinshasa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2015 08:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-great-congolese-caper---day-3---kinshasa/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;kinshasa---day-2&#34;&gt;Kinshasa - Day 2&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;After a rough night night, I managed to get up and get myself together by 9:00, when Papa John was schedule to show up so we could go grocery shopping. By the time he showed up, though, it was 10:30. Traffic… Common problem in Kinshasa! By then, we took off to ShopRite, a local, modern supermarket, where I purchased my groceries for the week. It was a little nerve wracking buying groceries for the week, let me tell you. Normally Jenny takes care of that kind of thing! I was very surprised at the selection, though. I managed to buy some fruit (bananas and grapes), eggs, butter, milk (which they store warm - weird), bread, sardines (Papa John insisted), cookies, and rice. Apparently a lot of the Congolese diet consists of rice dishes. Either that or “Foo-foo,” something I just learned of today from my new friend Andrew!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Great Congolese Caper - Day 4 - Kinshasa</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-great-congolese-caper---day-4---kinshasa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2015 08:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-great-congolese-caper---day-4---kinshasa/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;kinshasa---day-3&#34;&gt;Kinshasa - Day 3&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Today, I met my daughter! Yes, I met her yesterday, but that version of Mireille was guarded, afraid, and sullen. She&amp;rsquo;s asleep now - hopefully for the night. Today we made very good progress, and I am beyond excited!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The morning started out not so well. I slept terribly last night, by that I mean I didn&amp;rsquo;t really sleep at all. I fell asleep around 10:00, but Mireille fell out of bed at 10:45, and I didn&amp;rsquo;t sleep after that. I was worried about her, too many things going through my head… Every time she moved a little bit, I was up and on edge. So when 5:30 rolled around, I wasn&amp;rsquo;t very excited to hear her up, though I wasn&amp;rsquo;t surprised since she had been asleep since 6:00 the evening before!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Great Congolese Caper - Day 2 - Kinshasa</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-great-congolese-caper---day-2---kinshasa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2015 08:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-great-congolese-caper---day-2---kinshasa/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;kinshasa---day-1---airport-to-the-hotel&#34;&gt;Kinshasa - Day 1 - Airport to the Hotel&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I was happy when I landed in Paris that I finally got a text message back from my guide, Papa John. That made me feel much more comfortable about landing in Kinshasa, seeing as how I’ve read many bad stories about the experience.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It is 6:30 local time on Sunday evening as I land, and it is completely dark already. Since I was in the middle of the plane, I didn’t get a good look at the landing, but what I could see, there didn’t seem to be too many lights.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Great Congolese Caper - Day 2 - Paris, France</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-great-congolese-caper---day-2---paris-france/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2015 08:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-great-congolese-caper---day-2---paris-france/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;paris---charles-de-gaul-airport&#34;&gt;Paris - Charles De Gaul Airport&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I landed around 8:00 local time in Charles De Gaul Airport outside of Paris, France. For my first trip to France, it was a little underwhelming. I suppose it’s true what they say that you don’t really visit a country when you visit the airport…&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;After disembarking my flight, I followed the hallways and signage to where my next flight was taking off, Terminal 2E the K gates (I think). I bought the AT&amp;amp;T Passport plan before taking off, which allows for free text messaging and reduced call rates via cell phone, so I attempted to text Jenny to let her know that I landed. While my texts successfully went through eventually, Jenny was unable to text me back due to some complications with switching between iMessage and SMS texting. This is something I need to take up with Apple at some point, because it took us four days to finally figure it out. For those that might suffer the same issue, you have to turn off iMessage on your sending phone, then remove any text conversations that are on the phone, then send a new text message to the phone number and not the e-mail address… What a pain!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Great Congolese Caper - Day 1 - In the Air</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-great-congolese-caper---day-1---in-the-air/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2015 08:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-great-congolese-caper---day-1---in-the-air/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;seat-9a-to-msp&#34;&gt;Seat 9a to MSP&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Leg one is done. Yes, the easiest leg, but significant nonetheless. My seat wasn&amp;rsquo;t bad - I was on the window next to an older woman who didn&amp;rsquo;t take up too much room, so that was good.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Things I learned from this step of the journey:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;My earbuds suck. So much so that I have already replaced them with some cheap on ear headphones so I don&amp;rsquo;t have to monkey with them the whole time on the next two flights.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m too obsessed with food. Not knowing what the status of food on the upcoming flight is, I gorged myself at Charly&amp;rsquo;s Philly-style subs. Delicious, but didn&amp;rsquo;t need all that food! I think I&amp;rsquo;m afraid of starving in the next week and feel like I can stave it off by eating way too much before I go!&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now I&amp;rsquo;m sitting at gate G9 waiting for my next leg to board. Interesting room of people. Some people are clearly foreign, but it&amp;rsquo;s not super easy to determine. Going to be an interesting flight, but probably not quite as interesting as the next one!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Great Congolese Caper - Day 2 - In the Air</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-great-congolese-caper---day-2---in-the-air/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2015 08:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-great-congolese-caper---day-2---in-the-air/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;seat-33g-to-kinshasa&#34;&gt;Seat 33G to Kinshasa&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m Tired!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Despite there only being like 50 people in the gate area, this flight is completely full! I&amp;rsquo;m on the aisle in the middle section among the cattle again. The seat&amp;rsquo;s not bad, though there&amp;rsquo;s little leg room due to a heater or some box that is in my leg area. This is a cutting edge plane&amp;hellip; from the 90s. It has screens in each of the seatbacks that are touch sensitive (sort of) and retain the old 4:3 aspect ration. Didn&amp;rsquo;t matter - I slept for a couple of hours, woke up and watched Birdman (or most of it), then slept some more before watching the flight information channel as we descended to Kinshasa, where it was already dark by 6:30 when we landed… 1 Day down and I&amp;rsquo;ve seen very little sunlight!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Great Congolese Caper - Day 1 - Milwaukee</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-great-congolese-caper---day-1---milwaukee/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2015 08:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-great-congolese-caper---day-1---milwaukee/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;saturday-7-feb-2015-milwaukee-wi-usa&#34;&gt;Saturday, 7-Feb-2015, Milwaukee, WI, USA&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So it begins… The trip I&amp;rsquo;ve been both dreading and anticipating has finally started. As I sit here in General Mitchell International Airport, I am anxious and hopeful at what the next week will bring.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;http://4.bp.blogspot.com/-7dVvjWXROCU/VOlgHGKTOVI/AAAAAAAAkSg/gLq1pmincSM/s1600/IMG_1268.JPG&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;http://4.bp.blogspot.com/-Iv6YB9exWao/VOlgIKCrAmI/AAAAAAAAkSo/c3Tiry69eWg/s1600/IMG_7464.JPG&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re adopting a child from the Democratic Republic of Congo. Mireille is her name, and she is 2 and a half years old. She&amp;rsquo;s been our daughter by Congolese law for over 6 months, but politics and what appears to be corruption have prevented us from bringing her home to live with us in the U.S. One day, I&amp;rsquo;m sure that will happen, though that day is not today, nor is it this week. &lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mireille</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/mireille/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2014 15:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/mireille/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m outing us to the world. Well, Jenny outed us on Facebook about a month ago, but this post makes it official - we are in the process of adopting a little girl from the Democratic Republic of Congo. In fact, we&amp;rsquo;ve been matched with our daughter for 18 months, and are in fact her legal parents by that country&amp;rsquo;s laws. In a very strange combination of power plays and international politics, however, we are unable to bring her home to the United States. What&amp;rsquo;s worse, we still have no idea when it might be that we will be able to bring her home. That aside, she is already starting to provide for some fun stories, which I always like to share.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
