<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on The Hydrant</title>
    <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on The Hydrant</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 13:00:03 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Naughty</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2023/07/naughty/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 13:00:03 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2023/07/naughty/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Apparently all my kids are naughty! In the online world, dealing with bullies and hate speech is constantly a topic. It&amp;rsquo;s very easy in an anonymized world to pop off to people in ways that you might not if you were in the same room. Quinton has shown us that for years, though he was pretty inventive about it. At one point, I think he had 5 or 6 different free email addresses that he would use to sign back up for services that he got banned from because he was bullying or harassing people. I never in my life thought that my demure, perfect little daughter would be up to the same shenanigans&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hey Mo!</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2023/06/hey-mo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 08:03:43 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2023/06/hey-mo/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Jenny&amp;rsquo;s been looking at robot vacuum cleaners for awhile. Strangely, I&amp;rsquo;ve been against them. I&amp;rsquo;m not sure what it was about them, but I didn&amp;rsquo;t think they would be able to handle our floors. Our first floor has a mixture of wood and high pile carpet along with rugs and the like - I just figured a robot vacuum would struggle.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Then my brother bought one. Rocky, his robot&amp;rsquo;s name, is a fixture in his house now, and from what I can tell, is doing a serviceable job on his new hard floors! So I started to soften and do some research to see what the big deal was.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best Mother So Far</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2023/06/best-mother-so-far/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 14:43:30 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2023/06/best-mother-so-far/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;One of the best parts of being a parent, in my estimation, is watching my kids&amp;rsquo; sense of humor develop. Early on, it&amp;rsquo;s at once fun and annoying to watch them try new things out and see what type of reaction they get. The annoying part comes with things like the constant use of the word &amp;ldquo;diarhea&amp;rdquo; that Mireille currently thinks is funny. The fun part, though, is seeing Ethan tell his grandmother, who had recently burst a blood vessel in her eye, that she could potentially remediate it with a quick trip to the Halloween Store.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>So Long GPs</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2023/05/so-long-gps/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 09:03:26 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2023/05/so-long-gps/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Today we parted ways with our furry friends Zazu and Odin (or as Mireille would spell it, Oddainn - I don&amp;rsquo;t know why). They were fun little pets that kept me company while I worked with their squeals, foot falls, and very much so their smell&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Zazu joined us I think 5 years ago already. Quinton really wanted a pet - he wanted a dog. We convinced him that a guinea pig would be better. He was young enough at the time that he believed us! And for awhile, they were buddies.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hair</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2023/05/hair/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 09:38:11 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2023/05/hair/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hair is really important to my daughter. This is something I learned early on in her life with us. When she came to us from Congo, she had extensions in her hair and, though she coudln&amp;rsquo;t say anything in English, she conveyed very clearly that she liked them. She wasn&amp;rsquo;t very happy when we took them out a few days later (well, she wasn&amp;rsquo;t very happy about anything, really).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Over the years, she has been very vocal about wanting long hair and the types of things she would do with it. Jenny has done wonders caring for Mireille&amp;rsquo;s hair, but there&amp;rsquo;s just not much you can do with hair as curly as hers to make it long like she wanted it!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Catching up</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2023/04/catching-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 20:12:26 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2023/04/catching-up/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s been a minute&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Today, Bryce introduced me to a friend of his that is planning an RV trip. Rather than just answering a bunch of questions, I pointed him to this blog, which caused me to go back and re-read it, which reminded me how much fun it was to have these things written down. So here we are.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Well, what&amp;rsquo;s happened&amp;hellip; Oh, I got laid off! Yeah, the great startup experiment didn&amp;rsquo;t go the way I had hoped. I mean, I really enjoyed working there, and the pace of work was a lot of fun and all, but the downturn in the market along with the introduction of &lt;a href=&#34;https://openai.com/blog/chatgpt&#34;&gt;ChatGPT&lt;/a&gt;, as well as ALL of the tech companies laying people off, combined for the perfect storm to mean that I got to experience my very first layoff from the &lt;em&gt;being&lt;/em&gt; layed off perspective. I have to say, not a fan. Anyway, after 87 interviews with more than 20 companies, I finally landed at &lt;a href=&#34;https://tempo.io&#34;&gt;Tempo Software&lt;/a&gt; and I couldn&amp;rsquo;t be happier. The product mix is really quite interesting to me - they deal in Agile planning and tracking tools, which are things that I really enjoy working with!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ozark - Season 2022 - Wrap it up</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2022/06/ozark-season-2022-wrap-it-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 07:35:41 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2022/06/ozark-season-2022-wrap-it-up/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;And, that&amp;rsquo;s a wrap! We managed to get out of there a little before 8:00 on Friday morning and traveled straight back to where we came from. The drive was gloriously boring and uneventful. We stopped one time to get food at a Burger King near Topeka, but other than that, it was a more or less straight shot west on 70. Strangely, the winds of Kansas seemed to switch direction in the week we were gone, so they were in our face the whole way back just like the trip there. Kansas is weird.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ozark - Season 2022 - The Cave</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2022/06/ozark-season-2022-the-cave/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 07:23:41 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2022/06/ozark-season-2022-the-cave/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Two of the families had to leave on Friday morning, so it was just the Chovanecs and Gradys for Friday! Given the smaller group, we decided to do some excursions since logistics would be easier. Of course, we still couldn&amp;rsquo;t all fit in a single car&amp;hellip; Damn big families!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;After seeing off the other two families, and after some breakfast leftovers, we headed out towards Bridal Cave, a cave about 15 miles away. The drive was nice. Along the way we saw lots of interesting signs, including one for a bar called the &amp;ldquo;Glory Hole,&amp;rdquo; one for a mini-golf course called &amp;ldquo;Putt Pirates&amp;rdquo; who asked you to &amp;ldquo;put your balls in our puttholes,&amp;rdquo; and yet another one for a sausage place that bragged that &amp;ldquo;nobody beats our meat.&amp;rdquo; The realization came all at once that the Ozarks had a thing for double entendres. And they weren&amp;rsquo;t bad, honestly! Sadly we weren&amp;rsquo;t able to visit any of these classy establishments..&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ozark - Season 2022 - Jenny&#39;s Birthday</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2022/06/ozark-season-2022-jennys-birthday/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 07:13:41 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2022/06/ozark-season-2022-jennys-birthday/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Thursday! The last full day for some as they were leaving for various weekend commitments. It also happened to be Jenny&amp;rsquo;s birthday! There was nothing much on the docket for Thursday, so you guessed it, we did a bit of swimming, drinking, and eating.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The week was punishingly hot and muggy for those of us that live in the high desert in Colorado, so we did take plenty of breaks in the very cold, air conditioned house to play games. Pool was a big hit! Quinton played tons of it, probably in no small part due to the fact that he didn&amp;rsquo;t have a phone! Foosball was also quite popular. We did play some Jenga, Scrabble, and other board games as well. There was no lack of downtime activities at this house.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ozark - Season 2022 - Dan&#39;s Birthday</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2022/06/ozark-season-2022-dans-birthday/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2022 19:25:41 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2022/06/ozark-season-2022-dans-birthday/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Wednesday (I think, it started to get fuzzy in the middle there) was more of the same. We needed to get the boat back to Pirate Petes by 9:00 AM, so Micky, Jenny, and I took off around 7:30 to transist the 27 miles of water between our cabin and there. It was a lovely drive and we really didn&amp;rsquo;t see a boat to speak of! I think I had to deal with a wake one time when we passed a pontoon going the opposite direction.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ozark - Season 2022 - The Boat</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2022/06/ozark-season-2022-the-boat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2022 18:31:41 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2022/06/ozark-season-2022-the-boat/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The one thing we did that was &amp;ldquo;productive&amp;rdquo; on Monday outside of making food and fixing drinks was to decide on renting a boat for a day. Todd and Sandi had been out earlier that day checking out the area and found a rental place called Pirate Petes where we could rent a pontoon that would sit 12 (we had 13, but we figured we would chance it). So this morning, Todd, Tim, and I went to Pirate Pete&amp;rsquo;s to pickup our boat. This was about the time where we marveled at how much the Ozarks area has leaned into the Pirate mythos. I presume they encountered lake pirates at some point in their distant past&amp;hellip; Probably from Illinois&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ozark - Season 2022 - And, we relax...</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2022/06/ozark-season-2022-and-we-relax.../</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2022 18:13:41 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2022/06/ozark-season-2022-and-we-relax.../</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Day 1, really. Full day 1. Nothing on the plans for the day, so there was little possibility of being late. In that spirit, most of us managed to sleep well past 9:00, even Mireille. We got up and Jenny made some breakfast food that we had purchased, and we eventually meandered our way to the Party Deck!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This property is equipped with many outdoor surfaces from which to party. There is the boat deck, where one could party if they liked. There is the Martini Deck, another party location. There is the deck off of the game room, the deck off of the kitchen, and the main focal point of all water and party activities, the party deck.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ozark - Season 2022 - Retrospective and The Drive</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2022/06/ozark-season-2022-retrospective-and-the-drive/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2022 17:55:41 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2022/06/ozark-season-2022-retrospective-and-the-drive/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m going to try this one a little different. We just got back from the Ozarks yesterday. Consequently, Jenny and I watched the first episode of the last season of Ozark last night, and they started with the end, so I figured I&amp;rsquo;d try that.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It was nice to get caught up today! I started out with a nice run - a little slower and shorter than my normal route. Jenny and I got Starbucks, which we hadn&amp;rsquo;t done in a week. The dogs convalesced from their internment in Doggy Prison, er, camp. All in all it was shaping up to be a good day. We cleaned ou the Guinea Pig cage, then spent 45 minutes trying to retrieve Odin from underneath the hedge in the front yard that he decided was his new home&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Catching Up</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2022/06/catching-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 19:39:41 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2022/06/catching-up/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;So I find myself, once again, very far out of touch with these updates. One of the things I like best about these updates is the running dialog they represent for our vacations. Given we&amp;rsquo;ve got one of those coming up, it seems a good time to reboot!!!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;First, what&amp;rsquo;s happened since we last talked:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;rv-update-20&#34;&gt;RV Update 20!&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It seems I rudely left the world hanging on a final update from our Epic RV Trip from last summer! Many apologies. I had big intentions, and even some cool content planned, but much of that is now lost to time.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epic RVing with the Gradys - Day 19 - and 20...</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2021/07/epic-rving-with-the-gradys-day-19-and-20.../</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2021 19:49:31 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2021/07/epic-rving-with-the-gradys-day-19-and-20.../</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We made it!!! I had a good feeling that we would make it when we woke up in Battle Mountain to see about a 12 hour duration for our drive home. Of course, we are in an RV, so you spend about 25% more time than the map would tell you. Depending on road and wind conditions, I was most comfortable pushing Harvee at about 65 miles per hour, no more. The speed limit in Nevada and Utah is 80. So do the math&amp;hellip; Also, there are stops, there is road construction&amp;hellip; We tend to drive pretty leisurely, and when we stop, we typically do so for at least 30 minutes.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epic RVing with the Gradys - Day 18 - The Long Journey Home</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2021/07/epic-rving-with-the-gradys-day-18-the-long-journey-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 18:27:56 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2021/07/epic-rving-with-the-gradys-day-18-the-long-journey-home/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Interstate Highway System is an amazing thing! Of course, it takes a 9 hour drive on a road &lt;em&gt;other&lt;/em&gt; than the Interstate to really drive that fact home.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Today we gave in and pulled up stakes, one day early, and started the 23+ hour trip home. We have allotted three days (well, two and a half) to get home, but we’ll see. The trip today started going back where we came from on Highway 199, with all the tight turns and incline changes that it entails. It was everything I remembered from a few days earlier!!! I again judiciously utilized the turnouts. It took us about 2 hours and 15 minutes to travel the 85 miles from Crescent City to Grants Pass. We figured that would be the worst conditions of the trip! Well, we hoped…&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epic RVing with the Gradys - Day 17 - Jetboat Cruisin</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2021/07/epic-rving-with-the-gradys-day-17-jetboat-cruisin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jul 2021 18:27:56 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2021/07/epic-rving-with-the-gradys-day-17-jetboat-cruisin/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We had a reservation for a tour today and had to be there by 9:30. It was south back to Klamath, CA, so we had to negotiate a couple of road closures and the windy roads, so we left pretty early, around 8:15. After filling up the Jeep with fuel (gah, California gas prices!!!) and getting some much needed caffeinne, we headed back south along much the same route we had traveled the day prior. The drive was nearly the same in all ways, just a bit shorter as we stopped at Klamath Jetboat Tours for our trip.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epic RVing with the Gradys - Day 16 - Redwoods National Park</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2021/07/epic-rving-with-the-gradys-day-16-redwoods-national-park/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jul 2021 18:27:52 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2021/07/epic-rving-with-the-gradys-day-16-redwoods-national-park/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The day started out with a smash, literally. Jenny was making breakfast on the stove, but didn&amp;rsquo;t quite prop the stove up correctly. After setting off the smoke alarm a couple of times (a feature), she turned the stove off and moved the pan to a different burner to cool - that&amp;rsquo;s when the tempered glass that covers the stove when it&amp;rsquo;s not in use shattered. In her brain fog, Jenny forgot to put it up, and in my early morning fog, I failed to notice. So that was an unexpected 45 minute cleanup exercise and now will be an unexpected expense upon our return. Hopefully that&amp;rsquo;s the worst thing that happens - the stove still works, it just doesn&amp;rsquo;t have its handy cover&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epic RVing with the Gradys - Day 15 - California Bound - Updated!</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2021/07/epic-rving-with-the-gradys-day-15-california-bound-updated/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2021 21:35:26 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2021/07/epic-rving-with-the-gradys-day-15-california-bound-updated/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We are definitely starting to show some signs of either home sickness or road weariness, but we have one more stop on our journey, so we are determined to finish it off. We started the day off with a bit of logistical fun! Our camp was south of Portland about 30 miles, but we had to return the car to Portland. I didn&amp;rsquo;t want to drive the RV back into Portland and have to backtrack to get back south, so we had to figure something out. Luckily we are technology capable! I drove the car back into town, returned it, then it took me all of 5 minutes to wait for my Lyft to come and to drop me back off at camp 30 miles away. Honestly, it should have been much harder! I thought it was also an interesting sign that I happened to pickup the Lyft right outside a brewery - Moon Shrimp Brewery. Might have to try to find one of those, though judging by the size of the place, that could prove difficult. The other thing I noticed on my 35 minute Lyft ride back to camp was that Oregon, unlike Colorado, allows dispensaries to advertise. I found it a little jarring, I guess, but interesting nonetheless. So many strange laws around&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epic RVing with the Gradys - Day 14 - PDX, again</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2021/07/epic-rving-with-the-gradys-day-14-pdx-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jul 2021 21:31:38 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2021/07/epic-rving-with-the-gradys-day-14-pdx-again/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Wow, 14 days of vacation! It definitely shows up in some ways. The little things that start to annoy you about the people you are sharing 150 square feet with, like how they chew, or how they are looking with their eyes. We will need a bigger space soon, but for now we are OK.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We started LATE today! Leaving the waking to chance, nobody stirred until after 8:00. In my defense I stayed up slightly after midnight last night reading by the fire. I mean, the wood just wasn&amp;rsquo;t going out, so I had to stay and make sure it didn&amp;rsquo;t start a forest fire. Luckily nothing jumped from our fire ring to the surrounding area.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epic RVing with the Gradys - Day 13 - Day of Rest</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2021/07/epic-rving-with-the-gradys-day-13-day-of-rest/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2021 21:37:34 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2021/07/epic-rving-with-the-gradys-day-13-day-of-rest/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We decided to take it easy for a day! Our initial plan was to head out to Mt. Hood today, but we decided that we&amp;rsquo;d been going HARD for like 2 weeks straight, so we opted to stay around camp and do camping things today instead! That said, Jenny and I decided to do a 3 mile trail run this morning to stave off all of the calories we&amp;rsquo;ve been eating on vacation! It was a really nice run, actually. Super flat, low altitude, and nice and cool. Just what the doctor ordered for these old legs.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epic RVing with the Gradys - Day 12 - The Oregon Coast</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2021/07/epic-rving-with-the-gradys-day-12-the-oregon-coast/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2021 20:53:51 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2021/07/epic-rving-with-the-gradys-day-12-the-oregon-coast/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;OK, first an answer to yesterday&amp;rsquo;s mystery. I&amp;rsquo;m sure if you are my &amp;ldquo;audience&amp;rdquo; (hi dad), you were saying something like, &amp;ldquo;well duh, it&amp;rsquo;s the airport code for Portland.&amp;rdquo; Yes, of course it is that. But why PDX?? I think I have half an answer. Airport codes were first used in the 1930s when airliners started assigning two letter codes to all airports. By the 1940s, however there were too many airports for the codes, so they had to switch to three letter codes. So Portland used to be &amp;ldquo;PD,&amp;rdquo; but when they expanded to three letters, one of the &amp;ldquo;filler&amp;rdquo; letters was &amp;ldquo;X.&amp;rdquo; So Los Angeles (LA) became LAX, and Portland (PD) became PDX. I suppose the &amp;ldquo;D&amp;rdquo; was just the last letter of Portland, so, there you go&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epic RVing with the Gradys - Day 11 - PDX</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2021/07/epic-rving-with-the-gradys-day-11-pdx/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2021 20:21:24 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2021/07/epic-rving-with-the-gradys-day-11-pdx/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I have no idea why Portland is abbreviated as PDX. I will make it my mission before the trip is through to try to understand that.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Today was a driving day, but we only had about a 2 hour drive in front of us, so it was a little different than other driving days. Jenny and I got up early to try to finish off the laundry from the night before, but sadly the laundry facilities were closed. We were ready to say good by to Thousand Trails, Chehalis. It had some nice features, but overall the experience was suboptimal and may have turned Jenny off to RVing forever! It was damp all the time, it was completely full, there was trash everywhere because there were so many people, the water didn&amp;rsquo;t work for a quarter of the trip, and the toilets were overflowing for a good portion of the rest, and the laundry facilities, while modern, were more or less occupied during the times we could use them and closed otherwise. Oh, and we weren&amp;rsquo;t able to properly level the RV, so we were sleeping down and to the left for the whole time!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epic RVing with the Gradys - Day 10 - Olympic Peninsula</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2021/07/epic-rving-with-the-gradys-day-10-olympic-peninsula/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 21:50:25 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2021/07/epic-rving-with-the-gradys-day-10-olympic-peninsula/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Well, we&amp;rsquo;re about half way through. RVing is becoming a bit challenging. Between losing the water for a full day and being in the Northwest where nothing ever gets dry, people are starting to show some chinks in the armor. One of the men&amp;rsquo;s toilets today was overflowing onto the floor, and it wasn&amp;rsquo;t nice, fresh water flowing out&amp;hellip; We move on tomorrow.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Today we visited Olympic National Park, our third National Park on this trip! Olympic is situated on the Olympic Peninsula of Washington, and due to the fact that there are mountains in the middle of the peninsula, it makes it somewhat difficult to get anywhere. You pretty much have to travel around the perimeter to get anywhere. So you might see something that is 30 miles away and it will take 2 hours and 30 minutes to get to it. We chose the closest place in Olympic National Park, the Stairsteps area, and aimed for that, which was pretty good - it wasn&amp;rsquo;t too busy, and the foliage was very lush.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epic RVing with the Gradys - Day 9 - My Favorite Mountain</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2021/07/epic-rving-with-the-gradys-day-9-my-favorite-mountain/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jul 2021 19:46:04 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2021/07/epic-rving-with-the-gradys-day-9-my-favorite-mountain/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We lazily started the day, for the most part. Even still, I was up at 6:45, which is 7:45 local. I&amp;rsquo;ve been sleeping pretty well here! Last night when we got into the park we were surprised by the fact that the water was out in the park! We&amp;rsquo;ve been getting used to &amp;ldquo;roughing it,&amp;rdquo; but no shower in the morning - that&amp;rsquo;s a road too far!!! I took a little walk around the park and found out that there was one restroom in the park with water, but it was FAR! I went back to the RV and told Jenny who immediately grabbed her shower stuff and the car keys. She was able to shower while I was waited and also finished up some morning business, then we were set for the day!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epic RVing with the Gradys - Day 8 - The Emerald City</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2021/07/epic-rving-with-the-gradys-day-8-the-emerald-city/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2021 19:45:55 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2021/07/epic-rving-with-the-gradys-day-8-the-emerald-city/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;One week ago we left on this adventure!!! In a lot of ways that is hard to believe. We&amp;rsquo;ve certainly held up better than I would have expected being in such close quarters. This is in no small part due to Quinton&amp;rsquo;s mood being quite good the entire time. He really does seem to enjoy this style of trip - despite all the driving and hiking that we are doing!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epic RVing with the Gradys - Day 7 - Thousand Trails</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2021/07/epic-rving-with-the-gradys-day-7-thousand-trails/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 19:16:35 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2021/07/epic-rving-with-the-gradys-day-7-thousand-trails/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Today started late! Nobody stirred until 7:00 local (Pacific) time, which was 8:00 in the time our bodies were used to. We grabbed a quick shower, got some chai teas and burritos, then headed out on the open road in hopes of making it to the Seattle area early!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The first 40 minutes of driving were much like the last hour of driving the previous day - very windy!!! The temperature wasn&amp;rsquo;t quite so bad, though, and the light of day made things much more positive and the driver much more optimistic. Once we got into the Cascades about an hour later, the wind had died down, and we started to remember how amazing the views were here in Washington!!!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epic RVing with the Gradys - Day 6 - Westward Bound</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2021/06/epic-rving-with-the-gradys-day-6-westward-bound/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 19:03:19 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2021/06/epic-rving-with-the-gradys-day-6-westward-bound/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Travel day!!! We didn&amp;rsquo;t have a campsite booked for the night, so our next trip was necessarily going to span 2 days. We didn&amp;rsquo;t really have a plan for where we would stop, but we spent quite a bit of time trying to plan the logistics since there was a massive heat wave that started in the Pacific Northwest and was now moving east, right in our path. We were happy that it moved out of the Seattle/Portland area because that&amp;rsquo;s where we would spend the next 8 days or so, but we still had to travel through Western Montana and Eastern Washington, and temperatures were reported as high as 115 degrees!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epic RVing with the Gradys - Day 5 - Chasing Waterfalls</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2021/06/epic-rving-with-the-gradys-day-5-chasing-waterfalls/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 19:03:19 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2021/06/epic-rving-with-the-gradys-day-5-chasing-waterfalls/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Up early again today! We set the alarm for 6:00 AM, had a quick breakfast, then were out on the road for the 50 minute drive to the North Entrance of Yellowstone. It was definitely worth it, again. We beat a good deal of the traffic and didn&amp;rsquo;t have to wait in line to get in, though to be fair, I don&amp;rsquo;t recall seeing a line to get in any of the times I passed the north entrance gate.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epic RVing with the Gradys - Day 4 - Whitewater Rafting</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2021/06/epic-rving-with-the-gradys-day-4-whitewater-rafting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2021 21:05:48 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2021/06/epic-rving-with-the-gradys-day-4-whitewater-rafting/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Quinton may well be a blood relative of Tom Tibbett. Certainly he has a lot of traits in common with him, as well as his Grandpa and Grandma Grady. While the rest of us are happy to exist on our own, nodding to friendly folks but nothing more, Quinton is curious and likes to engage people in conversation.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We started more &amp;ldquo;Grady style&amp;rdquo; this morning. No alarm was set and we woke when the spirit moved us, which was around 7:30. It felt good to rest after putting about 22,000 steps on yesterday (probably closer to 30,000 for Mireille!) I was excited to try my new griddle and camp stove this morning. We had all the fixin&amp;rsquo;s, so I spent way too long getting things setup, and then basically made bacon and eggs. But they were made on a camp stove on a griddle!!! Honestly, it was pretty great, I&amp;rsquo;m not going to lie, though I am constantly surprised at how effective companies are at separating me from my money. We could have done the same thing in the RV in half the time with regular pans&amp;hellip; One nifty trick we did - Jenny gave me the teapot from the RV to heat up on the stove. After about 30 seconds, though, the plastic cover melted off and now we don&amp;rsquo;t have a teapot! Oops! I guess the camp stove is too strong&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epic RVing with the Gradys - Day 3 - Snoop Dogg&#39;s Windows</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2021/06/epic-rving-with-the-gradys-day-3-snoop-doggs-windows/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jun 2021 22:32:13 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2021/06/epic-rving-with-the-gradys-day-3-snoop-doggs-windows/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Yellowstone, wow! The &amp;ldquo;grandfather&amp;rdquo; of the national park system, and it is quite the site!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/pw/AM-JKLUeV7y-9wB0ArzdoLcLNC9aXBvUCDfmqvJuoqfQTtxaS7npYIwYDzkLgsKBHewEWasa1wHWf3HOtNhSdNSaK93OO2Acfr5A_NTIFrlhwIKo1hVNgLGKSsPZ6FzHJ9ntvpJxyaV05H-01E3a_dAYNSmtrQ=w3012-h1696-no&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h4&gt;The Granddaddy of them all&lt;/h4&gt; &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We started &lt;em&gt;early&lt;/em&gt; by our standards. 6:00 AM we were up, teeth brushed, breakfast eaten (waffles and sausage). By 7:00 we were on the road. It was nice to drive the rental car! It could go the speed limit, was maneuverable, and it didn&amp;rsquo;t get thrown around by the wind so much!!! By 8:00 we were in the park, had purchased our pass, and only had another 1.5 hours to drive before we would finally get somewhere fun to see. Yellowstone is HUGE!!!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epic RVing with the Gradys - Day 2 - Harvee, meet wind</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2021/06/epic-rving-with-the-gradys-day-2-harvee-meet-wind/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 21:01:05 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2021/06/epic-rving-with-the-gradys-day-2-harvee-meet-wind/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Sleeping in a rest stop has its perks. It&amp;rsquo;s free&amp;hellip; It&amp;rsquo;s close to the bathrooms&amp;hellip; And that&amp;rsquo;s about it. It also has its drawbacks. It&amp;rsquo;s bright (which could be a perk considering some of the other drawbacks), it&amp;rsquo;s loud, and there are a lot of people coming in and out all the time. We were able to fall asleep more or less OK, although it was hot, and we had a hard time configuring Harvee for optimal sleeping without jutting out our bed in the back, which can only be done in camping mode. Once we did fall asleep, however, there was a somewhat regular stream of car alarms and horns while people get out of their cars and forget their keys inside.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epic RVing with the Gradys - Day 1 - 9.5 MPG</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2021/06/epic-rving-with-the-gradys-day-1-9.5-mpg/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 22:47:37 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2021/06/epic-rving-with-the-gradys-day-1-9.5-mpg/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We just arrived at our first stopping point, a modern-ish rest stop in far north Wyoming, near Sheridan. The rest stops are pretty nice here in Wyoming, and unlike Colorado, they allow people to park overnight at their rest stops. We weren&amp;rsquo;t really sure where we would stay, but after stopping at a rest stop earlier in the day, they seemed to be setup properly with enough people around that it seemed safe. Some basic research on the internet said that rest stops were valid for staying, though they recommended NOT parking in truck spotss they needed to stop for legal reasons, so if you took their last spot, they might not be too happy! Not really wanting a mid-night confrontation, I am definitely trying to keep on the right side of the truckers. I&amp;rsquo;ve titled this day 9.5 MPG as that seems to be the average efficiency this vehicle will achieve. No more, no less. We&amp;rsquo;re about 550 miles into the trip at this point and the entire time, even with a reset, Harvee has averaged 9.5 MPG.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epic RVing with the Gradys - Day 0 and 0.5 - The Preamble</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2021/06/epic-rving-with-the-gradys-day-0-and-0.5-the-preamble/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2021 08:17:57 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2021/06/epic-rving-with-the-gradys-day-0-and-0.5-the-preamble/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s been an undeniably weird year. About 8 months ago, having been cooped up just like everybody else, I made a bold claim to Quinton that we should do an RV trip and that we would buy an RV. I&amp;rsquo;m still not sure what I was thinking, but like I said, it&amp;rsquo;s been a weird year! For awhile, I honestly looked at ways to make good on that strange claim. In January, though, Jenny helped me come to my senses and we decided it would be better to rent an RV. Yes, they are expensive to rent, but they are more expensive to buy, and then you have to store them, maintain them, and keep paying for them whether you like them or not! So we decided, even if it would cost us 10% of what it would to purchase, it would be better to just do that, get a really nice RV, and really put ourselves to the test of whether we are &amp;ldquo;RV People&amp;rdquo; or not.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Weakest Part of Every System...</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2021/04/the-weakest-part-of-every-system.../</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 19:23:27 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2021/04/the-weakest-part-of-every-system.../</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In the movies it is popular to portray computer hackers as these happy-go-lucky nerds who are mainly interested in whether they &lt;em&gt;can&lt;/em&gt; do something rather than whether than &lt;em&gt;should&lt;/em&gt; do something. In the movies they typically get in over their head, or go up against a rival hacker gang and&amp;hellip; get in over their head.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the real world, it&amp;rsquo;s hard to say that computer hackers are the same as the way they are portraid in the movies - at least the movies I remember. Sure, they are smart folks. But more often than not, at least for the vast majority of the hacking attempts, they are looking to exploit people to get access to their personal information so they can sell it to another bad actor who will then try to profit from having that information. Oh, and &lt;em&gt;most&lt;/em&gt; of the time, hackers are targeting the weakest part of every system - human beings!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COVID Rituals</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/09/covid-rituals/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Sep 2020 08:03:41 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/09/covid-rituals/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I started this post almost a month ago, that&amp;rsquo;s how things are going! Life in COVID remains largely the same, but is starting to feel &amp;ldquo;normal&amp;rdquo; in a lot of ways. Certainly there are things that we&amp;rsquo;d like to do, like go to the movies, or sit in a coffee shop, or have the whole family go to a basketball game, but in some ways, things are probably better. One thing we have been doing all along with varying degrees of success and consistentcy is to create new rituals to make things a little better.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>College - Year 2</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/09/college-year-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2020 09:03:44 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/09/college-year-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Ahh, COVID. I guess life goes on, or we try to do so, anyway. Ethan, after spending the last 5+ months at home (bonus Ethan time for us!) has now completed his transfer to Colorado State University and we have moved him into his dwelling for the upcoming school year! Even though this is Ethan&amp;rsquo;s second year of school, this year seemed almost worse in some ways than moving him in last year. Last year he was going to Regis, which on a good traffic day was only about a 30 minute drive from home. He had access to the city bus and train system to get him home whenever he liked, and we were pretty &amp;ldquo;comfortable&amp;rdquo; with the school. Not to mention, after last summer, we were kind of ready for him to leave (sorry Ethan)! This year he will be attending a big state school which we haven&amp;rsquo;t had an opportunity to really visit or connect with it at all due to the pandemic. Also, it&amp;rsquo;s a bit further away, 90 minutes in good traffic. Given all that, it just &lt;em&gt;felt&lt;/em&gt; different. Quinton seemed to actually care and notice that it was happening this time around. At one point he asked Jenny and I in an accusatory way why we weren&amp;rsquo;t more upset about Ethan leaving! It was kind of nice having him around for the last 5-6 months&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mary the Tooth Fairy</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/06/mary-the-tooth-fairy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 13:03:38 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/06/mary-the-tooth-fairy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Parenting can be hard, obviously. And sometimes we (read I) don&amp;rsquo;t really live up to the challenge. I&amp;rsquo;m hoping this has happened to others&amp;hellip; The last time Mireille lost a tooth was in January. For Mireille, losing a tooth is a somewhat difficult exercise. For some reason, her teeth are very stubborn, and new teeth come up all over the place and don&amp;rsquo;t always displace the tooth they are supposed to replace! So for a few of her teeth, I&amp;rsquo;ve tried my dad-best to extract them, only to end up in tears (both of us, actually), and she&amp;rsquo;s had to go to the dentist to get them out. That&amp;rsquo;s what had happened in January the last time she lost one!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mireille&#39;s Channel - Peace Out!</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/05/mireilles-channel-peace-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2020 09:03:58 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/05/mireilles-channel-peace-out/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;For the vast majority of this blog&amp;rsquo;s audience (Hi mom and dad!), you probably don&amp;rsquo;t know much about the Youtube generation and what types of things go on here. I can&amp;rsquo;t say I know much more outside of what I observe from my children as they are interacting with these sites, but let me try to explain. In today&amp;rsquo;s day and age, being a &amp;ldquo;Youtuber&amp;rdquo; is an actual profession that people aspire towards. There are some &amp;ldquo;internet famous&amp;rdquo; people that actually make not only a living, but millions of dollars a year just posting videos on Youtube. Some notable ones are PewDiePie and Rhett and Link, among others. Basically they post various things to Youtube, ranging from just recording themselves doing something mundane like playing video games, to full on productions in an almost talk show format, sort of like a more interactive PeeWee&amp;rsquo;s Playhouse.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mireille, the runner and COVID haircuts</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/04/mireille-the-runner-and-covid-haircuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Apr 2020 09:14:58 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/04/mireille-the-runner-and-covid-haircuts/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;And it continues&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I believe we are about 8 weeks in to this new reality now. Funny how initially I had all these ideas of things I would do &amp;ldquo;every day&amp;rdquo; during this situation. I was going to blog every day, that seemed like a funny and interesting idea. I was also going to draw something every day, which was fun for awhile, and I&amp;rsquo;ve continued it on a far less frequent basis, but I&amp;rsquo;m definitely not doing anything on a daily basis other than just living.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex... Explained...</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/04/sex...-explained.../</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 09:47:40 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/04/sex...-explained.../</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Over the past several nights, in the midst of our Corona Quarantine, Quinton and I have started watching the show Locke and Key on Netflix together. It&amp;rsquo;s a nice time for the two of us to hang out, watch a pretty well done, suspenseful show together, and have some interesting banter and conversation as a matter of course.  Last night, the episode was a little shorter than normal, and to be honest, our sleeping routines are starting to trend later on either end of the sleep equation, so after our episode was done, the next thing Netflix recommended for me to watch was a show called Sex Explained. Quinton looked at me with a little grin&amp;hellip; Being the designated sex educator in the family, I made a command decision that it would be a fine thing for him to watch, though I hadn&amp;rsquo;t watched it myself, so I had no idea what the content might be like. It was rated TV-MA (which Quinton still pronounces TV &amp;ldquo;mah&amp;rdquo;) afterall.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COVID Reality - Day 2-9</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/03/covid-reality-day-2-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 10:50:59 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/03/covid-reality-day-2-9/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;COVID Reality Day 6 was the Grady&amp;rsquo;s breaking point. There was widespread dissent in the ranks, and those that are supposed to be even and get us through all this were SUPER crabby. Mireille had a big tantrum the likes that I haven&amp;rsquo;t seen in quite awhile, Quinton managed to squeek out some tears at some point, Ethan is cooped up and wants to see his friends and his girlfriend, and Jenny and I were basically not on speaking terms with one another most of the day. We were on yelling terms, just not speaking terms. Today seems to be better. The saving grace is that it&amp;rsquo;s very nice outside - spring weather makes everything seem a little better.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COVID Reality - Day 1</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/03/covid-reality-day-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 08:50:41 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/03/covid-reality-day-1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Today is the first day of what I&amp;rsquo;m calling &amp;ldquo;COVID Reality.&amp;rdquo; In Colorado, while we aren&amp;rsquo;t ordered to &amp;ldquo;shelter in place,&amp;rdquo; anything that would be worthwhile leaving the house for has been closed down, most notably all sporting events, theaters, churches, restaurants, breweries, and bars. Oh, and schools. These closures are setup right now for 4 weeks. We&amp;rsquo;ll see how long it actually ends up being (I doubt &lt;em&gt;shorter&lt;/em&gt; than 4 weeks). So we&amp;rsquo;re getting to know our family better, for better or worse. I&amp;rsquo;m working from home, the kids are doing school from home, Ethan is doing college from home (they closed the campus for the rest of the year), and Jenny has had to take on the new jobs of teacher and principal in addition to Janitor, Laundress, and overall house CEO.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring Break - COVID-19 Edition - Chapter 4 - Home</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/03/spring-break-covid-19-edition-chapter-4-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 19:39:41 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/03/spring-break-covid-19-edition-chapter-4-home/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re cutting our vacation short! Today was originally supposed to be the day we took a trip on the narrow gauge railroad, but alas, they canceled their trips starting today. We were then going to go up to Telluride to take in the scenery there as well as do some snowmobiling, but threats of weather in the mountains and continued restaurant closures convinced us otherwise. As I write this, the county in which Telluride resides has just issued a &amp;ldquo;Shelter In Place&amp;rdquo; order, which is even more reason to be happy we didn&amp;rsquo;t end up there this morning!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring Break - COVID-19 Edition - Chapter 3 - Closed</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/03/spring-break-covid-19-edition-chapter-3-closed/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 19:39:41 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/03/spring-break-covid-19-edition-chapter-3-closed/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Happy St. Patrick&amp;rsquo;s Day!!!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We had a plan for the day, but we needed first to get some breakfast. That would come in the form of McDonalds and Starbucks, both of which were open, but neither of which would allow you to eat or consume there, abiding by the governor&amp;rsquo;s orders! Quinton discovered the mediocraty but sufficiency of the McDonald&amp;rsquo;s breakfast burritos (better with hot sauce) while Mireille enjoyed her Hot Cakes and sausage, which are&amp;hellip; fine&amp;hellip; The best part about where we are staying is that it is walking distance to so many places - mostly restaurants! But we were able to walk to both of these places, order in the dining room, then enjoy them back in our room before departing.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring Break - COVID-19 Edition - Chapter 2 - The Drive</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/03/spring-break-covid-19-edition-chapter-2-the-drive/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 19:39:32 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/03/spring-break-covid-19-edition-chapter-2-the-drive/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;On Monday at 7:45, we left home, without the animals (Ethan&amp;rsquo;s college canceled their classes the first three days of this week, so the animals could stay with him). We first stopped at Mireille&amp;rsquo;s school to pickup her packet of &amp;ldquo;school at home&amp;rdquo; papers. Then we headed west through the mountains towards Durango, CO.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For the first few hours, we listened to public radio. After about 2 hours of that, we had had enough of the Coronavirus talk, so we listened to a podcast about the space race. During that time, the mayor of Denver announced that he was ordering all restaurants and bars closed for dine-in for 8 weeks. Well, lucky for us - we weren&amp;rsquo;t going to be affected by that!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring Break - COVID-19 Edition - Chapter 1 - Preamble</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/03/spring-break-covid-19-edition-chapter-1-preamble/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2020 21:12:18 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/03/spring-break-covid-19-edition-chapter-1-preamble/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Spring Break!!! Woo!!!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Actually, as the years go on, the event has become more and more complicated. Three kids in two different schools last year was one thing - but this year, three kids in three different schools increased the complexity. And add to that the fact that I &lt;em&gt;just&lt;/em&gt; started a new job&amp;hellip; No worries - we would ignore the adult child, and that will simplify things!!! Well, sort of. Still, with the two youngers in two different schools, of course their spring break didn&amp;rsquo;t line up. So we took the older child&amp;rsquo;s break, took the younger child out of school, and planned on heading to Phoenix to visit with the Grandparents who we haven&amp;rsquo;t seen in Phoenix for a couple of years now. Easy peasy!!!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>So - I got a new job...</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/02/so-i-got-a-new-job.../</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 11:35:19 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/02/so-i-got-a-new-job.../</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It doesn&amp;rsquo;t happen very often, thankfully, but I started a new job this month! It also doesn&amp;rsquo;t happen very often that I blog about myself. Both good things, I think!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;At the beginning of February, I started a new job with Twilio. Headquartered in San Francisco, I&amp;rsquo;m actually working in Downtown Denver where one of the largest non-HQ offices is located. There are so many new things that I&amp;rsquo;m experiencing, which is sort of the point, I guess. For one, It&amp;rsquo;s been a long time since I&amp;rsquo;ve worked at a company with more than 500 employees (Twilio has ~3000). Also, it&amp;rsquo;s been a LONG time since I&amp;rsquo;ve worked downtown anywhere, and the first time I&amp;rsquo;ve worked in downtown Denver. The obvious complication is commuting, which is something I&amp;rsquo;m still experimenting with. Denver is progressive enough to have a Light Rail system, which I&amp;rsquo;ve been taking advantage of. Jenny&amp;rsquo;s actually been kind enough to ferry me between the house and the light rail station a few miles from our house, so even two weeks in I can already feel my driving skills start to erode!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big Update on Grady Kids</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/01/big-update-on-grady-kids/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2020 09:25:40 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/01/big-update-on-grady-kids/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s a broken record on this blog, but it&amp;rsquo;s again been a LONG time since I&amp;rsquo;ve done anything. There is definitely an ebb and flow to my state of mind that really dictates how much I observe of the world around me, and around the end of the year is a time of reflection for lots of people. So here it goes&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This post is going to read mostly as a Quinton post. It&amp;rsquo;s not that I don&amp;rsquo;t love my other kids, he&amp;rsquo;s just at a point where the things he does crack me up more than what I&amp;rsquo;m observing from my other kids right now. Ethan, Mireille, forgive me!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Dead Cat Saga</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/09/the-dead-cat-saga/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2019 14:51:03 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/09/the-dead-cat-saga/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A couple of weekends ago, Quinton and I, on a whim, went outside to play catch with a baseball. It&amp;rsquo;s sort of odd that we would do that. Most of Quin&amp;rsquo;s time at home involves playing XBox, and most of my time involves yelling at Quinton about playing XBox, but on this occassion we both decided to do something a little different.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Flash back to earlier that morning, upon waking up I saw that our doorbell camera had gone off a couple of times during the night. I studied the pictures (since I&amp;rsquo;m too cheap to pay for video storage) to find a cat hanging around on our front stoop. Kind of strange, but whatever. Later that morning I took something out to the garbage and, upon rounding the corner to the front of the house, I was presented with some kind of bad smell. I chalked it up to needing the garbage taken away and went about my day.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>College</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/08/college/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2019 20:24:15 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/08/college/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Yesterday, I had to mow my own lawn. Actually I wasn&amp;rsquo;t even that sad about that - it only takes about an hour to really do a number on my lawn. I do the mowing, of course, along with regular mower maintenance. Then I get the trimmer out and move the infringing grass back off of the cement walkways and what-not. Heck, I even took the time to fertilize. It was all done while I walked, contemplating what had just happened. A life event. A first. My indentured lawn-mower had left home and went to college!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Firsts, and a Conversation with Mireille</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/08/firsts-and-a-conversation-with-mireille/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 09:50:50 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/08/firsts-and-a-conversation-with-mireille/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Quinton started middle school this week. For some reason, middle school scares the hell out of me on behalf of my children. To boot, he&amp;rsquo;s been actively and heavily lobbying to be moved to the public school from our relatively more comfortable private school middle school situation. Well, he made pretty good arguments, so we relented, so now he has started school at Laredo Public Middle School, right next to where Ethan has spent his last 4 years at Smoky Hill.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adult Child</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/08/adult-child/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2019 13:18:08 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/08/adult-child/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Is that a contradiction? I suppose it doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter - that is what we have now. Ethan, as of last Friday, is considered by this society to be &amp;ldquo;an adult.&amp;rdquo; He is now able to drin&amp;hellip; Well, he can rent a ca&amp;hellip; Hmm&amp;hellip; He can be drafted, and he can vote, and if he were to do something bad, he can be punished like the hardened adult criminal that he would undoubtedly be.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hawaii Vacation 2019 - Day 8</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/06/hawaii-vacation-2019-day-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2019 20:38:50 -1000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/06/hawaii-vacation-2019-day-8/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;day-8---is-it-time-to-go-home-yet&#34;&gt;Day 8 - Is it time to go home yet?&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While we love Hawai&amp;rsquo;i, we are all ready to go home. We started the day like most others, coffee at the hotel lobby. We then collected the spawn and did some swimming before showering and heading back to Hale&amp;rsquo;iwa for lunch at &amp;ldquo;Killer Tacos.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;After lunch, we decided to do some more beach stuff. We got some stuff, though not as much as we did yesterday, and headed off on the .75 mile walk to Keiki Beach, home Keiki Pool, which is a natural pool in the beach that is popular for people with little kids with them.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hawaii Vacation 2019 - Day 7</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/06/hawaii-vacation-2019-day-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2019 19:55:11 -1000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/06/hawaii-vacation-2019-day-7/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;day-7---submarine&#34;&gt;Day 7 - Submarine&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;morning&#34;&gt;Morning&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Day 7 - this vacation is getting long!!! Still fun stuff to do, and so much that we haven&amp;rsquo;t even done yet! Today we had an appointment in Waikiki at 10:00 to go on a submarine! The trip there is about 90 minutes with morning traffic, so we left by 8:00 to get down there.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We took the standard mid-island route this time which looked much different this time! We got to see the pineapple fields and everything. Of course, it isn&amp;rsquo;t anywhere near as interesting as the windward coast route, but it was still interesting to see in the daylight.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hawaii Vacation 2019 - Day 6</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/06/hawaii-vacation-2019-day-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 18:09:33 -1000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/06/hawaii-vacation-2019-day-6/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;day-6---relax&#34;&gt;Day 6 - Relax&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;morning-at-turtle-bay&#34;&gt;Morning at Turtle Bay&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Thursday, I think. It&amp;rsquo;s sometimes hard to keep track on vacation - especially one this long! So we&amp;rsquo;ll go with Thursday. We didn&amp;rsquo;t have any excursions planned for this day, but that sort of made Jenny nervous that we would sit around the condo all day and play video games. She was probably correct&amp;hellip; That said, we began the morning with some Smash Brothers, as is now becoming a thing. Perhaps we will take this activity back to the mainland with us! I&amp;rsquo;ll give it a shot.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hawaii Vacation 2019 - Day 5</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/06/hawaii-vacation-2019-day-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2019 22:19:47 -1000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/06/hawaii-vacation-2019-day-5/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;day-5---polynesian-cultural-center&#34;&gt;Day 5 - Polynesian Cultural Center&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;morning&#34;&gt;Morning&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Well, we are certainly adjusted to the timezone by now. Nobody stirred until well after 6:00 AM, and nobody got out of bed until after 7:00. It seems pretty easy to acclimate to westernbound timezones, at least to a point. I remember the adjustment being very difficult in Manila, but here it&amp;rsquo;s been a breeze!!!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Jenny, Mireille, and I went over to the hotel lobby and got some morning drinks and a croissant while the boys continued sleeping. While we were there we started picking out locations where Forgetting Sarah Marshall was filmed. It&amp;rsquo;s kind of fun recognizing things from a movie&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hawaii Vacation 2019 - Day 4</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/06/hawaii-vacation-2019-day-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2019 21:51:32 -1000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/06/hawaii-vacation-2019-day-4/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;day-4---koalua-ranch&#34;&gt;Day 4 - Koalua Ranch&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;morning-shenanigans&#34;&gt;Morning Shenanigans&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The day still started earlyish. Jenny and I were out of bed and walking to the hotel lobby for some &amp;ldquo;coffee&amp;rdquo; before 7:00. We then went on a little walk of the grounds to see what we could see. Unfortunately it wasn&amp;rsquo;t much!!! There are a lot of trails on the property. Good for walking, biking, horse riding, etc. We probably did about 2 miles, but needed to get back to the kids and make sure they weren&amp;rsquo;t killing each other.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hawaii Vacation 2019 - Day 3</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/06/hawaii-vacation-2019-day-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2019 16:41:27 -1000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/06/hawaii-vacation-2019-day-3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;day-3---pearl-harbor&#34;&gt;Day 3 - Pearl Harbor&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;sunrise&#34;&gt;Sunrise&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;After our busted sunset last night, both boys were all into the idea of waking up this morning and seeing the sunrise. As it stood, I was able to convince Mireille to come with me! We had a nice walk, but ultimately our quest to see a sunrise failed due to clouds. Oh well!!!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/AwgGLZ7gX19xJytL3jHnpsAMEtCYQx3EkIgm_GvqwK3O2-5woAY4ZvLBNuY2tRmi8fbjsXyU5akfynrOpMUhM8bHT-t18ZbQc2E9dFLqRkslIv_5W6tV5VYD_enQ9dVj2iO65KOTEhI=w2012-h1508-no&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h4&gt;Bah - clouds!!!&lt;/h4&gt; &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/u_Dn9nIThJC3AGjoo2octheJczuAWVrg4nVNxJYG9vCHD6SJS26l2rwWJZV7zaYrqvptZn21NkVm0XbFTYCy31o2yyhbKog9LYvfvGGccP-7ZxNonaTRyWgcKQ_8vtZFEnInIGrarv8=w1132-h1508-no&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h4&gt;Mireille on our sunrise walk&lt;/h4&gt; &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;windward-drive&#34;&gt;Windward Drive&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our excursion for the day was to Pearl Harbor - perhaps you&amp;rsquo;ve heard of it! Unfortunately we were3 meeting all the way back in Honolulu. In fact, we were meeting in Waikiki, and our pickup time was 8:30 - right in the midst of rush hour!!! We took off around 6:45 as the drive is an hour in good conditions, and true to point, it took us about an hour and 15 minutes.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hawaii Vacation 2019 - Day 2</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/06/hawaii-vacation-2019-day-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2019 20:54:53 -1000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/06/hawaii-vacation-2019-day-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;day-2---turtle-bay-resort&#34;&gt;Day 2 - Turtle Bay Resort&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;birthday&#34;&gt;Birthday!!!&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Before I say anything, I have acknowledge the celebration of another year for my beautiful wife and mother of our children. 46, er, 39!!! Happy Birthday, Jenny!!!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/kXCnbC1DUJibx2_vywr_JWlB4jCdtvoL0t3rGsHUWChi9_6toQpGYx-DAMXvrKCzrrtvD630FWLik1pyqIz6sfHQJrTiD89sSwjhuCYbkEQlG7Fy_kd6PA1niDho4a2Py9CH6O8p9ts=w420-h316-no&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h4&gt;The Birthday girl at Breakfast with Mireille and Quinton&lt;/h4&gt; &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;sunrise&#34;&gt;Sunrise&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;After crashing &amp;ldquo;early&amp;rdquo; Hawaii time, I managed to wake up &amp;ldquo;early&amp;rdquo; Hawaii time again. Though I had only 6 or so hours of sleep, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t get it out of my head that I wanted to see a sunrise. So around 5:15 I ambled out of bed, brushed my teeth, and headed outside towards the beach.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hawaii Vacation 2019 - Day 1</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/06/hawaii-vacation-2019-day-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2019 00:44:45 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/06/hawaii-vacation-2019-day-1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;day-1---travel&#34;&gt;Day 1 - Travel&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;dia&#34;&gt;DIA&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In typical Grady fashion, we arrived at the airport area about three hours in advance of our 2:30 departure time. Don’t want to be hurried!!! We were able to secure parking for the week+ for around $60 at an off site lot, and even got upgraded to indoor parking since all of the outdoor spots were taken!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/m3pwUEJLpN5GpfGnT0Co_SaMcWe-rXHCrI_jYjxsvXeEsM_XESmq5f2-MpW5zAIVv6WJ2zpv8XxJjG9SA91ePLwWgMI4CpBoOHlg0jmdE-WGbiMlWu9G3gj1q53SAM7ZdvuvaU0jl2g=w1132-h1508-no&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h4&gt;Shuttle on the way to DIA&lt;/h4&gt; &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/LfsXxQPV78NDA763kccOq0tTkekdGt5h3tlC8fvR7W27YAPGU-zuMKCIMQQwAxRDrEbX7HJrX3rDEw3tdSVREy27tFoYYmD6i8ys0kJyrullrULk3l4n4XrT-Bt8kg7EY_zogdEQWBE=w1132-h1508-no&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h4&gt;Shuttle on the way to DIA&lt;/h4&gt; &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/760jNpdvT2mf2NzoIYmREWYt2yTk1HeXRwJpwhdcrrE33KQF_5knFNf7D8r-4_pvr1Rn8X6UgKF1IKjPqy03PO8K-7OLSqBOOBa6lG8zNb3GXhT3nRMMRBoxQM5slGHqssjbP5J-WEU=w1132-h1508-no&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h4&gt;Shuttle on the way to DIA&lt;/h4&gt; &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The morning went pretty easily. Prep for this vacation started over a week ago with Jenny’s packing, and really went into effect yesterday when we tried to get Mireille’s hair braided, then this morning with a haircut for Quinton. As we sit here waiting to board, I’m thinking back on vacations past, and looking forward to how this one might transpire.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quin Said a Bad Word</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/05/quin-said-a-bad-word/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 13:18:08 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/05/quin-said-a-bad-word/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s graduation week. I have a longer, more sentimental post that I&amp;rsquo;m working through, but I had to jot this one down quickly before it was lost to history. Since it is graduation week, we have family that have started arriving to help Ethan celebrate and to help remind us how old we are.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Last night, my parents, Ethan and his girlfriend Rachel, and Jenny and I were sitting around the table just talking about different things. It was nice. Quinton was in his room playing XBox and Mireille was kind of bouncing between the TV in the living room and upstairs. At one point, though, she came in and talked with all of us to ensure that she could tattle on her brother.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teeth, Hoops, and Firsts</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/04/teeth-hoops-and-firsts/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 09:38:11 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/04/teeth-hoops-and-firsts/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Mireille finally lost that first tooth! It was a few weeks ago, now. She was walking around the kitchen, and I asked her, like I had been every day for quite a few weeks, how her teeth were doing. Her two front teeth on the bottom were coming in behind the baby teeth. On that fateful night, one of them was finally loose enough that I felt confident enough to give it a little tug and evict it from its spot that the other tooth so badly wanted. She was tough - no crying or anything. I think she was a little sad that she didn&amp;rsquo;t lose it at school since they give you a cool necklace for your fallen chomper so you can take it home - she really wanted one of those necklaces!!! The other one never really got loose enough for me to pull, but the dentist did the deed a couple of weeks later with the help of some laughing gas and a little numbing medicine. I, sadly, wasn&amp;rsquo;t there to see it, but Jenny said she was pretty out of it. A little video would have been fun!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big Man on Campus - a tall tale by Quinton</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/02/big-man-on-campus-a-tall-tale-by-quinton/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 09:58:38 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/02/big-man-on-campus-a-tall-tale-by-quinton/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Quinton had an assignment to write a tall tale. Coincidental with getting the assignment, Quin had learned about a competition that his cousin, Graham, had recently done with his uncle, Bruce. For those that don&amp;rsquo;t know them, Graham is a 10 year old, not particularly big, and Bruce, his uncle, is about 5&amp;rsquo; 2&amp;quot; and weighs probably about 130 pounds. Anyway, Graham challenged uncle Bruce to a plank challenge. Bruce was able to plank for 5 minutes, but Graham was able to do it for 30 minutes! Inspired by this competition, Quinton decided to memorialize it in his very own tall tale.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Catching up to 2019</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/02/catching-up-to-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2019 17:00:42 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/02/catching-up-to-2019/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A new year&amp;hellip; It went and happened again, and again I find myself in the position of having a resolution of writing more. It seems a yearly concern, but here goes the latest attempt.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;2018 was very kind to the Grady&amp;rsquo;s. Ethan wrecked a couple of cars, but has now had his latest one for over 6 months without incident (knock on wood). Brandon got a new (to me) car in the form of a 2017 Chevy Malibu - yeah, I can&amp;rsquo;t seem to break that mold. Hey, they&amp;rsquo;re nice cars!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zazu</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/12/zazu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 14:48:10 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/12/zazu/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We added a new family member this weekend.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/6kl4ED5ZDHrieDhBgvzXocqKi4A1QreGuLoI1aLxT0RqNuE531kSBHa3ObLrH9FIH0pZuDINgdB1qzoKuZxNOHzQoxc5XwC-tI2JW8gRRNq6yOiQ1qbwf3sphyGHy893pq39kmaJXpY=w1194-h1590-no&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h4&gt;Zaz and Quinton&lt;/h4&gt; &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Say hello to &amp;ldquo;Zazu,&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;Zaz&amp;rdquo; as Quinton likes to call him. Quinton has really wanted a pet of his own for awhile now. He has been trying to get us to get another dog and for me to leave the dog alone so I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be the &amp;ldquo;alpha male&amp;rdquo; to this one like I am to Heinz.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moab</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/11/moab/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2018 19:58:19 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/11/moab/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-trip&#34;&gt;The Trip&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Moab. Or as Mireille would pronounce it, Mo-Ab. Small city of 5000 some people in Southeast Utah, the land of Mormons, backwards liquor laws, and some spectacular natural landscapes. Since we&amp;rsquo;ve moved to the west we&amp;rsquo;ve always looked for a reason to get out here to take in these sights. Thanks to some early travel by Mom and Pop Grady, having come through Denver the weekend prior for Thanksgiving day festivities, we finally had our opportunity to check it out over the Thanksgiving day weekend, figuring it wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be quite as busy or quite as hot as it would in the peak months.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mireille the Investigator</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/11/mireille-the-investigator/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 19:58:19 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/11/mireille-the-investigator/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I couldn&amp;rsquo;t find my toothbrush this morning. That may not sound that strange, but I have one of those big Sonicare toothbrushes that would seem very difficult to lose. In fact, where my toothbrush was supposed to be, Jenny&amp;rsquo;s had taken its place, a similar Sonicare but different color.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I had no idea where it could be. Initially I blamed Jenny for hiding it on me. She came home angry last night for reasons unknown, and was argumentative. Since I had brushed my teeth before she had gotten home, I immediately blamed her for hiding my toothbrush out of spite. However, she explained that she did not hide it, and I eventually believed her sincerity.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mireille the Observer</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/11/mireille-the-observer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 10:10:26 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/11/mireille-the-observer/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Mireille is far and away the most observant of our children. Ethan&amp;rsquo;s not bad - far better than myself. Quinton, well, he and I are about in the same boat, and it&amp;rsquo;s not a good boat. Mireille will notice just about anything, even if it seems inconsequential. For example, Jenny occasionally colors her hair, but in a subtle way such that color blind me will not notice. Mireille does, though. The other day, Jenny swapped out the pulls on our dressers in our room, and the first thing Mireille said when she walked in the room was &amp;ldquo;when did you get new ones of these?&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Catching Up</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/09/miscellaneous-catching-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Sep 2018 08:52:45 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/09/miscellaneous-catching-up/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It’s been awhile on a couple of these, so I figured I should jot them down before time erodes them from my memory.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This first story has been getting good traction in my friend and colleague circles. Before I can tell the story, I need to tee it up a little bit. Quinton is obviously a black male being raised among “the whites.” From time to time that causes some conflict in him. He really likes the idea of exploring black culture, but acknowledges that he doesn’t know much about it. One thing he likes to do to try to dip his toe into it is to listen to rap music. While there is a very deep collection of amazing rap songs, many, many of them delve into topics or language that is just a little rough to continually barrage the ears of our five year old, and ten year old as well.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Francisco - 2018 - Day 6</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/07/san-francisco-2018-day-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2018 20:18:26 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/07/san-francisco-2018-day-6/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Flying home is tough, but today was tougher than normal since our flight wasn&amp;rsquo;t until 8:30. I think I would almost prefer a midday flight. We theoretically had enough time to do some stuff, but we managed to accomplish all that we had set out to do in the prior 5 days. So it was going to be awkward. As I sit here, we were 3 hours early for our 8:30 PM flight to Denver, but it has been delayed by an hour, so we will be sitting here for some time!!!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Francisco - 2018 - Day 5</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/07/san-francisco-2018-day-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2018 20:18:22 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/07/san-francisco-2018-day-5/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Our penultimate day of vacation started out early-ish. Of course, we got out to Starbucks and had some donut holes from our new favorite donut shop in California, the creatively named &amp;ldquo;Jelly Donut,&amp;rdquo; where I can&amp;rsquo;t say I ever saw a jelly donut there&amp;hellip; I was a little nervous to be going to the wharf today because it was a weekend, so tourist traffic would be high. Our ultimate goal was to get to our whale watching tour by 3:00 which took off at the wharf, and the website gave instructions to places where you could park inexpensively for $50 a day. Being slightly more tech savvy, I found a spot at a nearby garage for $19 using Spot Hero.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Francisco - 2018 - Day 4</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/07/san-francisco-2018-day-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2018 20:18:16 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/07/san-francisco-2018-day-4/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Day 4 - I finally was able to get up in time to hit the road for a run. While I&amp;rsquo;m quite out of shape, I was still able to cut 25 seconds per mile off of my new-normal running speed while in the oxygen rich California air! Almost enough to get me to go out and do it again on this trip&amp;hellip; Almost&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Much like yesterday, today was about doing the things that Jenny and I had planned on doing on our last trip but were prevented from doing due to the wildfires in Wine Country. So after our typical morning routine of breakfast, Starbucks, and now donuts, we headed NORTH this time to the Napa/Sonoma region for some wine stuff.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Francisco - 2018 - Day 3</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/07/san-francisco-2018-day-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2018 22:16:20 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/07/san-francisco-2018-day-3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Friday was all about Muir Woods. Jenny and I had planned to visit here when we came to the area last September but weren&amp;rsquo;t able to make it due to the wildfires at the time. We were lucky to have seen a sign that warned visitors that they needed a parking reservation prior to visiting. We had secured a noon parking reservation for the day, but we were a little early. The parking attendants informed us that we couldn&amp;rsquo;t come until our reservation time, so we continued down the road to Muir Beach, about 3 miles past the entrance to Muir Woods.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Francisco - 2018 - Day 2</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/07/san-francisco-2018-day-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2018 22:16:15 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/07/san-francisco-2018-day-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;After some much needed sleep, we woke up fairly early-ish and took in the world famous Embassy Suites complimentary breakfast! Well, most of us did. Despite getting up in time, Ethan decided not to partake.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The first order of business, feed the addiction, off to the local Starbucks. Once that was out of the way, we were free to head downtown for a day in the city. Our first stop was Fisherman&amp;rsquo;s Wharf. To get there we got to cross the Golden Gate Bridge going south, which means we had to pay a toll! Actually we didn&amp;rsquo;t pay the toll right then, we were just scanned. For those interested in how to pay tolls for Golden Gate Bridge, you can just go to their website up to 48 hours after you cross and enter your license plate information along with payment details. Pretty easy. It costs $6 to cross the bridge most times.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Francisco - 2018 - Day 1</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/07/san-francisco-2018-day-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 21:48:18 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/07/san-francisco-2018-day-1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve been traveling WAY too much lately. After a brief trip to Jacksonville, the boys and I went into the mountains last weekend, then I boarded a plane to Chicago on Monday only to return on Tuesday in anticipation of an early Wednesday departure to San Francisco. I&amp;rsquo;m happy I&amp;rsquo;m not sick!!! Can&amp;rsquo;t say the same for Quinton, however. Jenny called me on Monday evening to inform me that Quinton had been throwing up all day and into the evening. Should be fun!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2018 Boy&#39;s Trip - Day 2</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/07/2018-boys-trip-day-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 20:50:03 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/07/2018-boys-trip-day-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;day-2&#34;&gt;Day 2&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We started the day slowly, as any good boy&amp;rsquo;s trip would. Since we didn&amp;rsquo;t go to bed until later, we slept in until after 8:00. I sort of wanted to get going, so I got up and started cooking half of our 2 pounds of bacon and a dozen eggs. The smell was enough to wake Ethan up by 8:30, mainly because the apartment was so full of smoke that I think he started suffocating. No matter, he was up.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2018 Boy&#39;s Trip</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/07/2018-boys-trip/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2018 20:29:30 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/07/2018-boys-trip/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;day-1&#34;&gt;Day 1&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here we sit at 521 Elm St. in historic Leadville, CO, our VRBO for the weekend. Ethan, Quinton, and I are doing our first &amp;ldquo;boy&amp;rsquo;s weekend.&amp;rdquo; It was hard leaving Jenny and Mireille behind, but we stayed the course and are going through with it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The trip up here was rougher than expected. Traffic out of Denver to the mountains via I70 was somehow worse than it normally would be when we are coming up to ski, but we persevered. We even took a slight detour going over Loveland Pass, a route that we normally cut short by 30 minutes by going through the Eisenhower tunnel, but this weekend is about adventure and doing things that we wouldn&amp;rsquo;t normally be able to do when the girls are around!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Old Blog Reclaimed!</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/05/old-blog-reclaimed/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 14:45:58 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/05/old-blog-reclaimed/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I have a small project going on right now. I&amp;rsquo;ve downloaded my old blog from Blogspot and have started persisting it here, in a more controlled fashion - everything all in one place! Since I had over 180 posts on that blog, it will take some time to reclaim all of the old posts and reformat them to properly work here, but the work has begun. It is tedious work, involving some level of digital archaeology, but I think it is worthwhile and will make this blog much more portable in the future.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring Break 2018 - Day Three</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/03/spring-break-2018-day-three/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Mar 2018 20:15:04 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/03/spring-break-2018-day-three/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;taos&#34;&gt;Taos&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our third day was dedicated to Taos. Having slept in a little, but not quite as much as the prior day, we had a little extra time to do some swimming in hopes of getting away from the crowds in the pool. We weren&amp;rsquo;t successful in avoiding crowds, but we did get about 45 minutes of swimming in before we left the hotel. Mireille, Quinton, and I played some hide and seek (it&amp;rsquo;s more fun than you would think). Mireille learned she could float with her little floatie thing, and even jumped into the pool with it on! Jenny and Ethan I&amp;rsquo;m sure did boring things in the room&amp;hellip; Probably showered or whatever.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring Break 2018 - Day Two</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/03/spring-break-2018-day-two/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 21:34:29 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/03/spring-break-2018-day-two/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;los-alamos&#34;&gt;Los Alamos&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Thank goodness, today started out MUCH later than the prior one. Nobody really stirred until 9:00, giving Mireille a much needed 13 hours, and Quinton an even more needed 11.5. Of course, I was also happy to finally get 10 myself, though I was up several times in the night for the &amp;ldquo;old man pee.&amp;rdquo; While we all got ready, Jenny and Mireille went to get some coffee at the very convenient on presmises Starbucks in the lobby. Jenny noted when we got back that they rode the &amp;ldquo;alligator&amp;rdquo; to get down to the first floor.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring Break 2018 - Day One</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/03/spring-break-2018-day-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2018 21:00:53 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/03/spring-break-2018-day-one/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;am&#34;&gt;AM&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As we suspected, and as is typical, we were up way too early. Mireille woke up around 7:00 the first time, Quinton followed about 7:30. While Mireille was able to fall back to sleep for a bit, Quinton was screaming for food by 8:00, so we were up! We left Ethan to sleep while the rest of us went down to one of the dozen or so restaurants the hotel had to offer for a nice buffet breakfast. It was at breakfast that I learned that New Mexico is the only state in the union that has a &amp;ldquo;state question.&amp;rdquo; That question is, perhaps predictably, &amp;ldquo;red or green.&amp;rdquo; They are referring, of course, to what color alien they keep at Area 51! OK, they don&amp;rsquo;t mean that - it refers to chili peppers, where New Mexico is the &amp;ldquo;world leader,&amp;rdquo; whatever that means. At breakfast and restaurants it means that you basically get chili with anything you order, and you can order red or greeen chili to your liking. I typically choose green since I am now a Denver native, and that&amp;rsquo;s what us quirky Denver natives like.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring Break 2018 - The Drive</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/03/spring-break-2018-the-drive/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 22:29:27 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/03/spring-break-2018-the-drive/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Are we going to the hotel tonight?&amp;rdquo; This is the question repeated at least nightly for the last two weeks by our youngest, Mireille. For some reason she just loves hotels! I think it has something to do with the swimming pools. Perhaps she just likes to travel! At any rate, it had been a constant anthem for the last several weeks - &amp;ldquo;are we going to the hotel?&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The day before we left, we dropped the &amp;ldquo;Flex-car&amp;rdquo; off at Rack Attack to get rails and a luggage rack installed. We also purchased a travel box so we could finally travel in style. While the car had it&amp;rsquo;s new rack put on, Jenny, Ethan, and I visited the University of Denver, a local private school, to see if Ethan had any interested. Thankfully, he didn&amp;rsquo;t. It&amp;rsquo;s a pricey school!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Honor Roll</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/03/honor-roll/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 12:42:11 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/03/honor-roll/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Last Wednesday, I was able to witness the St. Pius X 2nd Trimester Honor Roll ceremony, and my favorite middle child was among the honorees. Quinton achieved all A- or better in the last trimester. In fact, he got all A&amp;rsquo;s with the exception of one A- which he got in Art.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Congratulations, Quinton!!!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/P-EV9sE9rOIKWk_qnewG_KJ9N0mPtppQopCnCnmJ1iuDUdHJwbqaiS3ojWPgjtGlaT5IcEl7RxCuaSHBFy4QfKaWcTZYKrhvpg2eXTl2sYm_WFyfZ7F1P94Apr30aj7RPx7EsB4f448=w1896-h1422-no&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h4&gt;Quinton and the Gold Honor Roll&lt;/h4&gt; &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Oh, and just because she is adorable, here is a picture of Mireille in her new soccer uniform.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Website</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/03/new-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Mar 2018 12:26:58 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/03/new-website/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I know, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t look any different. That&amp;rsquo;s sort of the beauty of this story. I&amp;rsquo;m going to warn you, if you normally come here for my amusing anecdotes about my kids, or perhaps to be regaled about my home improvement exploits, this story will probably seem somewhat dull. However, I owe this entry to the greater technological community, as there might be somebody, somewhere, that thinks even a little bit like me and are trying to do something similar to what I&amp;rsquo;m trying to do. And if they are a little like me, they will systematically hack their way through problems using Google, and maybe this article will show up and help them.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Next Renovation</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/02/the-next-renovation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2018 09:36:02 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/02/the-next-renovation/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s been awhile since we&amp;rsquo;ve done any major remodeling work to our house (yeah, right!), so it was time for us to embark on our next gigantic project. The thought was that we would do both upstairs bathrooms at more or less the same time. The kid&amp;rsquo;s bathroom was supposed to be &amp;ldquo;easy&amp;rdquo; since I was going to leave the shower pretty much alone, just update the fixtures and the shower head, but concentrate mostly on the floor, toilet, and vanity. Our master bathroom was going to be a little more involved, new toilet, floor, and entirely new shower save for the shower pan. Well, plans changed&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christmas with the Tibbetts</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/02/christmas-with-the-tibbetts/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2018 10:50:09 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/02/christmas-with-the-tibbetts/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We live in Colorado. Our families, by and large, still dwell in places throughout the Midwest. Year after year this generates some degree of conflict, particularly when it comes time for celebrating the holidays. For this holiday season, we celebrated Grady Christmas on the ever traditional weekend of the first weekend of November. For the Tibbett holiday celebration, then, we coordinated an early January celebration. Actually, it was planned to coincide with my 45th birthday, because who wouldn&amp;rsquo;t want to travel to the frigid midwest to stay in remote, rural Wisconsin with his in-laws on their 45th birthday!!!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elf on the Shelf</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/12/elf-on-the-shelf/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2017 18:45:01 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/12/elf-on-the-shelf/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;There are many traditions that I&amp;rsquo;ve learned of since leaving the nest that my family was either ignorant to or just didn&amp;rsquo;t celebrate. One happened this morning, and has for the last 21 years of my marriage, yet I still forget to celebrate it - St. Nicholas&amp;rsquo;s Day. Jenny celebrated it year after year, yet I did not, so even though I&amp;rsquo;ve now been in my adult life much longer than I was ever in my parents&amp;rsquo; home, I still forget&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thanksgiving 2017</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/12/thanksgiving-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2017 12:16:24 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/12/thanksgiving-2017/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Thanksgiving is literally my favorite holiday. I just love getting together with family and friends, cooking a delicious meal, eating said meal, just hanging out and napping with people. I think even more than Christmas, it is the most relaxing holiday out there!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This year, having already done the &amp;ldquo;Grady Christmas&amp;rdquo; several weeks earlier, our plan was to stay put for Thanksgiving. Luckily there are others in the greater Denver metropolitan area that are also too far away to spend the day with family, so they became our extended family for Thanksgiving. On the menu was the traditional Thanksgiving faire, turkey, rolls, potatoes and gravy, stuffing, scalloped corn, pie (lots of pie), macaronni and cheese, gouda roll-ups, bean dip - you know, the traditional stuff! One of the reasons I like hosting so much is because I get to keep the leftovers, so I planned ahead. For the nine people that were at our meal we cooked 28 pounds of turkey!!!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Epic of the Flex</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/11/the-epic-of-the-flex/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2017 16:16:59 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/11/the-epic-of-the-flex/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;If you are familiar with our family, you know that we don&amp;rsquo;t really place a high value on vehicles. Basically whatever can get us from point A to point B reliably and without a whole lot of money in maintenance will do. In our particular family, we now have three vehicles, two Chevy Malibu&amp;rsquo;s that have a combined age approaching 30 years, and a &amp;ldquo;new&amp;rdquo; Ford Flex that is only 3 years old, but is approaching 100,000 miles itself. The Flex is supposed to be our &amp;ldquo;reliable&amp;rdquo; car.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suburban Archeologist</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/10/suburban-archeologist/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2017 08:42:44 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/10/suburban-archeologist/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Not an interesting update for those that are looking for news on my adorable and smart children, but something I&amp;rsquo;m documenting for posterity, and for my own purposes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We do quite a lot of home improvement. I&amp;rsquo;ve always been the type that likes to try something on my own before calling a professional in to do it correctly and quickly. Last weekend, a couple of long running &amp;ldquo;curiosity&amp;rdquo; type projects finally had some major movement, which, since I&amp;rsquo;m kind of a dork, made me pretty excited!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A perfect parent&#39;s weekend...</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/09/a-perfect-parents-weekend.../</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2017 09:38:40 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/09/a-perfect-parents-weekend.../</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This was a couple of weeks ago now, so it&amp;rsquo;s not as fresh in my mind as it was when it happened, but the event was important enough that I think it warrants documentation. You see, this was Mireille&amp;rsquo;s fifth birthday, her second in the United States.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For the weeks leading up to September 9, Mireille has been asking on a regular basis about her birthday party. She really wanted to have a party, with a bounce castle, and a cake, and presents! Hopefully she wasn&amp;rsquo;t disappointed. The only thing we didn&amp;rsquo;t really have was a cake, but we had a whole bunch of cupcakes! She didn&amp;rsquo;t seem too impressed, though, because it wasn&amp;rsquo;t a cake!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mireille Funnies</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/09/mireille-funnies/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 11:52:46 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/09/mireille-funnies/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Jenny was talking to Mireille on Sunday about things that girls talk about. I wasn&amp;rsquo;t privvy to the details of the entire conversation, because that wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be appropriate - I&amp;rsquo;m a boy. One little nugget Jenny shared with me was when Mireille admitted to her, &amp;ldquo;I wish I was a unicorn. But I&amp;rsquo;m just Mireille&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Then, yesterday, our little Unicorn proved she listens and absorbs way more than she ever lets on. Since moving to Colorado we&amp;rsquo;ve had some difficulty adapting to the local colloqualisms. It&amp;rsquo;s not too different here, but the differences that do exist between here and Milwaukee are hard, particularly for adults. The one that seems most stubborn for Jenny and I is calling the last meal of the day dinner (CO) instead of supper (WI). Any time Jenny will say it in front of Maylee, she will make a big deal of correcting her. Just yesterday, Jenny and I were sitting on our newly completed deck with Mireille and discussing what we should do for supper. Mireille looked seriously at Jenny and said quietly, &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s dinner mom, not supper.&amp;rdquo; Maylee is so proud, and now I am double thinking anything I say in front of her.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colorado Adventure Series - Snow Mountain Ranch Day 4</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/08/colorado-adventure-series-snow-mountain-ranch-day-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2017 17:52:46 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/08/colorado-adventure-series-snow-mountain-ranch-day-4/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;day-4&#34;&gt;Day 4&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Today started out much the same as the last. I got up &amp;ldquo;early&amp;rdquo; and headed out for a quick run around the campus. The main difference today was that Ethan decided he would come with me! He&amp;rsquo;s training for soccer and was supposed to run 5 miles over the weekend. He decided that 3.2 at 9000 feet was a rough equivalent of 5 at 5280, which I&amp;rsquo;m inclined to agree with.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colorado Adventure Series - Snow Mountain Ranch Day 3</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/08/colorado-adventure-series-snow-mountain-ranch-day-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2017 16:52:46 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/08/colorado-adventure-series-snow-mountain-ranch-day-3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;day-3&#34;&gt;Day 3&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Day three started out later than day 2. With nothing really pushing us out of bed, the room slept in. I got up &amp;ldquo;early&amp;rdquo; around 7:00 or so and circumnavigated the property on a &amp;ldquo;run&amp;rdquo; of sorts. Not sure you can really call it a run. Jogging occured, but a lot of walking also occurred. It was very brisk to start the day, at only 36 degF, and a bit of fog made it a little spooky, but it was good to get out and about and get the blood pumping earlyish. As part of my run I found the Heritage farm, a turn of the century farm that has been preserved and now they hold horse riding breakfasts there. There are also some llamas there. The nicest part was the view from Piano Prairie, though. Framed just right, you could almost imagine what it might look like if there were no roads or dwellings of any kind.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colorado Adventure Series - Snow Mountain Ranch Day 2</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/08/colorado-adventure-series-snow-mountain-ranch-day-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2017 21:52:46 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/08/colorado-adventure-series-snow-mountain-ranch-day-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;day-2&#34;&gt;Day 2&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our first full day of vacation! Today is exciting because it will be most of our first time whitewater rafting. We were to be in Kremmling, about 45 miles away, by 8:30 for our half day whitewater rafting adventure. So we set an alarm for 6:30, which was fine with everybody considering we were all in bed &lt;strong&gt;early&lt;/strong&gt; the night before, got dressed, had breakfast at the cafeteria, and headed west on 40 to the bustling metropolis of Kremmling via Granby. Fortunately for Jenny, we quickly passed a Starbucks at a City Market in Granby so she was able to feed her addiction while in deep rural Colorado.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colorado Adventure Series - Snow Mountain Ranch Day 1</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/08/colorado-adventure-series-snow-mountain-ranch-day-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2017 20:52:46 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/08/colorado-adventure-series-snow-mountain-ranch-day-1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;prelude&#34;&gt;Prelude&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When we first moved to Colorado two years ago, we made a point of being &amp;ldquo;tourists in our own state.&amp;rdquo; It seems so often that we live somewhere and never really get to experience it like somebody who visits. Life always seems to catch up with us. Lord Soccer demands attention, work, school, the house&amp;hellip; It&amp;rsquo;s a never ending cycle of demands on our time. So we&amp;rsquo;ve tried to keep it more fresh here in Colorado, since there is so much to see out here (despite there not being any measurable amount of recreational water anywhere out here).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Logitech K810 Reset</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/07/logitech-k810-reset/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2017 08:26:10 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/07/logitech-k810-reset/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I have been using the same external keyboard for my last three Macs, an excellent little Bluetooth keyboard from Logitech called the &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.logitech.com/en-us/product/bluetooth-illuminated-keyboard-k810&#34;&gt;Logitech K810&lt;/a&gt;. It&amp;rsquo;s meant to be a keyboard for a Windows machine, but it works perfectly well for my Mac as well as my various iDevices.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This morning when I came in to start working for the day, I found the keyboard had lost its mind! None of the keys worked properly. When I&amp;rsquo;d press Alt (which I have mapped to Command), it would turn the volume up. If I tried the Alt on the right side of the space bar, it would bring up the Print dialog. Things just weren&amp;rsquo;t quite right.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Driver Out There</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/06/new-driver-out-there/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2017 14:52:46 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/06/new-driver-out-there/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As of Monday, June 26, the world has a new driver. Ethan passed his driver&amp;rsquo;s test last Friday and made it official with the DMV (and our insurance agent) on Monday. It was actually a nice thing today. It&amp;rsquo;s Bike to Work day here in Denver, so I rode my bike in. About 2 miles from home, one of my tires popped, and I didn&amp;rsquo;t have a repair kit with me. It was 7:00, but since he now has a license, I was able to save a marriage by having the 16 year old come and pick me up so I could repair the tire and continue on to work. Already that insurance money is paying dividends!!!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summer is here!</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/06/summer-is-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 14:52:46 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/06/summer-is-here/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Summer is finally upon us. Last week was a full week without school, except for Mireille, but that&amp;rsquo;s daycare - even though she calls it school. The temperatures as of last Thursday definitely represented a shift into the ungodly hot area, though in Denver, if you can find shade, you are in good shape since the humidity is very comfortable. As a family we are definitely settling in more and more as the years have gone by.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mireille&#39;s English Progression</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/05/mireilles-english-progression/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2017 15:18:41 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/05/mireilles-english-progression/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s been over a year, and Mireille continues to grow and develop. Outside of some difficulties in identifying colors (something I can&amp;rsquo;t really fault her here) and a current disinterest in letters or numbers, she&amp;rsquo;s developing quite on par with what I would expect. She does continue to have some interesting phrases, usages, and interactions from time to time that merit documentation.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Recently she has started using a phrase whenever people do something that she really doesn&amp;rsquo;t understand. Not that she doesn&amp;rsquo;t understand what they are saying or doing, but doesn&amp;rsquo;t understand why a person would do that in the first place! As you can imagine, this is something that happens a lot with her American family, particularly her dense father and brothers. The phrase she attributes to this is, &amp;ldquo;What your problem is?&amp;rdquo; The look on her face is impossible to properly document, but it&amp;rsquo;s pretty hilarious any time she does it - funny enough that it hasn&amp;rsquo;t started bothering me quite yet.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Happy Mother&#39;s Day</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/05/happy-mothers-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2017 11:04:40 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/05/happy-mothers-day/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Happy Mother&amp;rsquo;s Day to my kids&amp;rsquo; mom, and of course my wife, who luckily happen to be the same person! This year we celebrated by going to a brunch at one of our favorite places, Bull and Bush Brewpub! It&amp;rsquo;s a difficult thing to get all of our kids both out of the house and behaving in a public place, but for the most part they held it together through brunch.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bathroom Remodel</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/02/bathroom-remodel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2017 08:26:10 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/02/bathroom-remodel/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Our house was built in the 80s, 1982 to be exact. Many, if not most things have not really been touched since then. Sure, fresh paint has been applied to the walls and carpet occasionally replaced, but the &amp;ldquo;bones&amp;rdquo; of the house have remained unchanged for the last 35 years.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;That changed immediately when we moved in almost 2 years ago. It started with windows, moved to the kitchen (which is still awesome, btw), moved on to doors, and now has passed to the biggest thorn remaining on the first floor, the bathroom.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Potpourri</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/01/potpourri/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2017 17:02:48 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/01/potpourri/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As is typical now a days, I find myself delinquent in my posting. I blame my new job. Nothing more. Oh, and having three kids is hard. Not sure I&amp;rsquo;ve mentioned that. Still, they keep us on our toes, and I occasionally remember to write some of the remarkable things down that they do. The following is a small collection of the things I&amp;rsquo;ve remembered.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;mireille&#34;&gt;Mireille&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;on-language&#34;&gt;&amp;hellip;on language&amp;hellip;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Mireille&amp;rsquo;s pronoun usage continues to improve, though her favorite pronoun continues to be &amp;ldquo;him.&amp;rdquo; The possessive form of her version of the &amp;ldquo;super pronoun&amp;rdquo; is &lt;strong&gt;him&amp;rsquo;s&lt;/strong&gt;. I don&amp;rsquo;t know where she heard the song, but the other day she started singing an adorable rendition of Sir Mix-A-Lot&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Baby Got Back,&amp;rdquo; or at least the beginning of it. Her&amp;rsquo;s, however, went like this.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2016 - The Year in Review - First Trimester</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/12/2016-the-year-in-review-first-trimester/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2016 18:55:09 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/12/2016-the-year-in-review-first-trimester/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I can remember one year when we did the traditional &amp;ldquo;Holiday Letter.&amp;rdquo; It was the year that we were in the process of trying to adopt Quinton, so we were &amp;ldquo;marketing ourselves&amp;rdquo; to our family and friends that year. Looking back, it was a fun letter to do, even if it was not necessary from the salesman side of house. I thought it would be fun to condense 2016 into a bit of a letter to our family (thank you both of my readers) and so that future versions of ourselves might enjoy reading it as well. So, here it goes!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mireille&#39;s English - now with Pronouns!!!</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/12/mireilles-english-now-with-pronouns/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2016 20:47:29 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/12/mireilles-english-now-with-pronouns/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Mireille has been in the US for right around 8 months now, and she still has yet to stop amazing me with how quickly she is adjusting. It&amp;rsquo;s not only just the English, though that is remarkable, but everything else as well. I don&amp;rsquo;t think I can really explain it better than I can show it with the picture below which I believe encapsulates the completeness of Mireille&amp;rsquo;s Westernization.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/2B5AUc23X1rnygldAUI-kzhS2D8AhJQZ_CP8M5YQqQZWd4nZh-JeTZwJoSUJIYCaaoV6bstFzernyA=w1014-h1350-no&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h4&gt;Westernized Mireille&lt;/h4&gt; &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Beyond device usage and creature comforts, Mireille continues to pickup English at an alarming rate. She&amp;rsquo;s been playing around with pronouns lately. The other day, while in the same bathroom as is shown in the above picture, she said to me, &amp;ldquo;Ethan&amp;rsquo;s too big for this bathroom.&amp;rdquo; I prodded her to ask her why she thought he was too big, and she responded, &amp;ldquo;him&amp;rsquo;s butt&amp;rsquo;s too big.&amp;rdquo; Him is pretty much the pronoun for any person that is not herself. She still rarely uses &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;my&amp;rdquo; but instead opts for speaking of herself in the third person, but she has started referring to others in the shorthand &amp;ldquo;him,&amp;rdquo; so that&amp;rsquo;s progress!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The First Snow of the Year</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/11/the-first-snow-of-the-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2016 09:31:29 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/11/the-first-snow-of-the-year/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Last week it snowed in Denver for the first time this season. It&amp;rsquo;s a mixed bag out here for snow. People don&amp;rsquo;t really care for it in the city, like most places, but love when it happens in the mountains, where it is supposed to be. My kids certainly love it, at least the first snow.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Mireille has been saying &amp;ldquo;snow&amp;rsquo;s coming?&amp;rdquo; since about August when Jenny showed her some snow boots she could wear. When it finally snowed last week, I picked her up from school and the first thing she said was &amp;ldquo;it&amp;rsquo;s snowing!&amp;rdquo; As soon as we got home, she wormed her way into her snow pants, coat, boots, hat, and gloves and demanded that I come outside with her so she could play in the snow.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Bloggable Offense</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/11/a-bloggable-offense/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2016 09:22:02 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/11/a-bloggable-offense/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Quinton loves his iPad, and he loves video games. Those are his leisure time activities, which is a funny thing to say, leisure time for an 8 year old! What he really loves to do is to enjoy both of them at the same time, which is something we try to limit for various reasons. It also presents itself as an opportunity for us when dolling out discipline.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Last week, Quinton had some egregious issue for which he had to be punished. The worst thing we can do to him is to take away his iPad. Since this escalated, we had to not only take away his iPad, but also limit video games for the weekend. Because he is stubborn he still managed to get his iPad from time to time, so I took additional measures to actually take away his network access, which I can do from the wireless router. This was effective, for a time&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>October 2016 - Big Update!</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/10/october-2016-big-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2016 19:39:06 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/10/october-2016-big-update/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s October! October has been a busy month, but what month hasn&amp;rsquo;t been, really. So it&amp;rsquo;s been awhile since there&amp;rsquo;s been an update of much substance. So, while my family answers the door to greet and treat Halloween visitors in full costume, I thought I would take a few minutes (or 60) and update the world on the goings on in the Grady Household.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;adoption---complete&#34;&gt;Adoption - Complete&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;rsquo;t have to restate how much work and waiting it&amp;rsquo;s been to complete this, our second adoption. It&amp;rsquo;s been long. This past Friday, though, we hit a big milestone. Mireille had her day in court, and she is now officially adopted in the United States, meaning she if officially a Grady! I wish that meant we were all done! But alas, this is yet another milestone. It marks our ability to complete more paperwork, and pay out more money for interesting new bureaucratic processes. But, it is a reason to celebrate, at least for the fact that this part of the process has come to a close.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mireille the Magician</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/10/mireille-the-magician/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2016 20:34:27 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/10/mireille-the-magician/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Quick one today. I need to document this, because it cracks me up. Lately Mireille has been doing magic tricks. Yes, you read that correctly - my four year old knows how to do magic tricks. Well, she knows a single trick, but she&amp;rsquo;s OK at it, and is working at it and trying to perfect it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;What she does is she takes an item and puts it in her hand. Then she asks you to pick which hand it is in. When you do, she shows you, and typically it is in that hand. Then she will try to distract you while she puts the object in her pocket. Then the routine starts over - pick a hand&amp;hellip; This time she&amp;rsquo;ll open both, and lo and behold, it&amp;rsquo;s gone. She&amp;rsquo;ll even proclaim, &amp;ldquo;It gone!&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quick Updates</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/10/quick-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2016 10:18:11 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/10/quick-updates/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;After five days of adult vacation in New Orleans, Jenny and I were happy to be back with our kids, and probably a bit surprised that five days wasn&amp;rsquo;t quite enough to really decompress! Things went back to normal very quickly.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Mirielle gas been constantly about three things - now, trick or treating, and the party that she was going to yesterday. The snow things is pretty funny. I seem to remember her not liking it very much when it showed up last spring, but just about every day she will ask us, very seriously, &amp;ldquo;snow coming?&amp;rdquo; I think she mainly wants to wear her snow boots that she found in her closet. Having a girl is weird!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mireille&#39;s Birthday!</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/09/mireilles-birthday/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2016 08:39:35 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/09/mireilles-birthday/</guid>
      <description>&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/e-j3FvpALopCYntwuaiyc7wa4_Qm-mfhdj7qBx7BAAlLlglMH3tfmX92zOXM_ulob2HionFUDqtRyw=w1014-h1350-no&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h4&gt;Mireille on her Fourth Birthday&lt;/h4&gt; &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our little girl turned four!!! This was a pretty special birthday for us. It&amp;rsquo;s the first one we got to celebrate with her! We have sent her gifts for each birthday in the Congo, but I&amp;rsquo;m pretty sure she hated all of those gifts. It was a weird thing - it&amp;rsquo;s very expensive to send stuff to the Congo, so we would just send one of our agency&amp;rsquo;s lawyers money and ask them to purchase something local for her. Then they would give it to her and send us pictures. One year they got her this really creepy looking doll and she looked like she would rather play with mud than with that doll!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colorado Adventure Series - Crested Butte</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/08/colorado-adventure-series-crested-butte/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2016 21:38:05 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/08/colorado-adventure-series-crested-butte/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A couple of weeks ago, friends of ours from Wisconsin contacted us and asked if we wanted to spend some time with them in Crested Butte. They have a condo there that they were going to be visiting, and we decided it would be fun to check it out. I have to say, I&amp;rsquo;m glad we did.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Crested Butte is quite a long drive from our home. At about 4.5 hours, it&amp;rsquo;s by far the furthest we&amp;rsquo;ve traveled for this summer&amp;rsquo;s adventures, but we couldn&amp;rsquo;t pass up the opportunity to check it out. It was supposed to be a nice place with a good sized and under attended ski hill. So why not!??!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Theme!!!</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/08/new-theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2016 19:04:39 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/08/new-theme/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;You may have noticed something new when you browsed here today. No, I didn&amp;rsquo;t adopt another kid&amp;hellip; I didn&amp;rsquo;t have to shovel 12 inches of snow&amp;hellip; It&amp;rsquo;s a new theme for the website! I&amp;rsquo;m sure you are as excited as I am about the change&amp;hellip; Doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter - this is my blog, and I can put whatever I want here.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This theme is awhile in the making. I&amp;rsquo;ve been doing web development for probably 17 years (well, I&amp;rsquo;ve been pretending to do it for that long - much of that time has been dedicated to managing web developers, but let&amp;rsquo;s not split hairs), and in the time I&amp;rsquo;ve been doing it, it has changed mightily. In the early years, you had to do literally everything yourself. And in an environment that didn&amp;rsquo;t match up with many of the desktop or server environments (that being HTML/JavaScript/CSS), it wasn&amp;rsquo;t always pretty.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More English</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/08/more-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2016 09:19:33 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/08/more-english/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I was amused by these so I had to post them. Mireille is learning English really quickly. Not all is worthy of recording as most is mundane, but there are a few&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;She loves to eat! And she loves to try new food - but she doesn&amp;rsquo;t always like the food that she&amp;rsquo;s trying. When she happens to try something that she doesn&amp;rsquo;t like she says &amp;ldquo;I like this uh-uh.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Family Hikes</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/07/family-hikes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2016 21:04:51 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/07/family-hikes/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Last summer when we moved to CO, we weren&amp;rsquo;t very busy initially, so we took the opportunity to explore our great new state. This summer, after track has ended and we&amp;rsquo;ve buttoned up most of our backlog of home improvements, we have decided to do the same thing.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Two weekends ago we went to Frisco for the weekend with Maylee and Steve. While there we stayed at a hotel, did a little shopping, visited three breweries (yeah), but the main event was a 20 mile bike ride, 10 miles each way between Frisco and Breckenridge. It was really a lot of fun, and the kids did really well, particularly Quinton who biked it all under his own power and didn&amp;rsquo;t complain a single time! Mireille was biking in her own way behind my bike, even peddling (the wrong way) from time to time. It was a lot of fun, but we were all very tired when we were done.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethan Driving Lessons</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/07/ethan-driving-lessons/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2016 21:27:19 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/07/ethan-driving-lessons/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s fun having somebody to drive you around, I&amp;rsquo;m finding. Since getting his permit, Ethan has logged a little over 5 hours of driving of the 50 that he needs to log by June next year in order to obtain his driver&amp;rsquo;s license. When he started driving, and after seeing the number of hours he would have to drive, I told him that there were over 300 breweries in Colorado, and the way he was going to learn how to drive was to take me to as many of them as he could&amp;hellip; Last night he told me that it was time to drive, and that I should grab my Pub Pass and we would stop for a beer somewhere. Man, that kid knows how to convince me!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quinton&#39;s Last Track Meet</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/07/quintons-last-track-meet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2016 21:27:10 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/07/quintons-last-track-meet/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Quinton joined the Aurora Recreational Track Team this summer. We were excited about this particular activity because it would be something Quinton couldn&amp;rsquo;t just partially do. We find that, often times during soccer or basketball, Quinton is perfectly content to move at about half pace. He is bigger and faster than most of the kids he plays against in those sports, so if he plays about half way, he can still be competitive but not sweat too much. Not so much with track - there, he has to run his butt off to compete!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More English with Mireille</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/07/more-english-with-mireille/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2016 21:27:01 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/07/more-english-with-mireille/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s been nearly 5 months now, and Mireille has really amped up her mastery of the English language. We recently went on vacation with the whole family to Wisconsin, so I had the opportunity to spend a lot of focused time with her. As the week went on, I started to see how she is systematically adding new words to her vocabulary all the time. First, she will point at something and ask you what it is (she says &amp;ldquo;Ques at?&amp;rdquo; which means &amp;ldquo;what&amp;rsquo;s that?&amp;rdquo;). Then you will tell her the name for that thing. Then she will repeat the name, but with a question inflection at the end of the name, forcing you to then repeat yourself. Finally, she will repeat the word, this time with statement inflection. The word isn&amp;rsquo;t always locked in at this point, but you can see it settling in for remembering.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Life of a Single Father</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/06/life-of-a-single-father/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2016 21:43:24 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/06/life-of-a-single-father/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s 9:44 PM on Thursday evening. I&amp;rsquo;ve finally settled down to my computer and&#xA;a bomber of my local&amp;rsquo;s double IPA. It&amp;rsquo;s the first time today that I&amp;rsquo;ve been&#xA;able to sit without somebody demanding something or me having to be preparing&#xA;something for somebody. You see, Jenny has been traveling for work since Monday&#xA;morning, leaving me, a single father of three.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve been a single father in the past. There&amp;rsquo;s something much more complicated&#xA;about being a single father now-a-days, however. Not only is it three kids,&#xA;which even though we&amp;rsquo;ve added only one child, the apparent number of children&#xA;seems to have risen exponentially. No, it&amp;rsquo;s not &lt;em&gt;just&lt;/em&gt; the third child, but the&#xA;fact that the third child is a three year old black girl! Let me explain.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ACHC Camp and English</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/06/achc-camp-and-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2016 07:58:48 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/06/achc-camp-and-english/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Last weekend we had to opportunity to go to the African-Caribbean&#xA;Heritage Camp. It is one of a set of camps put on by an organization in town&#xA;here that focuses on transracially formed families, specifically formed through&#xA;adoption. Yeah, they have organizations for everything! We had been to the camp&#xA;once before, two years ago, and enjoyed it so much that we decided to move to&#xA;Denver!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Over the course of the two and a half days of camp we were all immersed with&#xA;people in a very similar situation to our family. There were many speakers&#xA;and round tables which were both thought provoking and frustrating (mainly&#xA;the round tables), but in the end it was a great experience for our family to&#xA;be around other families that look just like ours. That just doesn&amp;rsquo;t happen&#xA;very often!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Father-In-Law</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/05/my-father-in-law/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2016 10:33:43 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/05/my-father-in-law/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;just-for-context&#34;&gt;This post got lost in the draft folder. So I&amp;rsquo;m posting it about three weeks late.&#xA;Just for context&amp;hellip;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Last weekend, my father-in-law, Bruce Tom Tibbett, passed away. It was a difficult&#xA;thing to comprehend, somebody that we&amp;rsquo;ve been so close to for so long will no longer&#xA;be with us. I&amp;rsquo;m sure I heard it somewhere how Freud describes the death of a&#xA;parent - it reminds us of our mortality. It starts the clock on when we are likely&#xA;to follow. I think that is certainly true, but for Tom, I think it is something more&#xA;as well. He has left a hole that will not be easily filled again in many people&amp;rsquo;s&#xA;lives, my own being one of them.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quinton the Actor</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/05/quinton-the-actor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2016 14:15:12 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/05/quinton-the-actor/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;For some reason, Quinton has decided lately that he wants to be an actor. He feels&#xA;he could be rich, and feels that he&amp;rsquo;s every bit as good as the people he&amp;rsquo;s seen on&#xA;TV and movies.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Yesterday on our trip back from Colorado Springs where we were watching soccer,&#xA;Quinton was going into great detail about what would happen when he&amp;rsquo;s an actor. First&#xA;I told him that he&amp;rsquo;d probably need to hire an agent. He said fine, but when I told&#xA;him that he&amp;rsquo;d have to pay one, he changed his mind. Eventually he decided that he&#xA;could just have me be his agent. I&amp;rsquo;m sure he figures I have great Hollywood&#xA;connections and would make a great agent. Of course, he wouldn&amp;rsquo;t have to pay me&amp;hellip;&#xA;When confronted with the fact that I would still need to pay for things, he came up&#xA;with some clever thoughts. I could live with him, for one thing. Jenny and Mireille&#xA;would still live in our house, but he and I would live in his mansion. Then we could&#xA;have a Mustang to drive around in since we wouldn&amp;rsquo;t have anybody else to drive&#xA;around, and he doesn&amp;rsquo;t intend to have a girlfriend or anything. He did say we could&#xA;get a truck - you know, for long trips&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Happy 15th Birthday, Ethan!</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/05/happy-15th-birthday-ethan/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2016 07:42:46 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/05/happy-15th-birthday-ethan/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s not often that I blog about our oldest son, Ethan. He&amp;rsquo;s not cute and&#xA;little anymore. He doesn&amp;rsquo;t say stupid things innocently so that I can have&#xA;poignant teaching moments with him&amp;hellip; Well, he doesn&amp;rsquo;t do that as often, and&#xA;he would probably take exception to me announcing them to the world now that&#xA;he&amp;rsquo;s all social media savvy and all.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Ethan has grown into quite the young man. Though he is only 15, he has already&#xA;learned many of life&amp;rsquo;s most important lessons, mainly the ones about treating&#xA;others as you would want to be treated - he excels at that. He has adjusted&#xA;famously to having his life uprooted, moved to a new state, and started a&#xA;high school where the lunchroom staff is larger than the entire population of&#xA;his old school.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning English</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/05/learning-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2016 07:57:13 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/05/learning-english/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Mireille has been in the US for around 2 months now and by all accounts is doing&#xA;pretty well. One thing that we constantly worry about is whether she is picking&#xA;up English quickly enough. Of course we are on all these Facebook groups and&#xA;we constantly hear about how much English people&amp;rsquo;s kids are picking up and&#xA;Mireille has been a bit slow on that front. I tend to think many of those&#xA;people are embellishing their stories quite a bit, but whatever - she is a&#xA;strong willed girl and she&amp;rsquo;s going to speak Lingala, dammit!!!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mireille Quickies</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/04/mireille-quickies/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2016 08:30:03 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/04/mireille-quickies/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I have a couple of &amp;ldquo;novels&amp;rdquo; in the works. Sometimes I let those clog up the&#xA;works when I should be doing smaller, more frequent updates. So this is one&#xA;of those smaller, more frequent updates. I&amp;rsquo;m finding my available time much&#xA;harder to come by with the addition of the third child. I&amp;rsquo;m sure that will&#xA;normalize out at some point, right? Those with three or more kids, back me up&#xA;here!!!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Sh!tty Morning</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/03/a-shtty-morning/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2016 07:40:04 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/03/a-shtty-morning/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Mireille&amp;rsquo;s been home with us for two weeks today. Many of you are probably&#xA;looking for some post that goes through that in some detail. This is not that&#xA;post. I&amp;rsquo;m working up a larger post, but interestingly, going from two to three&#xA;kids, and having that new kid be 3.5 years old, well, it changes how you can&#xA;spend your time. Ah, material for another post. This post deals with an&#xA;acute familial incident that happened to involve the entire family in one way&#xA;or another&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two Days on the Hill</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/02/two-days-on-the-hill/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2016 10:15:09 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/02/two-days-on-the-hill/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;preamble&#34;&gt;Preamble&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I briefly considered titling this &amp;ldquo;Mr. Grady Goes to Washington,&amp;rdquo; but I didn&amp;rsquo;t&#xA;like it for a couple of reasons. First, I don&amp;rsquo;t really think of myself as&#xA;Mr. Grady. And more importantly, I have never really seen the movie, and I hate&#xA;giving false information.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is a story about a number of things&amp;hellip; Adoption, politics, travel, weather&amp;hellip;&#xA;Hold on to your seats, and grab some NoDoze. This might get boring!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>She&#39;s Coming Home!!!</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/02/shes-coming-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2016 07:59:33 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/02/shes-coming-home/</guid>
      <description>&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/8Cmk5RKPfdXpaITEv7XJyNfYnunG3NmosrbdGaL6hmNT8xmcfekDIwFpiTUXebs8netwE55Ia_lnrA=w960-h1280-no&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h4&gt;Riding to my Red Eye&lt;/h4&gt; &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/5aF5JNcVIg8S4rvaO79bFdIqBLGA_mYCLmNZe3qE_HhfIN0Yle6bJ_IQ_BaNU3Rt7DYd1Avu8uxjkA=w1830-h1372-no&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h4&gt;Dulles Airport&lt;/h4&gt; &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/LO3UXr1yK65hVk0Q7KT4ZkmBoFLyqGwVgfsN9TaPSxpoquee6pXACZhxRopLJo9ETWlIqcALK5XvMg=w1030-h1372-no&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h4&gt;Empty International Arrival Terminal&lt;/h4&gt; &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/I-TpkEc4M1Hcf9oRJUGd9E0AJ86Ok2jyM_jGiy-cn2oxIBcBfTVJ4pu6Du2sQExLK-0zVskY2sYxcw=w1830-h1372-no&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h4&gt;UA 951 from Brussels&lt;/h4&gt; &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/Zov87qb-27qil2rQQ-Bs8pcOE2rnyCz_lgO3s7MEa4KK8CtLCysnczJA5d8au9puQgczsIUvrt5ukA=w1030-h1372-no&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h4&gt;At at DGM, Ironic Lunch&lt;/h4&gt; &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/pULwNKpVhdF6v3e4MVWfMDR4LpmIS_vG712y3il8U98dPUp_pAZhM7mWODSD9cqxIUYDePngrWPGRQ=w750-h1334-no&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h4&gt;The Wait is Excruciating&lt;/h4&gt; &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/jvof0kJy-0WdJfXpVacQcv3Wad5_uGqSBjSqg-P0yZCiB949FdD47d-uw5yb7xWXwHjWSnhtKxitgw=w750-h1334-no&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h4&gt;The Plane has Landed!&lt;/h4&gt; &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/Oq_wZEZM9mUEzmD49xpEGgHsBAAZbUwMWqjnfEqxzXOBY8832uOsnT-gpPz9PcJgsT2IwbWkgQoJxw=w1030-h1372-no&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h4&gt;Busiest Time of Day&lt;/h4&gt; &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/zKDZBQ6_DyPykIbkGVJNqNaS9_GCQCqW_UA72WdY71xhPlUF4jlhLgfdYpzHR4pOgqu2ym6UQESxhg=w1030-h1372-no&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h4&gt;She&amp;#39;s Here!&lt;/h4&gt; &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/zQintpxRx8zj5NpvRDhAh0YUnfo1DR2586B3_hBFty7d10K8zCDrpsAANJ0jTL5sIX11Ou1qqfSaPw=w1030-h1372-no&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h4&gt;Confused?&lt;/h4&gt; &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/oDLo_MrcVdoQTTq2oN0mDOEKtjPmDcQcCwqx9DDMlM4sQboQKCkJlX6LY4rvUkq9Yk5vy88u5tYu-A=w960-h1280-no&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h4&gt;Proof - in the U.S.&lt;/h4&gt; &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/pmrnTNojliemaBuiEpFBycuntkbPIQ5QpDOVArbRS9WjIcLid1Fk7zHvlxnSPyWNxBLOElJsIYTf-Q=w1030-h1372-no&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h4&gt;Playing Dress-up&lt;/h4&gt; &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/v5plBg_Zj6namKB2EtbrBso03tHlqrF2v6nAbiaWebBi6LaVS0uV5AQYLh-CL7sDJ84URgqzzkuwKA=w1030-h1372-no&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h4&gt;And... Out.&lt;/h4&gt; &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/J2QYL2Va9P-TU_HqxF1a1Txbk0Pjh6UwJ2FUkjLrvaOC0mmvQAgToc87lvyxL4iqhEcWsP4ecm5I9w=w1830-h1372-no&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h4&gt;Playing with Mama&lt;/h4&gt; &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/mQXECZJiXoSzMQqp1qJGokFoswcbSSVCLg-Y_9qXsEmkJttXCW0xCXigQyAbSL7PcPMwnyA9RsJVjg=w1030-h1372-no&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h4&gt;Women, they be shoppin!&lt;/h4&gt; &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/hfMDCIc8_bLR7hh_qaZSLeMFkR0JVXYi6E3DMzPOGuA39cuAcWxcMAUaTMu5yN5Lsvkbhq0qDzfaKw=w1830-h1372-no&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h4&gt;Playing with Yaya&lt;/h4&gt; &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/kFLi3_pZq2O7j6fjv4eDbBYosc00XZ0WR5l318dTgPVfZhf23JO2YSrOfsK2WTheJj86YU4-gqr6wA=w1030-h1372-no&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h4&gt;Starting the Hair Restoration Project&lt;/h4&gt; &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Left on the red-eye on Saturday night.&#xA;Nothing open in the airport.&#xA;Arrived at Dulles at 4:00 AM.&#xA;Nothing open in the airport.&#xA;$25 cab ride to the hotel 7 miles away.&#xA;Couldn&amp;rsquo;t check me in.&#xA;I annoyed them into letting me check in early.&#xA;Napped for 2 hours.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Happy Birthday Quinton!</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/02/happy-birthday-quinton/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2016 08:26:05 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/02/happy-birthday-quinton/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;8 years ago yesterday, we were given a call that Quinton&amp;rsquo;s birth mother was&#xA;going into labor. By 10:30 AM on this morning, 8 years ago, Quinton was born!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s hard to believe that it&amp;rsquo;s been 8 years. Looking back on the pictures, so&#xA;much has happened. He has grown so much, made us laugh, made us cry, asked so&#xA;many important questions, and taught us things we never thought we even needed&#xA;to know. I don&amp;rsquo;t think he will ever know how lucky we are to have him as part&#xA;of our lives.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The &#34;Hack&#34; Font</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/02/the-hack-font/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2016 10:53:23 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/02/the-hack-font/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Sorry, no cute stories about Quinton and the funny things he says today.&#xA;No interesting tales about Ethan and his quest to become a driver one day&#xA;in the next year or so&amp;hellip; Today I thought I&amp;rsquo;d take an aside and post a public&#xA;service announcement on the &lt;a href=&#34;http://sourcefoundry.org/hack/&#34;&gt;&amp;ldquo;Hack&amp;rdquo; font&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Why do you care? You likely do not. However, if you&amp;rsquo;ve found this post and are&#xA;still reading, let me tell you why I like Hack.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>January Ski Weekend</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/01/january-ski-weekend/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2016 07:41:50 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/01/january-ski-weekend/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As a sort of late birthday present, a few of our Wisconsin friends came out and&#xA;enjoyed a ski weekend with us at Copper Mountain, the resort where we have our&#xA;season passes. Tim Z. was the first to arrive on Friday afternoon. After&#xA;dropping off the dog, then picking Tim up from the airport, we headed west&#xA;through typically terrible Denver traffic - perhaps leaving at 4:30 was a poor&#xA;decision. Nevertheless, we made it to our hotel by around 7:00 after only&#xA;having to stop once for snacks and toilets.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRC Update</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/01/drc-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2016 08:04:12 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/01/drc-update/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;So&amp;hellip; There are a couple of updates, but we&amp;rsquo;re still stuck.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The US sent a delegation of congressmen to the DRC to talk specifically about&#xA;this issue. As has become typical, the DRC responded with things that we want&#xA;to hear. I won&amp;rsquo;t go into details, but I wanted to document, for posterity,&#xA;the letter I wrote to my congressmen in Colorado. I&amp;rsquo;ve been interacting with&#xA;their offices for the past couple of months and have a fairly good rapport&#xA;going with my contacts.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Mission Viejo Elementary Football League</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/01/the-mission-viejo-elementary-football-league/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2016 08:08:47 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/01/the-mission-viejo-elementary-football-league/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m pretty sure I posted about Quinton&amp;rsquo;s recent obsession with Football in a&#xA;prior post or two. If not, let me just say that Quinton has fallen HARD for&#xA;football and all things about it. It&amp;rsquo;s to the point where he will actually put&#xA;down his iPad (gasp) and ask me to turn on a football game when he knows one&#xA;will be on. If you know Quinton, you know that is not something to take&#xA;lightly.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kids these days</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/12/kids-these-days/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2015 11:21:28 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/12/kids-these-days/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Most days are pretty much the same. I get up at 5:30, shower, get Ethan up at&#xA;6:00, make breakfast for us, then leave around 6:30 to get him to School. After&#xA;that I&amp;rsquo;m not sure what typically happens as Jenny just takes care of it. Well,&#xA;last week I had the opportunity to walk Quinton to school because Ethan had&#xA;final exams and would be getting done around the time Quinton would normally&#xA;be going to school.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>There, I fixed it - plumbing edition</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/12/there-i-fixed-it-plumbing-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2015 07:27:08 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/12/there-i-fixed-it-plumbing-edition/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;One of these days I will get around to posting the epic project that we&amp;rsquo;ve&#xA;undertaken of redoing our kitchen. It&amp;rsquo;s been about 4 months in the making and&#xA;we&amp;rsquo;re hitting the final stretch! Last week the countertops were installed&#xA;so we finally got our new sink installed. Unfortunately, the countertop guys&#xA;don&amp;rsquo;t do plumbing, so that&amp;rsquo;s my job!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I had budgeted three trips to the hardware store, and I was right on the&#xA;money! The problems I had to deal with in this particular plumbing experience&#xA;were as follows:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thanksgiving, Colorado Style</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/12/thanksgiving-colorado-style/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2015 07:44:26 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/12/thanksgiving-colorado-style/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Our first major holiday in Colorado is my favorite of all holidays, Thanksgiving!&#xA;While it&amp;rsquo;s difficult to not be able to spend it with family, we were able to&#xA;make good memories of it by spending it in the Mountains at a ski resort. Hopefully&#xA;this is something we will make a tradition out of, because it was a lot of fun!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We went up on Wednesday and left a little early in hopes of beating the traffic&#xA;into the mountains. One thing you will hear from people that live in Colorado is&#xA;that going into the mountains, while awesome, is severely compromised by the&#xA;traffic on I70. At only 2 lanes for a long ways, many, MANY resorts to&#xA;service by that road, and unpredictable weather, it can be tricky to navigate.&#xA;We were lucky and made it up in the basic standard, about 90 minutes from our&#xA;house (maybe a little more, but it was in that general timeframe).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Grady Farm</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/11/the-grady-farm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2015 09:37:32 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/11/the-grady-farm/</guid>
      <description>&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/2ssrnwpL8xPHeMbi6EuMg_ECKw_tJsw_5XF9aLkMUsIS-UE-14PU=w1448-h1048-no&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h4&gt;Grady Family Farm - circa 1980&lt;/h4&gt; &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The picture is of the farm I grew up on that is 13 miles north and west of&#xA;Marquette, Iowa- The present owners took down the barn, chicken house, granary,&#xA;and corn crib- but curiously left the outhouse that is south of the house.&#xA;The picture is looking to the west and the farm my mother grew up on is the one&#xA;in the distant west, just in viewing- you can not see the church and cemetery&#xA;that is less than on quarter of a mile to the right in the picture- St Pius V&#xA;Catholic Church, Cherry Mound where my Mom and Dad are buried and where I mowed&#xA;every summer for about six years- I knew every tombstone in the cemetery and&#xA;when someone wanted to know where their relative was buried, the priest would&#xA;contact me and I would show them. I had the documents where our family, the&#xA;Horans, (Mom&amp;rsquo;s mother&amp;rsquo;s maiden name) gave the land for the church and cemetery&#xA;in 1874 or 5- but gave them to one of my brothers who seemed to want frame it&#xA;and hang it on his wall somewhere.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Casa Bonita</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/11/casa-bonita/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2015 20:49:12 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/11/casa-bonita/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to a new section of the blog, the &lt;em&gt;Weekends&lt;/em&gt; section. These entries&#xA;will cover things that we do as a family on the weekends. From hikes to&#xA;restaurants to whatever else. Since we&amp;rsquo;re new to the area, most things we do&#xA;here are new to us!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;casa-bonita&#34;&gt;Casa Bonita&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Last weekend&amp;rsquo;s destination was &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.casabonitadenver.com/&#34;&gt;Casa Bonita&lt;/a&gt;,&#xA;&amp;ldquo;The Most Entertaining Restaurant In The World.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/XmkgSzdNfabljCplYIunK-G4Gxsd0kBWPyklGXSKD1bPknIIq0HA=w1028-h1370-no&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h4&gt;Casa Bonita&lt;/h4&gt; &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;That&amp;rsquo;s their tag line, anyway. We shall see.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bike Hangar Idea</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/11/bike-hangar-idea/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2015 20:02:33 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/11/bike-hangar-idea/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Thought I would put this out there as I had never thought of this before.&#xA;We needed to hang our bikes in the garage. I didn&amp;rsquo;t really want to spend too&#xA;much money on hardware, so we just got the cheap hooks that you can get at&#xA;Home Depot - they were like $1.50 each. I typically don&amp;rsquo;t like using those&#xA;hooks because it&amp;rsquo;s a pain to find studs to drill and put them into, and then&#xA;when you do, it rarely lines up with the thing you want to hang.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adoption Woes</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/11/adoption-woes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2015 10:22:35 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/11/adoption-woes/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;ve known us for any amount of time, you know that we are, and have been&#xA;in the process of adopting from the Democratic Republic of Congo for the past&#xA;3 years. It has been a long, LONG process.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;tldr&#34;&gt;TL;DR;&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Last month, the Congolese government has dashed our hopes of completing this&#xA;adoption in the near timeframe. It is questionable if we will ever be able&#xA;to complete it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quinton&#39;s Snowboard</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/11/quintons-snowboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Nov 2015 21:44:52 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/11/quintons-snowboard/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We are first year Coloradoans, so we are behaving like them. We purchased&#xA;season ski passes, even though it is next to impossible to get into the&#xA;mountains due to all the traffic. We are in the process of upgrading all of our&#xA;equipment because no Coloradoan would be caught dead with the 10 year old&#xA;skis that we have!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Since we are planning on going to the mountains for our first trip over&#xA;Thanksgiving, we needed to get some equipment for Quinton and Ethan. Luckily,&#xA;they bend over backwards in Colroado to hook your kids on the whole mountain&#xA;experience. So they have all sorts of deals on equipment. For Quinton, who&#xA;wants to snowboard, it costs $109 to purchase a bunch of used stuff for the year,&#xA;then you can sell it back to them next season for $55 and put that towards&#xA;a new setup. Great theory.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Kitchen Discovery</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/11/a-kitchen-discovery/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2015 20:55:58 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/11/a-kitchen-discovery/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re redoing our kitchen right now. I have a long post queued up for some time&#xA;in the near future to go through some of the experience and show pictures. It&amp;rsquo;s&#xA;been fun, but it&amp;rsquo;s also been interesting.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Last weekend we finally got to the point where we could take out our old&#xA;lower cabinets and replace them with the new ones. The plan was to demolish&#xA;on Saturday and install on Sunday. For the most part this went off without&#xA;a hitch.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quinton&#39;s Christmas List</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/11/quintons-christmas-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2015 08:38:04 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/11/quintons-christmas-list/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Jenny had Quinton write a letter to Santa. Since he was also typing a thank&#xA;you letter to his grandparents on my e-mail, he decided to e-mail his letter&#xA;to Santa this year. I came across it in my drafts folder and found it amusing.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;dear santa i want a ps vita a dirt bike a soccer ball a trampoline football&#xA;gear mostly a dirt bike and a ps vita and halo 5 and ps 4 and 100 dollars and&#xA;a golden retreiver.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Now With Comments</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/11/now-with-comments/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2015 10:12:59 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/11/now-with-comments/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;re here, great! I&amp;rsquo;m not sure how you found it because I haven&amp;rsquo;t yet&#xA;linked the old blog to this one, nor have I done any advertisement or anything&#xA;(I probably won&amp;rsquo;t ever advertise).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There will be a larger series on how the new blog was constructed and some of&#xA;the technical ins and outs, but I wanted to quickly mention that the blog&#xA;is soft-launched, and today I added the ability to comment using&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://disqus.com/&#34;&gt;Discus&lt;/a&gt;, a SaaS based commenting and discuussion&#xA;platform. Please test it out and contact me with any problems you see. It&amp;rsquo;s sort&#xA;of &amp;ldquo;in beta&amp;rdquo; right now (not Disqus, but my usage of it).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quinton and Fun With Words</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/11/quinton-and-fun-with-words/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2015 19:21:14 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/11/quinton-and-fun-with-words/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;New words for the dictionary:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;becept /bee * &amp;lsquo;cept/&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Origin - from what I can tell, a combination of except and besides. Perfectly&#xA;encapsulates the meaning of both in different situations.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Example: &amp;ldquo;Everyone is having fun becept me.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;w&amp;rsquo;bout /wuh * &amp;lsquo;bout/&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Origin - shortened version of &amp;ldquo;what about.&amp;rdquo; Not particularly interesting for&#xA;its meaning but rather it&amp;rsquo;s usage.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Example: &amp;ldquo;The moon doesn&amp;rsquo;t have it&amp;rsquo;s own light - it only reflects the sun&amp;rsquo;s&#xA;light.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>There, I Fixed It</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/10/there-i-fixed-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2015 21:34:14 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/10/there-i-fixed-it/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Quinton has really wanted a remote control airplane for quite some time. Uncle&#xA;Blaine bought him a remote control helicopter a little over a year ago that&#xA;he absolutely loved for the entirety of the 10 minutes before he lost it in&#xA;the trees. Over the years he&amp;rsquo;s amassed quite the aresnal of cheap, crappy&#xA;remote control things - cars, trucks, motorcycles - each one cheaper and&#xA;crappier than the last. So when he continually asked for an airplane, I continually&#xA;managed to push him off.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skype with Mireille</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/10/skype-with-mireille/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2015 09:53:21 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/10/skype-with-mireille/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We got to Skype with Mireille this morning. It&amp;rsquo;s always bittersweet talking&#xA;with her. On the one hand, you want to make sure you keep in touch so she at&#xA;least has some sort of connection, but on another hand it just sort of hurts&#xA;to talk with her. When we talk with her, we are reminded of the situation that&#xA;we&amp;rsquo;re in, whereas other times we can sort of ignore it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hide and Seek</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/10/hide-and-seek/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2015 09:52:05 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/10/hide-and-seek/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s hard to play Hide and Seek when you have a dog&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
