<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on The Hydrant</title>
    <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on The Hydrant</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Sep 2018 08:52:45 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Catching Up</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/09/miscellaneous-catching-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Sep 2018 08:52:45 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/09/miscellaneous-catching-up/</guid>
      <description>It’s been awhile on a couple of these, so I figured I should jot them down before time erodes them from my memory.
This first story has been getting good traction in my friend and colleague circles. Before I can tell the story, I need to tee it up a little bit. Quinton is obviously a black male being raised among “the whites.” From time to time that causes some conflict in him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Francisco - 2018 - Day 6</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/07/san-francisco-2018-day-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2018 20:18:26 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/07/san-francisco-2018-day-6/</guid>
      <description>Flying home is tough, but today was tougher than normal since our flight wasn&amp;rsquo;t until 8:30. I think I would almost prefer a midday flight. We theoretically had enough time to do some stuff, but we managed to accomplish all that we had set out to do in the prior 5 days. So it was going to be awkward. As I sit here, we were 3 hours early for our 8:30 PM flight to Denver, but it has been delayed by an hour, so we will be sitting here for some time!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Francisco - 2018 - Day 5</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/07/san-francisco-2018-day-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2018 20:18:22 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/07/san-francisco-2018-day-5/</guid>
      <description>Our penultimate day of vacation started out early-ish. Of course, we got out to Starbucks and had some donut holes from our new favorite donut shop in California, the creatively named &amp;ldquo;Jelly Donut,&amp;rdquo; where I can&amp;rsquo;t say I ever saw a jelly donut there&amp;hellip; I was a little nervous to be going to the wharf today because it was a weekend, so tourist traffic would be high. Our ultimate goal was to get to our whale watching tour by 3:00 which took off at the wharf, and the website gave instructions to places where you could park inexpensively for $50 a day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Francisco - 2018 - Day 4</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/07/san-francisco-2018-day-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2018 20:18:16 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/07/san-francisco-2018-day-4/</guid>
      <description>Day 4 - I finally was able to get up in time to hit the road for a run. While I&amp;rsquo;m quite out of shape, I was still able to cut 25 seconds per mile off of my new-normal running speed while in the oxygen rich California air! Almost enough to get me to go out and do it again on this trip&amp;hellip; Almost&amp;hellip;
Much like yesterday, today was about doing the things that Jenny and I had planned on doing on our last trip but were prevented from doing due to the wildfires in Wine Country.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Francisco - 2018 - Day 3</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/07/san-francisco-2018-day-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2018 22:16:20 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/07/san-francisco-2018-day-3/</guid>
      <description>Friday was all about Muir Woods. Jenny and I had planned to visit here when we came to the area last September but weren&amp;rsquo;t able to make it due to the wildfires at the time. We were lucky to have seen a sign that warned visitors that they needed a parking reservation prior to visiting. We had secured a noon parking reservation for the day, but we were a little early.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Francisco - 2018 - Day 2</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/07/san-francisco-2018-day-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2018 22:16:15 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/07/san-francisco-2018-day-2/</guid>
      <description>After some much needed sleep, we woke up fairly early-ish and took in the world famous Embassy Suites complimentary breakfast! Well, most of us did. Despite getting up in time, Ethan decided not to partake.
The first order of business, feed the addiction, off to the local Starbucks. Once that was out of the way, we were free to head downtown for a day in the city. Our first stop was Fisherman&amp;rsquo;s Wharf.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Francisco - 2018 - Day 1</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/07/san-francisco-2018-day-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 21:48:18 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/07/san-francisco-2018-day-1/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been traveling WAY too much lately. After a brief trip to Jacksonville, the boys and I went into the mountains last weekend, then I boarded a plane to Chicago on Monday only to return on Tuesday in anticipation of an early Wednesday departure to San Francisco. I&amp;rsquo;m happy I&amp;rsquo;m not sick!!! Can&amp;rsquo;t say the same for Quinton, however. Jenny called me on Monday evening to inform me that Quinton had been throwing up all day and into the evening.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018 Boy&#39;s Trip - Day 2</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/07/2018-boys-trip-day-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 20:50:03 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/07/2018-boys-trip-day-2/</guid>
      <description>Day 2 We started the day slowly, as any good boy&amp;rsquo;s trip would. Since we didn&amp;rsquo;t go to bed until later, we slept in until after 8:00. I sort of wanted to get going, so I got up and started cooking half of our 2 pounds of bacon and a dozen eggs. The smell was enough to wake Ethan up by 8:30, mainly because the apartment was so full of smoke that I think he started suffocating.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018 Boy&#39;s Trip</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/07/2018-boys-trip/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2018 20:29:30 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/07/2018-boys-trip/</guid>
      <description>Day 1 Here we sit at 521 Elm St. in historic Leadville, CO, our VRBO for the weekend. Ethan, Quinton, and I are doing our first &amp;ldquo;boy&amp;rsquo;s weekend.&amp;rdquo; It was hard leaving Jenny and Mireille behind, but we stayed the course and are going through with it.
The trip up here was rougher than expected. Traffic out of Denver to the mountains via I70 was somehow worse than it normally would be when we are coming up to ski, but we persevered.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Old Blog Reclaimed!</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/05/old-blog-reclaimed/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 14:45:58 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/05/old-blog-reclaimed/</guid>
      <description>I have a small project going on right now. I&amp;rsquo;ve downloaded my old blog from Blogspot and have started persisting it here, in a more controlled fashion - everything all in one place! Since I had over 180 posts on that blog, it will take some time to reclaim all of the old posts and reformat them to properly work here, but the work has begun. It is tedious work, involving some level of digital archaeology, but I think it is worthwhile and will make this blog much more portable in the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spring Break 2018 - Day Three</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/03/spring-break-2018-day-three/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Mar 2018 20:15:04 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/03/spring-break-2018-day-three/</guid>
      <description>Taos Our third day was dedicated to Taos. Having slept in a little, but not quite as much as the prior day, we had a little extra time to do some swimming in hopes of getting away from the crowds in the pool. We weren&amp;rsquo;t successful in avoiding crowds, but we did get about 45 minutes of swimming in before we left the hotel. Mireille, Quinton, and I played some hide and seek (it&amp;rsquo;s more fun than you would think).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spring Break 2018 - Day Two</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/03/spring-break-2018-day-two/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 21:34:29 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/03/spring-break-2018-day-two/</guid>
      <description>Los Alamos Thank goodness, today started out MUCH later than the prior one. Nobody really stirred until 9:00, giving Mireille a much needed 13 hours, and Quinton an even more needed 11.5. Of course, I was also happy to finally get 10 myself, though I was up several times in the night for the &amp;ldquo;old man pee.&amp;rdquo; While we all got ready, Jenny and Mireille went to get some coffee at the very convenient on presmises Starbucks in the lobby.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spring Break 2018 - Day One</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/03/spring-break-2018-day-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2018 21:00:53 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/03/spring-break-2018-day-one/</guid>
      <description>AM As we suspected, and as is typical, we were up way too early. Mireille woke up around 7:00 the first time, Quinton followed about 7:30. While Mireille was able to fall back to sleep for a bit, Quinton was screaming for food by 8:00, so we were up! We left Ethan to sleep while the rest of us went down to one of the dozen or so restaurants the hotel had to offer for a nice buffet breakfast.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spring Break 2018 - The Drive</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/03/spring-break-2018-the-drive/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 22:29:27 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/03/spring-break-2018-the-drive/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Are we going to the hotel tonight?&amp;rdquo; This is the question repeated at least nightly for the last two weeks by our youngest, Mireille. For some reason she just loves hotels! I think it has something to do with the swimming pools. Perhaps she just likes to travel! At any rate, it had been a constant anthem for the last several weeks - &amp;ldquo;are we going to the hotel?&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Honor Roll</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/03/honor-roll/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 12:42:11 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/03/honor-roll/</guid>
      <description>Last Wednesday, I was able to witness the St. Pius X 2nd Trimester Honor Roll ceremony, and my favorite middle child was among the honorees. Quinton achieved all A- or better in the last trimester. In fact, he got all A&amp;rsquo;s with the exception of one A- which he got in Art.
Congratulations, Quinton!!!
  Quinton and the Gold Honor Roll   Oh, and just because she is adorable, here is a picture of Mireille in her new soccer uniform.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Website</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/03/new-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Mar 2018 12:26:58 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/03/new-website/</guid>
      <description>I know, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t look any different. That&amp;rsquo;s sort of the beauty of this story. I&amp;rsquo;m going to warn you, if you normally come here for my amusing anecdotes about my kids, or perhaps to be regaled about my home improvement exploits, this story will probably seem somewhat dull. However, I owe this entry to the greater technological community, as there might be somebody, somewhere, that thinks even a little bit like me and are trying to do something similar to what I&amp;rsquo;m trying to do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Next Renovation</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/02/the-next-renovation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2018 09:36:02 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/02/the-next-renovation/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been awhile since we&amp;rsquo;ve done any major remodeling work to our house (yeah, right!), so it was time for us to embark on our next gigantic project. The thought was that we would do both upstairs bathrooms at more or less the same time. The kid&amp;rsquo;s bathroom was supposed to be &amp;ldquo;easy&amp;rdquo; since I was going to leave the shower pretty much alone, just update the fixtures and the shower head, but concentrate mostly on the floor, toilet, and vanity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas with the Tibbetts</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/02/christmas-with-the-tibbetts/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2018 10:50:09 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/02/christmas-with-the-tibbetts/</guid>
      <description>We live in Colorado. Our families, by and large, still dwell in places throughout the Midwest. Year after year this generates some degree of conflict, particularly when it comes time for celebrating the holidays. For this holiday season, we celebrated Grady Christmas on the ever traditional weekend of the first weekend of November. For the Tibbett holiday celebration, then, we coordinated an early January celebration. Actually, it was planned to coincide with my 45th birthday, because who wouldn&amp;rsquo;t want to travel to the frigid midwest to stay in remote, rural Wisconsin with his in-laws on their 45th birthday!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elf on the Shelf</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/12/elf-on-the-shelf/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2017 18:45:01 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/12/elf-on-the-shelf/</guid>
      <description>There are many traditions that I&amp;rsquo;ve learned of since leaving the nest that my family was either ignorant to or just didn&amp;rsquo;t celebrate. One happened this morning, and has for the last 21 years of my marriage, yet I still forget to celebrate it - St. Nicholas&amp;rsquo;s Day. Jenny celebrated it year after year, yet I did not, so even though I&amp;rsquo;ve now been in my adult life much longer than I was ever in my parents&amp;rsquo; home, I still forget&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thanksgiving 2017</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/12/thanksgiving-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2017 12:16:24 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/12/thanksgiving-2017/</guid>
      <description>Thanksgiving is literally my favorite holiday. I just love getting together with family and friends, cooking a delicious meal, eating said meal, just hanging out and napping with people. I think even more than Christmas, it is the most relaxing holiday out there!
This year, having already done the &amp;ldquo;Grady Christmas&amp;rdquo; several weeks earlier, our plan was to stay put for Thanksgiving. Luckily there are others in the greater Denver metropolitan area that are also too far away to spend the day with family, so they became our extended family for Thanksgiving.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Epic of the Flex</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/11/the-epic-of-the-flex/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2017 16:16:59 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/11/the-epic-of-the-flex/</guid>
      <description>If you are familiar with our family, you know that we don&amp;rsquo;t really place a high value on vehicles. Basically whatever can get us from point A to point B reliably and without a whole lot of money in maintenance will do. In our particular family, we now have three vehicles, two Chevy Malibu&amp;rsquo;s that have a combined age approaching 30 years, and a &amp;ldquo;new&amp;rdquo; Ford Flex that is only 3 years old, but is approaching 100,000 miles itself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Suburban Archeologist</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/10/suburban-archeologist/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2017 08:42:44 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/10/suburban-archeologist/</guid>
      <description>Not an interesting update for those that are looking for news on my adorable and smart children, but something I&amp;rsquo;m documenting for posterity, and for my own purposes.
We do quite a lot of home improvement. I&amp;rsquo;ve always been the type that likes to try something on my own before calling a professional in to do it correctly and quickly. Last weekend, a couple of long running &amp;ldquo;curiosity&amp;rdquo; type projects finally had some major movement, which, since I&amp;rsquo;m kind of a dork, made me pretty excited!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A perfect parent&#39;s weekend...</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/09/a-perfect-parents-weekend.../</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2017 09:38:40 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/09/a-perfect-parents-weekend.../</guid>
      <description>This was a couple of weeks ago now, so it&amp;rsquo;s not as fresh in my mind as it was when it happened, but the event was important enough that I think it warrants documentation. You see, this was Mireille&amp;rsquo;s fifth birthday, her second in the United States.
For the weeks leading up to September 9, Mireille has been asking on a regular basis about her birthday party. She really wanted to have a party, with a bounce castle, and a cake, and presents!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mireille Funnies</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/09/mireille-funnies/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 11:52:46 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/09/mireille-funnies/</guid>
      <description>Jenny was talking to Mireille on Sunday about things that girls talk about. I wasn&amp;rsquo;t privvy to the details of the entire conversation, because that wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be appropriate - I&amp;rsquo;m a boy. One little nugget Jenny shared with me was when Mireille admitted to her, &amp;ldquo;I wish I was a unicorn. But I&amp;rsquo;m just Mireille&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;
Then, yesterday, our little Unicorn proved she listens and absorbs way more than she ever lets on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Colorado Adventure Series - Snow Mountain Ranch Day 4</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/08/colorado-adventure-series-snow-mountain-ranch-day-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2017 17:52:46 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/08/colorado-adventure-series-snow-mountain-ranch-day-4/</guid>
      <description>Day 4 Today started out much the same as the last. I got up &amp;ldquo;early&amp;rdquo; and headed out for a quick run around the campus. The main difference today was that Ethan decided he would come with me! He&amp;rsquo;s training for soccer and was supposed to run 5 miles over the weekend. He decided that 3.2 at 9000 feet was a rough equivalent of 5 at 5280, which I&amp;rsquo;m inclined to agree with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Colorado Adventure Series - Snow Mountain Ranch Day 3</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/08/colorado-adventure-series-snow-mountain-ranch-day-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2017 16:52:46 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/08/colorado-adventure-series-snow-mountain-ranch-day-3/</guid>
      <description>Day 3 Day three started out later than day 2. With nothing really pushing us out of bed, the room slept in. I got up &amp;ldquo;early&amp;rdquo; around 7:00 or so and circumnavigated the property on a &amp;ldquo;run&amp;rdquo; of sorts. Not sure you can really call it a run. Jogging occured, but a lot of walking also occurred. It was very brisk to start the day, at only 36 degF, and a bit of fog made it a little spooky, but it was good to get out and about and get the blood pumping earlyish.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Colorado Adventure Series - Snow Mountain Ranch Day 2</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/08/colorado-adventure-series-snow-mountain-ranch-day-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2017 21:52:46 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/08/colorado-adventure-series-snow-mountain-ranch-day-2/</guid>
      <description>Day 2 Our first full day of vacation! Today is exciting because it will be most of our first time whitewater rafting. We were to be in Kremmling, about 45 miles away, by 8:30 for our half day whitewater rafting adventure. So we set an alarm for 6:30, which was fine with everybody considering we were all in bed early the night before, got dressed, had breakfast at the cafeteria, and headed west on 40 to the bustling metropolis of Kremmling via Granby.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Colorado Adventure Series - Snow Mountain Ranch Day 1</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/08/colorado-adventure-series-snow-mountain-ranch-day-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2017 20:52:46 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/08/colorado-adventure-series-snow-mountain-ranch-day-1/</guid>
      <description>Prelude When we first moved to Colorado two years ago, we made a point of being &amp;ldquo;tourists in our own state.&amp;rdquo; It seems so often that we live somewhere and never really get to experience it like somebody who visits. Life always seems to catch up with us. Lord Soccer demands attention, work, school, the house&amp;hellip; It&amp;rsquo;s a never ending cycle of demands on our time. So we&amp;rsquo;ve tried to keep it more fresh here in Colorado, since there is so much to see out here (despite there not being any measurable amount of recreational water anywhere out here).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Logitech K810 Reset</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/07/logitech-k810-reset/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2017 08:26:10 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/07/logitech-k810-reset/</guid>
      <description>I have been using the same external keyboard for my last three Macs, an excellent little Bluetooth keyboard from Logitech called the Logitech K810. It&amp;rsquo;s meant to be a keyboard for a Windows machine, but it works perfectly well for my Mac as well as my various iDevices.
This morning when I came in to start working for the day, I found the keyboard had lost its mind! None of the keys worked properly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Driver Out There</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/06/new-driver-out-there/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2017 14:52:46 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/06/new-driver-out-there/</guid>
      <description>As of Monday, June 26, the world has a new driver. Ethan passed his driver&amp;rsquo;s test last Friday and made it official with the DMV (and our insurance agent) on Monday. It was actually a nice thing today. It&amp;rsquo;s Bike to Work day here in Denver, so I rode my bike in. About 2 miles from home, one of my tires popped, and I didn&amp;rsquo;t have a repair kit with me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summer is here!</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/06/summer-is-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 14:52:46 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/06/summer-is-here/</guid>
      <description>Summer is finally upon us. Last week was a full week without school, except for Mireille, but that&amp;rsquo;s daycare - even though she calls it school. The temperatures as of last Thursday definitely represented a shift into the ungodly hot area, though in Denver, if you can find shade, you are in good shape since the humidity is very comfortable. As a family we are definitely settling in more and more as the years have gone by.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mireille&#39;s English Progression</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/05/mireilles-english-progression/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2017 15:18:41 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/05/mireilles-english-progression/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been over a year, and Mireille continues to grow and develop. Outside of some difficulties in identifying colors (something I can&amp;rsquo;t really fault her here) and a current disinterest in letters or numbers, she&amp;rsquo;s developing quite on par with what I would expect. She does continue to have some interesting phrases, usages, and interactions from time to time that merit documentation.
Recently she has started using a phrase whenever people do something that she really doesn&amp;rsquo;t understand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Mother&#39;s Day</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/05/happy-mothers-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2017 11:04:40 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/05/happy-mothers-day/</guid>
      <description>Happy Mother&amp;rsquo;s Day to my kids&amp;rsquo; mom, and of course my wife, who luckily happen to be the same person! This year we celebrated by going to a brunch at one of our favorite places, Bull and Bush Brewpub! It&amp;rsquo;s a difficult thing to get all of our kids both out of the house and behaving in a public place, but for the most part they held it together through brunch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bathroom Remodel</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/02/bathroom-remodel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2017 08:26:10 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/02/bathroom-remodel/</guid>
      <description>Our house was built in the 80s, 1982 to be exact. Many, if not most things have not really been touched since then. Sure, fresh paint has been applied to the walls and carpet occasionally replaced, but the &amp;ldquo;bones&amp;rdquo; of the house have remained unchanged for the last 35 years.
That changed immediately when we moved in almost 2 years ago. It started with windows, moved to the kitchen (which is still awesome, btw), moved on to doors, and now has passed to the biggest thorn remaining on the first floor, the bathroom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Potpourri</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/01/potpourri/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2017 17:02:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/01/potpourri/</guid>
      <description>As is typical now a days, I find myself delinquent in my posting. I blame my new job. Nothing more. Oh, and having three kids is hard. Not sure I&amp;rsquo;ve mentioned that. Still, they keep us on our toes, and I occasionally remember to write some of the remarkable things down that they do. The following is a small collection of the things I&amp;rsquo;ve remembered.
Mireille &amp;hellip;on language&amp;hellip; Mireille&amp;rsquo;s pronoun usage continues to improve, though her favorite pronoun continues to be &amp;ldquo;him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2016 - The Year in Review - First Trimester</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/12/2016-the-year-in-review-first-trimester/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2016 18:55:09 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/12/2016-the-year-in-review-first-trimester/</guid>
      <description>I can remember one year when we did the traditional &amp;ldquo;Holiday Letter.&amp;rdquo; It was the year that we were in the process of trying to adopt Quinton, so we were &amp;ldquo;marketing ourselves&amp;rdquo; to our family and friends that year. Looking back, it was a fun letter to do, even if it was not necessary from the salesman side of house. I thought it would be fun to condense 2016 into a bit of a letter to our family (thank you both of my readers) and so that future versions of ourselves might enjoy reading it as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mireille&#39;s English - now with Pronouns!!!</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/12/mireilles-english-now-with-pronouns/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2016 20:47:29 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/12/mireilles-english-now-with-pronouns/</guid>
      <description>Mireille has been in the US for right around 8 months now, and she still has yet to stop amazing me with how quickly she is adjusting. It&amp;rsquo;s not only just the English, though that is remarkable, but everything else as well. I don&amp;rsquo;t think I can really explain it better than I can show it with the picture below which I believe encapsulates the completeness of Mireille&amp;rsquo;s Westernization.
  Westernized Mireille   Beyond device usage and creature comforts, Mireille continues to pickup English at an alarming rate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The First Snow of the Year</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/11/the-first-snow-of-the-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2016 09:31:29 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/11/the-first-snow-of-the-year/</guid>
      <description>Last week it snowed in Denver for the first time this season. It&amp;rsquo;s a mixed bag out here for snow. People don&amp;rsquo;t really care for it in the city, like most places, but love when it happens in the mountains, where it is supposed to be. My kids certainly love it, at least the first snow.
Mireille has been saying &amp;ldquo;snow&amp;rsquo;s coming?&amp;rdquo; since about August when Jenny showed her some snow boots she could wear.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Bloggable Offense</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/11/a-bloggable-offense/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2016 09:22:02 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/11/a-bloggable-offense/</guid>
      <description>Quinton loves his iPad, and he loves video games. Those are his leisure time activities, which is a funny thing to say, leisure time for an 8 year old! What he really loves to do is to enjoy both of them at the same time, which is something we try to limit for various reasons. It also presents itself as an opportunity for us when dolling out discipline.
Last week, Quinton had some egregious issue for which he had to be punished.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>October 2016 - Big Update!</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/10/october-2016-big-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2016 19:39:06 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/10/october-2016-big-update/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s October! October has been a busy month, but what month hasn&amp;rsquo;t been, really. So it&amp;rsquo;s been awhile since there&amp;rsquo;s been an update of much substance. So, while my family answers the door to greet and treat Halloween visitors in full costume, I thought I would take a few minutes (or 60) and update the world on the goings on in the Grady Household.
Adoption - Complete I don&amp;rsquo;t have to restate how much work and waiting it&amp;rsquo;s been to complete this, our second adoption.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mireille the Magician</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/10/mireille-the-magician/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2016 20:34:27 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/10/mireille-the-magician/</guid>
      <description>Quick one today. I need to document this, because it cracks me up. Lately Mireille has been doing magic tricks. Yes, you read that correctly - my four year old knows how to do magic tricks. Well, she knows a single trick, but she&amp;rsquo;s OK at it, and is working at it and trying to perfect it.
What she does is she takes an item and puts it in her hand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick Updates</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/10/quick-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2016 10:18:11 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/10/quick-updates/</guid>
      <description>After five days of adult vacation in New Orleans, Jenny and I were happy to be back with our kids, and probably a bit surprised that five days wasn&amp;rsquo;t quite enough to really decompress! Things went back to normal very quickly.
Mirielle gas been constantly about three things - now, trick or treating, and the party that she was going to yesterday. The snow things is pretty funny. I seem to remember her not liking it very much when it showed up last spring, but just about every day she will ask us, very seriously, &amp;ldquo;snow coming?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mireille&#39;s Birthday!</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/09/mireilles-birthday/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2016 08:39:35 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/09/mireilles-birthday/</guid>
      <description>Mireille on her Fourth Birthday   Our little girl turned four!!! This was a pretty special birthday for us. It&amp;rsquo;s the first one we got to celebrate with her! We have sent her gifts for each birthday in the Congo, but I&amp;rsquo;m pretty sure she hated all of those gifts. It was a weird thing - it&amp;rsquo;s very expensive to send stuff to the Congo, so we would just send one of our agency&amp;rsquo;s lawyers money and ask them to purchase something local for her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Colorado Adventure Series - Crested Butte</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/08/colorado-adventure-series-crested-butte/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2016 21:38:05 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/08/colorado-adventure-series-crested-butte/</guid>
      <description>A couple of weeks ago, friends of ours from Wisconsin contacted us and asked if we wanted to spend some time with them in Crested Butte. They have a condo there that they were going to be visiting, and we decided it would be fun to check it out. I have to say, I&amp;rsquo;m glad we did.
Crested Butte is quite a long drive from our home. At about 4.5 hours, it&amp;rsquo;s by far the furthest we&amp;rsquo;ve traveled for this summer&amp;rsquo;s adventures, but we couldn&amp;rsquo;t pass up the opportunity to check it out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Theme!!!</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/08/new-theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2016 19:04:39 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/08/new-theme/</guid>
      <description>You may have noticed something new when you browsed here today. No, I didn&amp;rsquo;t adopt another kid&amp;hellip; I didn&amp;rsquo;t have to shovel 12 inches of snow&amp;hellip; It&amp;rsquo;s a new theme for the website! I&amp;rsquo;m sure you are as excited as I am about the change&amp;hellip; Doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter - this is my blog, and I can put whatever I want here.
This theme is awhile in the making. I&amp;rsquo;ve been doing web development for probably 17 years (well, I&amp;rsquo;ve been pretending to do it for that long - much of that time has been dedicated to managing web developers, but let&amp;rsquo;s not split hairs), and in the time I&amp;rsquo;ve been doing it, it has changed mightily.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More English</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/08/more-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2016 09:19:33 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/08/more-english/</guid>
      <description>I was amused by these so I had to post them. Mireille is learning English really quickly. Not all is worthy of recording as most is mundane, but there are a few&amp;hellip;
She loves to eat! And she loves to try new food - but she doesn&amp;rsquo;t always like the food that she&amp;rsquo;s trying. When she happens to try something that she doesn&amp;rsquo;t like she says &amp;ldquo;I like this uh-uh.&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Family Hikes</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/07/family-hikes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2016 21:04:51 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/07/family-hikes/</guid>
      <description>Last summer when we moved to CO, we weren&amp;rsquo;t very busy initially, so we took the opportunity to explore our great new state. This summer, after track has ended and we&amp;rsquo;ve buttoned up most of our backlog of home improvements, we have decided to do the same thing.
Two weekends ago we went to Frisco for the weekend with Maylee and Steve. While there we stayed at a hotel, did a little shopping, visited three breweries (yeah), but the main event was a 20 mile bike ride, 10 miles each way between Frisco and Breckenridge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ethan Driving Lessons</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/07/ethan-driving-lessons/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2016 21:27:19 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/07/ethan-driving-lessons/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s fun having somebody to drive you around, I&amp;rsquo;m finding. Since getting his permit, Ethan has logged a little over 5 hours of driving of the 50 that he needs to log by June next year in order to obtain his driver&amp;rsquo;s license. When he started driving, and after seeing the number of hours he would have to drive, I told him that there were over 300 breweries in Colorado, and the way he was going to learn how to drive was to take me to as many of them as he could&amp;hellip; Last night he told me that it was time to drive, and that I should grab my Pub Pass and we would stop for a beer somewhere.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quinton&#39;s Last Track Meet</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/07/quintons-last-track-meet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2016 21:27:10 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/07/quintons-last-track-meet/</guid>
      <description>Quinton joined the Aurora Recreational Track Team this summer. We were excited about this particular activity because it would be something Quinton couldn&amp;rsquo;t just partially do. We find that, often times during soccer or basketball, Quinton is perfectly content to move at about half pace. He is bigger and faster than most of the kids he plays against in those sports, so if he plays about half way, he can still be competitive but not sweat too much.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More English with Mireille</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/07/more-english-with-mireille/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2016 21:27:01 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/07/more-english-with-mireille/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been nearly 5 months now, and Mireille has really amped up her mastery of the English language. We recently went on vacation with the whole family to Wisconsin, so I had the opportunity to spend a lot of focused time with her. As the week went on, I started to see how she is systematically adding new words to her vocabulary all the time. First, she will point at something and ask you what it is (she says &amp;ldquo;Ques at?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life of a Single Father</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/06/life-of-a-single-father/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2016 21:43:24 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/06/life-of-a-single-father/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s 9:44 PM on Thursday evening. I&amp;rsquo;ve finally settled down to my computer and a bomber of my local&amp;rsquo;s double IPA. It&amp;rsquo;s the first time today that I&amp;rsquo;ve been able to sit without somebody demanding something or me having to be preparing something for somebody. You see, Jenny has been traveling for work since Monday morning, leaving me, a single father of three.
I&amp;rsquo;ve been a single father in the past.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ACHC Camp and English</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/06/achc-camp-and-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2016 07:58:48 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/06/achc-camp-and-english/</guid>
      <description>Last weekend we had to opportunity to go to the African-Caribbean Heritage Camp. It is one of a set of camps put on by an organization in town here that focuses on transracially formed families, specifically formed through adoption. Yeah, they have organizations for everything! We had been to the camp once before, two years ago, and enjoyed it so much that we decided to move to Denver!
Over the course of the two and a half days of camp we were all immersed with people in a very similar situation to our family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Father-In-Law</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/05/my-father-in-law/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2016 10:33:43 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/05/my-father-in-law/</guid>
      <description>This post got lost in the draft folder. So I&amp;rsquo;m posting it about three weeks late.
Just for context&amp;hellip; Last weekend, my father-in-law, Bruce Tom Tibbett, passed away. It was a difficult thing to comprehend, somebody that we&amp;rsquo;ve been so close to for so long will no longer be with us. I&amp;rsquo;m sure I heard it somewhere how Freud describes the death of a parent - it reminds us of our mortality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quinton the Actor</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/05/quinton-the-actor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2016 14:15:12 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/05/quinton-the-actor/</guid>
      <description>For some reason, Quinton has decided lately that he wants to be an actor. He feels he could be rich, and feels that he&amp;rsquo;s every bit as good as the people he&amp;rsquo;s seen on TV and movies.
Yesterday on our trip back from Colorado Springs where we were watching soccer, Quinton was going into great detail about what would happen when he&amp;rsquo;s an actor. First I told him that he&amp;rsquo;d probably need to hire an agent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy 15th Birthday, Ethan!</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/05/happy-15th-birthday-ethan/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2016 07:42:46 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/05/happy-15th-birthday-ethan/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s not often that I blog about our oldest son, Ethan. He&amp;rsquo;s not cute and little anymore. He doesn&amp;rsquo;t say stupid things innocently so that I can have poignant teaching moments with him&amp;hellip; Well, he doesn&amp;rsquo;t do that as often, and he would probably take exception to me announcing them to the world now that he&amp;rsquo;s all social media savvy and all.
Ethan has grown into quite the young man. Though he is only 15, he has already learned many of life&amp;rsquo;s most important lessons, mainly the ones about treating others as you would want to be treated - he excels at that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning English</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/05/learning-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2016 07:57:13 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/05/learning-english/</guid>
      <description>Mireille has been in the US for around 2 months now and by all accounts is doing pretty well. One thing that we constantly worry about is whether she is picking up English quickly enough. Of course we are on all these Facebook groups and we constantly hear about how much English people&amp;rsquo;s kids are picking up and Mireille has been a bit slow on that front. I tend to think many of those people are embellishing their stories quite a bit, but whatever - she is a strong willed girl and she&amp;rsquo;s going to speak Lingala, dammit!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mireille Quickies</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/04/mireille-quickies/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2016 08:30:03 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/04/mireille-quickies/</guid>
      <description>I have a couple of &amp;ldquo;novels&amp;rdquo; in the works. Sometimes I let those clog up the works when I should be doing smaller, more frequent updates. So this is one of those smaller, more frequent updates. I&amp;rsquo;m finding my available time much harder to come by with the addition of the third child. I&amp;rsquo;m sure that will normalize out at some point, right? Those with three or more kids, back me up here!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Sh!tty Morning</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/03/a-shtty-morning/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2016 07:40:04 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/03/a-shtty-morning/</guid>
      <description>Mireille&amp;rsquo;s been home with us for two weeks today. Many of you are probably looking for some post that goes through that in some detail. This is not that post. I&amp;rsquo;m working up a larger post, but interestingly, going from two to three kids, and having that new kid be 3.5 years old, well, it changes how you can spend your time. Ah, material for another post. This post deals with an acute familial incident that happened to involve the entire family in one way or another&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two Days on the Hill</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/02/two-days-on-the-hill/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2016 10:15:09 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/02/two-days-on-the-hill/</guid>
      <description>Preamble I briefly considered titling this &amp;ldquo;Mr. Grady Goes to Washington,&amp;rdquo; but I didn&amp;rsquo;t like it for a couple of reasons. First, I don&amp;rsquo;t really think of myself as Mr. Grady. And more importantly, I have never really seen the movie, and I hate giving false information.
This is a story about a number of things&amp;hellip; Adoption, politics, travel, weather&amp;hellip; Hold on to your seats, and grab some NoDoze. This might get boring!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>She&#39;s Coming Home!!!</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/02/shes-coming-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2016 07:59:33 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/02/shes-coming-home/</guid>
      <description>Riding to my Red Eye     Dulles Airport     Empty International Arrival Terminal     UA 951 from Brussels     At at DGM, Ironic Lunch     The Wait is Excruciating     The Plane has Landed!     Busiest Time of Day     She&amp;#39;s Here!     Confused?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Birthday Quinton!</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/02/happy-birthday-quinton/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2016 08:26:05 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/02/happy-birthday-quinton/</guid>
      <description>8 years ago yesterday, we were given a call that Quinton&amp;rsquo;s birth mother was going into labor. By 10:30 AM on this morning, 8 years ago, Quinton was born!
It&amp;rsquo;s hard to believe that it&amp;rsquo;s been 8 years. Looking back on the pictures, so much has happened. He has grown so much, made us laugh, made us cry, asked so many important questions, and taught us things we never thought we even needed to know.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The &#34;Hack&#34; Font</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/02/the-hack-font/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2016 10:53:23 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/02/the-hack-font/</guid>
      <description>Sorry, no cute stories about Quinton and the funny things he says today. No interesting tales about Ethan and his quest to become a driver one day in the next year or so&amp;hellip; Today I thought I&amp;rsquo;d take an aside and post a public service announcement on the &amp;ldquo;Hack&amp;rdquo; font.
Why do you care? You likely do not. However, if you&amp;rsquo;ve found this post and are still reading, let me tell you why I like Hack.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>January Ski Weekend</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/01/january-ski-weekend/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2016 07:41:50 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/01/january-ski-weekend/</guid>
      <description>As a sort of late birthday present, a few of our Wisconsin friends came out and enjoyed a ski weekend with us at Copper Mountain, the resort where we have our season passes. Tim Z. was the first to arrive on Friday afternoon. After dropping off the dog, then picking Tim up from the airport, we headed west through typically terrible Denver traffic - perhaps leaving at 4:30 was a poor decision.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DRC Update</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/01/drc-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2016 08:04:12 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/01/drc-update/</guid>
      <description>So&amp;hellip; There are a couple of updates, but we&amp;rsquo;re still stuck.
The US sent a delegation of congressmen to the DRC to talk specifically about this issue. As has become typical, the DRC responded with things that we want to hear. I won&amp;rsquo;t go into details, but I wanted to document, for posterity, the letter I wrote to my congressmen in Colorado. I&amp;rsquo;ve been interacting with their offices for the past couple of months and have a fairly good rapport going with my contacts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Mission Viejo Elementary Football League</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/01/the-mission-viejo-elementary-football-league/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2016 08:08:47 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/01/the-mission-viejo-elementary-football-league/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m pretty sure I posted about Quinton&amp;rsquo;s recent obsession with Football in a prior post or two. If not, let me just say that Quinton has fallen HARD for football and all things about it. It&amp;rsquo;s to the point where he will actually put down his iPad (gasp) and ask me to turn on a football game when he knows one will be on. If you know Quinton, you know that is not something to take lightly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kids these days</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/12/kids-these-days/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2015 11:21:28 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/12/kids-these-days/</guid>
      <description>Most days are pretty much the same. I get up at 5:30, shower, get Ethan up at 6:00, make breakfast for us, then leave around 6:30 to get him to School. After that I&amp;rsquo;m not sure what typically happens as Jenny just takes care of it. Well, last week I had the opportunity to walk Quinton to school because Ethan had final exams and would be getting done around the time Quinton would normally be going to school.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>There, I fixed it - plumbing edition</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/12/there-i-fixed-it-plumbing-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2015 07:27:08 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/12/there-i-fixed-it-plumbing-edition/</guid>
      <description>One of these days I will get around to posting the epic project that we&amp;rsquo;ve undertaken of redoing our kitchen. It&amp;rsquo;s been about 4 months in the making and we&amp;rsquo;re hitting the final stretch! Last week the countertops were installed so we finally got our new sink installed. Unfortunately, the countertop guys don&amp;rsquo;t do plumbing, so that&amp;rsquo;s my job!
I had budgeted three trips to the hardware store, and I was right on the money!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thanksgiving, Colorado Style</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/12/thanksgiving-colorado-style/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2015 07:44:26 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/12/thanksgiving-colorado-style/</guid>
      <description>Our first major holiday in Colorado is my favorite of all holidays, Thanksgiving! While it&amp;rsquo;s difficult to not be able to spend it with family, we were able to make good memories of it by spending it in the Mountains at a ski resort. Hopefully this is something we will make a tradition out of, because it was a lot of fun!
We went up on Wednesday and left a little early in hopes of beating the traffic into the mountains.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Grady Farm</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/11/the-grady-farm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2015 09:37:32 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/11/the-grady-farm/</guid>
      <description>Grady Family Farm - circa 1980   The picture is of the farm I grew up on that is 13 miles north and west of Marquette, Iowa- The present owners took down the barn, chicken house, granary, and corn crib- but curiously left the outhouse that is south of the house. The picture is looking to the west and the farm my mother grew up on is the one in the distant west, just in viewing- you can not see the church and cemetery that is less than on quarter of a mile to the right in the picture- St Pius V Catholic Church, Cherry Mound where my Mom and Dad are buried and where I mowed every summer for about six years- I knew every tombstone in the cemetery and when someone wanted to know where their relative was buried, the priest would contact me and I would show them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Casa Bonita</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/11/casa-bonita/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2015 20:49:12 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/11/casa-bonita/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to a new section of the blog, the Weekends section. These entries will cover things that we do as a family on the weekends. From hikes to restaurants to whatever else. Since we&amp;rsquo;re new to the area, most things we do here are new to us!
Casa Bonita Last weekend&amp;rsquo;s destination was Casa Bonita, &amp;ldquo;The Most Entertaining Restaurant In The World.&amp;rdquo;
  Casa Bonita   That&amp;rsquo;s their tag line, anyway.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bike Hangar Idea</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/11/bike-hangar-idea/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2015 20:02:33 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/11/bike-hangar-idea/</guid>
      <description>Thought I would put this out there as I had never thought of this before. We needed to hang our bikes in the garage. I didn&amp;rsquo;t really want to spend too much money on hardware, so we just got the cheap hooks that you can get at Home Depot - they were like $1.50 each. I typically don&amp;rsquo;t like using those hooks because it&amp;rsquo;s a pain to find studs to drill and put them into, and then when you do, it rarely lines up with the thing you want to hang.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adoption Woes</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/11/adoption-woes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2015 10:22:35 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/11/adoption-woes/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;ve known us for any amount of time, you know that we are, and have been in the process of adopting from the Democratic Republic of Congo for the past 3 years. It has been a long, LONG process.
TL;DR; Last month, the Congolese government has dashed our hopes of completing this adoption in the near timeframe. It is questionable if we will ever be able to complete it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quinton&#39;s Snowboard</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/11/quintons-snowboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Nov 2015 21:44:52 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/11/quintons-snowboard/</guid>
      <description>We are first year Coloradoans, so we are behaving like them. We purchased season ski passes, even though it is next to impossible to get into the mountains due to all the traffic. We are in the process of upgrading all of our equipment because no Coloradoan would be caught dead with the 10 year old skis that we have!
Since we are planning on going to the mountains for our first trip over Thanksgiving, we needed to get some equipment for Quinton and Ethan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Kitchen Discovery</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/11/a-kitchen-discovery/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2015 20:55:58 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/11/a-kitchen-discovery/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;re redoing our kitchen right now. I have a long post queued up for some time in the near future to go through some of the experience and show pictures. It&amp;rsquo;s been fun, but it&amp;rsquo;s also been interesting.
Last weekend we finally got to the point where we could take out our old lower cabinets and replace them with the new ones. The plan was to demolish on Saturday and install on Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quinton&#39;s Christmas List</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/11/quintons-christmas-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2015 08:38:04 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/11/quintons-christmas-list/</guid>
      <description>Jenny had Quinton write a letter to Santa. Since he was also typing a thank you letter to his grandparents on my e-mail, he decided to e-mail his letter to Santa this year. I came across it in my drafts folder and found it amusing.
 dear santa i want a ps vita a dirt bike a soccer ball a trampoline football gear mostly a dirt bike and a ps vita and halo 5 and ps 4 and 100 dollars and a golden retreiver.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Now With Comments</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/11/now-with-comments/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2015 10:12:59 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/11/now-with-comments/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;re here, great! I&amp;rsquo;m not sure how you found it because I haven&amp;rsquo;t yet linked the old blog to this one, nor have I done any advertisement or anything (I probably won&amp;rsquo;t ever advertise).
There will be a larger series on how the new blog was constructed and some of the technical ins and outs, but I wanted to quickly mention that the blog is soft-launched, and today I added the ability to comment using Discus, a SaaS based commenting and discuussion platform.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quinton and Fun With Words</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/11/quinton-and-fun-with-words/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2015 19:21:14 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/11/quinton-and-fun-with-words/</guid>
      <description>New words for the dictionary:
becept /bee * &amp;lsquo;cept/
Origin - from what I can tell, a combination of except and besides. Perfectly encapsulates the meaning of both in different situations.
Example: &amp;ldquo;Everyone is having fun becept me.&amp;rdquo;
w&amp;rsquo;bout /wuh * &amp;lsquo;bout/
Origin - shortened version of &amp;ldquo;what about.&amp;rdquo; Not particularly interesting for its meaning but rather it&amp;rsquo;s usage.
Example: &amp;ldquo;The moon doesn&amp;rsquo;t have it&amp;rsquo;s own light - it only reflects the sun&amp;rsquo;s light.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>There, I Fixed It</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/10/there-i-fixed-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2015 21:34:14 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/10/there-i-fixed-it/</guid>
      <description>Quinton has really wanted a remote control airplane for quite some time. Uncle Blaine bought him a remote control helicopter a little over a year ago that he absolutely loved for the entirety of the 10 minutes before he lost it in the trees. Over the years he&amp;rsquo;s amassed quite the aresnal of cheap, crappy remote control things - cars, trucks, motorcycles - each one cheaper and crappier than the last.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skype with Mireille</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/10/skype-with-mireille/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2015 09:53:21 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/10/skype-with-mireille/</guid>
      <description>We got to Skype with Mireille this morning. It&amp;rsquo;s always bittersweet talking with her. On the one hand, you want to make sure you keep in touch so she at least has some sort of connection, but on another hand it just sort of hurts to talk with her. When we talk with her, we are reminded of the situation that we&amp;rsquo;re in, whereas other times we can sort of ignore it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hide and Seek</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/10/hide-and-seek/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2015 09:52:05 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/10/hide-and-seek/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s hard to play Hide and Seek when you have a dog&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>