<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Amusing on The Hydrant</title>
    <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/tags/amusing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Amusing on The Hydrant</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 11:52:46 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://dogsbuttbrew.com/tags/amusing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Mireille Funnies</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/09/mireille-funnies/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 11:52:46 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/09/mireille-funnies/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Jenny was talking to Mireille on Sunday about things that girls talk about. I wasn&amp;rsquo;t privvy to the details of the entire conversation, because that wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be appropriate - I&amp;rsquo;m a boy. One little nugget Jenny shared with me was when Mireille admitted to her, &amp;ldquo;I wish I was a unicorn. But I&amp;rsquo;m just Mireille&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Then, yesterday, our little Unicorn proved she listens and absorbs way more than she ever lets on. Since moving to Colorado we&amp;rsquo;ve had some difficulty adapting to the local colloqualisms. It&amp;rsquo;s not too different here, but the differences that do exist between here and Milwaukee are hard, particularly for adults. The one that seems most stubborn for Jenny and I is calling the last meal of the day dinner (CO) instead of supper (WI). Any time Jenny will say it in front of Maylee, she will make a big deal of correcting her. Just yesterday, Jenny and I were sitting on our newly completed deck with Mireille and discussing what we should do for supper. Mireille looked seriously at Jenny and said quietly, &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s dinner mom, not supper.&amp;rdquo; Maylee is so proud, and now I am double thinking anything I say in front of her.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mireille&#39;s English - now with Pronouns!!!</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/12/mireilles-english-now-with-pronouns/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2016 20:47:29 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/12/mireilles-english-now-with-pronouns/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Mireille has been in the US for right around 8 months now, and she still has yet to stop amazing me with how quickly she is adjusting. It&amp;rsquo;s not only just the English, though that is remarkable, but everything else as well. I don&amp;rsquo;t think I can really explain it better than I can show it with the picture below which I believe encapsulates the completeness of Mireille&amp;rsquo;s Westernization.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/2B5AUc23X1rnygldAUI-kzhS2D8AhJQZ_CP8M5YQqQZWd4nZh-JeTZwJoSUJIYCaaoV6bstFzernyA=w1014-h1350-no&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h4&gt;Westernized Mireille&lt;/h4&gt; &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Beyond device usage and creature comforts, Mireille continues to pickup English at an alarming rate. She&amp;rsquo;s been playing around with pronouns lately. The other day, while in the same bathroom as is shown in the above picture, she said to me, &amp;ldquo;Ethan&amp;rsquo;s too big for this bathroom.&amp;rdquo; I prodded her to ask her why she thought he was too big, and she responded, &amp;ldquo;him&amp;rsquo;s butt&amp;rsquo;s too big.&amp;rdquo; Him is pretty much the pronoun for any person that is not herself. She still rarely uses &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;my&amp;rdquo; but instead opts for speaking of herself in the third person, but she has started referring to others in the shorthand &amp;ldquo;him,&amp;rdquo; so that&amp;rsquo;s progress!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quinton and Fun With Words</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/11/quinton-and-fun-with-words/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2015 19:21:14 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/11/quinton-and-fun-with-words/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;New words for the dictionary:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;becept /bee * &amp;lsquo;cept/&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Origin - from what I can tell, a combination of except and besides. Perfectly&#xA;encapsulates the meaning of both in different situations.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Example: &amp;ldquo;Everyone is having fun becept me.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;w&amp;rsquo;bout /wuh * &amp;lsquo;bout/&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Origin - shortened version of &amp;ldquo;what about.&amp;rdquo; Not particularly interesting for&#xA;its meaning but rather it&amp;rsquo;s usage.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Example: &amp;ldquo;The moon doesn&amp;rsquo;t have it&amp;rsquo;s own light - it only reflects the sun&amp;rsquo;s&#xA;light.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
