<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Travel on The Hydrant</title>
    <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/tags/travel/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Travel on The Hydrant</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 07:35:41 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://dogsbuttbrew.com/tags/travel/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Ozark - Season 2022 - Wrap it up</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2022/06/ozark-season-2022-wrap-it-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 07:35:41 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2022/06/ozark-season-2022-wrap-it-up/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;And, that&amp;rsquo;s a wrap! We managed to get out of there a little before 8:00 on Friday morning and traveled straight back to where we came from. The drive was gloriously boring and uneventful. We stopped one time to get food at a Burger King near Topeka, but other than that, it was a more or less straight shot west on 70. Strangely, the winds of Kansas seemed to switch direction in the week we were gone, so they were in our face the whole way back just like the trip there. Kansas is weird.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ozark - Season 2022 - The Cave</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2022/06/ozark-season-2022-the-cave/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 07:23:41 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2022/06/ozark-season-2022-the-cave/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Two of the families had to leave on Friday morning, so it was just the Chovanecs and Gradys for Friday! Given the smaller group, we decided to do some excursions since logistics would be easier. Of course, we still couldn&amp;rsquo;t all fit in a single car&amp;hellip; Damn big families!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;After seeing off the other two families, and after some breakfast leftovers, we headed out towards Bridal Cave, a cave about 15 miles away. The drive was nice. Along the way we saw lots of interesting signs, including one for a bar called the &amp;ldquo;Glory Hole,&amp;rdquo; one for a mini-golf course called &amp;ldquo;Putt Pirates&amp;rdquo; who asked you to &amp;ldquo;put your balls in our puttholes,&amp;rdquo; and yet another one for a sausage place that bragged that &amp;ldquo;nobody beats our meat.&amp;rdquo; The realization came all at once that the Ozarks had a thing for double entendres. And they weren&amp;rsquo;t bad, honestly! Sadly we weren&amp;rsquo;t able to visit any of these classy establishments..&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ozark - Season 2022 - Jenny&#39;s Birthday</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2022/06/ozark-season-2022-jennys-birthday/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 07:13:41 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2022/06/ozark-season-2022-jennys-birthday/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Thursday! The last full day for some as they were leaving for various weekend commitments. It also happened to be Jenny&amp;rsquo;s birthday! There was nothing much on the docket for Thursday, so you guessed it, we did a bit of swimming, drinking, and eating.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The week was punishingly hot and muggy for those of us that live in the high desert in Colorado, so we did take plenty of breaks in the very cold, air conditioned house to play games. Pool was a big hit! Quinton played tons of it, probably in no small part due to the fact that he didn&amp;rsquo;t have a phone! Foosball was also quite popular. We did play some Jenga, Scrabble, and other board games as well. There was no lack of downtime activities at this house.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ozark - Season 2022 - Dan&#39;s Birthday</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2022/06/ozark-season-2022-dans-birthday/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2022 19:25:41 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2022/06/ozark-season-2022-dans-birthday/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Wednesday (I think, it started to get fuzzy in the middle there) was more of the same. We needed to get the boat back to Pirate Petes by 9:00 AM, so Micky, Jenny, and I took off around 7:30 to transist the 27 miles of water between our cabin and there. It was a lovely drive and we really didn&amp;rsquo;t see a boat to speak of! I think I had to deal with a wake one time when we passed a pontoon going the opposite direction.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ozark - Season 2022 - The Boat</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2022/06/ozark-season-2022-the-boat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2022 18:31:41 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2022/06/ozark-season-2022-the-boat/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The one thing we did that was &amp;ldquo;productive&amp;rdquo; on Monday outside of making food and fixing drinks was to decide on renting a boat for a day. Todd and Sandi had been out earlier that day checking out the area and found a rental place called Pirate Petes where we could rent a pontoon that would sit 12 (we had 13, but we figured we would chance it). So this morning, Todd, Tim, and I went to Pirate Pete&amp;rsquo;s to pickup our boat. This was about the time where we marveled at how much the Ozarks area has leaned into the Pirate mythos. I presume they encountered lake pirates at some point in their distant past&amp;hellip; Probably from Illinois&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ozark - Season 2022 - And, we relax...</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2022/06/ozark-season-2022-and-we-relax.../</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2022 18:13:41 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2022/06/ozark-season-2022-and-we-relax.../</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Day 1, really. Full day 1. Nothing on the plans for the day, so there was little possibility of being late. In that spirit, most of us managed to sleep well past 9:00, even Mireille. We got up and Jenny made some breakfast food that we had purchased, and we eventually meandered our way to the Party Deck!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This property is equipped with many outdoor surfaces from which to party. There is the boat deck, where one could party if they liked. There is the Martini Deck, another party location. There is the deck off of the game room, the deck off of the kitchen, and the main focal point of all water and party activities, the party deck.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ozark - Season 2022 - Retrospective and The Drive</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2022/06/ozark-season-2022-retrospective-and-the-drive/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2022 17:55:41 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2022/06/ozark-season-2022-retrospective-and-the-drive/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m going to try this one a little different. We just got back from the Ozarks yesterday. Consequently, Jenny and I watched the first episode of the last season of Ozark last night, and they started with the end, so I figured I&amp;rsquo;d try that.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It was nice to get caught up today! I started out with a nice run - a little slower and shorter than my normal route. Jenny and I got Starbucks, which we hadn&amp;rsquo;t done in a week. The dogs convalesced from their internment in Doggy Prison, er, camp. All in all it was shaping up to be a good day. We cleaned ou the Guinea Pig cage, then spent 45 minutes trying to retrieve Odin from underneath the hedge in the front yard that he decided was his new home&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Catching Up</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2022/06/catching-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 19:39:41 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2022/06/catching-up/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;So I find myself, once again, very far out of touch with these updates. One of the things I like best about these updates is the running dialog they represent for our vacations. Given we&amp;rsquo;ve got one of those coming up, it seems a good time to reboot!!!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;First, what&amp;rsquo;s happened since we last talked:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;rv-update-20&#34;&gt;RV Update 20!&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It seems I rudely left the world hanging on a final update from our Epic RV Trip from last summer! Many apologies. I had big intentions, and even some cool content planned, but much of that is now lost to time.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring Break - COVID-19 Edition - Chapter 4 - Home</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/03/spring-break-covid-19-edition-chapter-4-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 19:39:41 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/03/spring-break-covid-19-edition-chapter-4-home/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re cutting our vacation short! Today was originally supposed to be the day we took a trip on the narrow gauge railroad, but alas, they canceled their trips starting today. We were then going to go up to Telluride to take in the scenery there as well as do some snowmobiling, but threats of weather in the mountains and continued restaurant closures convinced us otherwise. As I write this, the county in which Telluride resides has just issued a &amp;ldquo;Shelter In Place&amp;rdquo; order, which is even more reason to be happy we didn&amp;rsquo;t end up there this morning!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring Break - COVID-19 Edition - Chapter 3 - Closed</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/03/spring-break-covid-19-edition-chapter-3-closed/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 19:39:41 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/03/spring-break-covid-19-edition-chapter-3-closed/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Happy St. Patrick&amp;rsquo;s Day!!!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We had a plan for the day, but we needed first to get some breakfast. That would come in the form of McDonalds and Starbucks, both of which were open, but neither of which would allow you to eat or consume there, abiding by the governor&amp;rsquo;s orders! Quinton discovered the mediocraty but sufficiency of the McDonald&amp;rsquo;s breakfast burritos (better with hot sauce) while Mireille enjoyed her Hot Cakes and sausage, which are&amp;hellip; fine&amp;hellip; The best part about where we are staying is that it is walking distance to so many places - mostly restaurants! But we were able to walk to both of these places, order in the dining room, then enjoy them back in our room before departing.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring Break - COVID-19 Edition - Chapter 2 - The Drive</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/03/spring-break-covid-19-edition-chapter-2-the-drive/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 19:39:32 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/03/spring-break-covid-19-edition-chapter-2-the-drive/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;On Monday at 7:45, we left home, without the animals (Ethan&amp;rsquo;s college canceled their classes the first three days of this week, so the animals could stay with him). We first stopped at Mireille&amp;rsquo;s school to pickup her packet of &amp;ldquo;school at home&amp;rdquo; papers. Then we headed west through the mountains towards Durango, CO.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For the first few hours, we listened to public radio. After about 2 hours of that, we had had enough of the Coronavirus talk, so we listened to a podcast about the space race. During that time, the mayor of Denver announced that he was ordering all restaurants and bars closed for dine-in for 8 weeks. Well, lucky for us - we weren&amp;rsquo;t going to be affected by that!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring Break - COVID-19 Edition - Chapter 1 - Preamble</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/03/spring-break-covid-19-edition-chapter-1-preamble/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2020 21:12:18 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/03/spring-break-covid-19-edition-chapter-1-preamble/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Spring Break!!! Woo!!!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Actually, as the years go on, the event has become more and more complicated. Three kids in two different schools last year was one thing - but this year, three kids in three different schools increased the complexity. And add to that the fact that I &lt;em&gt;just&lt;/em&gt; started a new job&amp;hellip; No worries - we would ignore the adult child, and that will simplify things!!! Well, sort of. Still, with the two youngers in two different schools, of course their spring break didn&amp;rsquo;t line up. So we took the older child&amp;rsquo;s break, took the younger child out of school, and planned on heading to Phoenix to visit with the Grandparents who we haven&amp;rsquo;t seen in Phoenix for a couple of years now. Easy peasy!!!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring Break 2018 - Day Three</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/03/spring-break-2018-day-three/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Mar 2018 20:15:04 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/03/spring-break-2018-day-three/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;taos&#34;&gt;Taos&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our third day was dedicated to Taos. Having slept in a little, but not quite as much as the prior day, we had a little extra time to do some swimming in hopes of getting away from the crowds in the pool. We weren&amp;rsquo;t successful in avoiding crowds, but we did get about 45 minutes of swimming in before we left the hotel. Mireille, Quinton, and I played some hide and seek (it&amp;rsquo;s more fun than you would think). Mireille learned she could float with her little floatie thing, and even jumped into the pool with it on! Jenny and Ethan I&amp;rsquo;m sure did boring things in the room&amp;hellip; Probably showered or whatever.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring Break 2018 - Day Two</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/03/spring-break-2018-day-two/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 21:34:29 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/03/spring-break-2018-day-two/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;los-alamos&#34;&gt;Los Alamos&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Thank goodness, today started out MUCH later than the prior one. Nobody really stirred until 9:00, giving Mireille a much needed 13 hours, and Quinton an even more needed 11.5. Of course, I was also happy to finally get 10 myself, though I was up several times in the night for the &amp;ldquo;old man pee.&amp;rdquo; While we all got ready, Jenny and Mireille went to get some coffee at the very convenient on presmises Starbucks in the lobby. Jenny noted when we got back that they rode the &amp;ldquo;alligator&amp;rdquo; to get down to the first floor.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring Break 2018 - Day One</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/03/spring-break-2018-day-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2018 21:00:53 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/03/spring-break-2018-day-one/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;am&#34;&gt;AM&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As we suspected, and as is typical, we were up way too early. Mireille woke up around 7:00 the first time, Quinton followed about 7:30. While Mireille was able to fall back to sleep for a bit, Quinton was screaming for food by 8:00, so we were up! We left Ethan to sleep while the rest of us went down to one of the dozen or so restaurants the hotel had to offer for a nice buffet breakfast. It was at breakfast that I learned that New Mexico is the only state in the union that has a &amp;ldquo;state question.&amp;rdquo; That question is, perhaps predictably, &amp;ldquo;red or green.&amp;rdquo; They are referring, of course, to what color alien they keep at Area 51! OK, they don&amp;rsquo;t mean that - it refers to chili peppers, where New Mexico is the &amp;ldquo;world leader,&amp;rdquo; whatever that means. At breakfast and restaurants it means that you basically get chili with anything you order, and you can order red or greeen chili to your liking. I typically choose green since I am now a Denver native, and that&amp;rsquo;s what us quirky Denver natives like.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring Break 2018 - The Drive</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/03/spring-break-2018-the-drive/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 22:29:27 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/03/spring-break-2018-the-drive/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Are we going to the hotel tonight?&amp;rdquo; This is the question repeated at least nightly for the last two weeks by our youngest, Mireille. For some reason she just loves hotels! I think it has something to do with the swimming pools. Perhaps she just likes to travel! At any rate, it had been a constant anthem for the last several weeks - &amp;ldquo;are we going to the hotel?&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The day before we left, we dropped the &amp;ldquo;Flex-car&amp;rdquo; off at Rack Attack to get rails and a luggage rack installed. We also purchased a travel box so we could finally travel in style. While the car had it&amp;rsquo;s new rack put on, Jenny, Ethan, and I visited the University of Denver, a local private school, to see if Ethan had any interested. Thankfully, he didn&amp;rsquo;t. It&amp;rsquo;s a pricey school!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Epic of the Flex</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/11/the-epic-of-the-flex/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2017 16:16:59 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/11/the-epic-of-the-flex/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;If you are familiar with our family, you know that we don&amp;rsquo;t really place a high value on vehicles. Basically whatever can get us from point A to point B reliably and without a whole lot of money in maintenance will do. In our particular family, we now have three vehicles, two Chevy Malibu&amp;rsquo;s that have a combined age approaching 30 years, and a &amp;ldquo;new&amp;rdquo; Ford Flex that is only 3 years old, but is approaching 100,000 miles itself. The Flex is supposed to be our &amp;ldquo;reliable&amp;rdquo; car.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Life of a Single Father</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/06/life-of-a-single-father/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2016 21:43:24 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/06/life-of-a-single-father/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s 9:44 PM on Thursday evening. I&amp;rsquo;ve finally settled down to my computer and&#xA;a bomber of my local&amp;rsquo;s double IPA. It&amp;rsquo;s the first time today that I&amp;rsquo;ve been&#xA;able to sit without somebody demanding something or me having to be preparing&#xA;something for somebody. You see, Jenny has been traveling for work since Monday&#xA;morning, leaving me, a single father of three.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve been a single father in the past. There&amp;rsquo;s something much more complicated&#xA;about being a single father now-a-days, however. Not only is it three kids,&#xA;which even though we&amp;rsquo;ve added only one child, the apparent number of children&#xA;seems to have risen exponentially. No, it&amp;rsquo;s not &lt;em&gt;just&lt;/em&gt; the third child, but the&#xA;fact that the third child is a three year old black girl! Let me explain.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two Days on the Hill</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/02/two-days-on-the-hill/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2016 10:15:09 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/02/two-days-on-the-hill/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;preamble&#34;&gt;Preamble&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I briefly considered titling this &amp;ldquo;Mr. Grady Goes to Washington,&amp;rdquo; but I didn&amp;rsquo;t&#xA;like it for a couple of reasons. First, I don&amp;rsquo;t really think of myself as&#xA;Mr. Grady. And more importantly, I have never really seen the movie, and I hate&#xA;giving false information.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is a story about a number of things&amp;hellip; Adoption, politics, travel, weather&amp;hellip;&#xA;Hold on to your seats, and grab some NoDoze. This might get boring!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>She&#39;s Coming Home!!!</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/02/shes-coming-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2016 07:59:33 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/02/shes-coming-home/</guid>
      <description>&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/8Cmk5RKPfdXpaITEv7XJyNfYnunG3NmosrbdGaL6hmNT8xmcfekDIwFpiTUXebs8netwE55Ia_lnrA=w960-h1280-no&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h4&gt;Riding to my Red Eye&lt;/h4&gt; &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/5aF5JNcVIg8S4rvaO79bFdIqBLGA_mYCLmNZe3qE_HhfIN0Yle6bJ_IQ_BaNU3Rt7DYd1Avu8uxjkA=w1830-h1372-no&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h4&gt;Dulles Airport&lt;/h4&gt; &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/LO3UXr1yK65hVk0Q7KT4ZkmBoFLyqGwVgfsN9TaPSxpoquee6pXACZhxRopLJo9ETWlIqcALK5XvMg=w1030-h1372-no&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h4&gt;Empty International Arrival Terminal&lt;/h4&gt; &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/I-TpkEc4M1Hcf9oRJUGd9E0AJ86Ok2jyM_jGiy-cn2oxIBcBfTVJ4pu6Du2sQExLK-0zVskY2sYxcw=w1830-h1372-no&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h4&gt;UA 951 from Brussels&lt;/h4&gt; &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/Zov87qb-27qil2rQQ-Bs8pcOE2rnyCz_lgO3s7MEa4KK8CtLCysnczJA5d8au9puQgczsIUvrt5ukA=w1030-h1372-no&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h4&gt;At at DGM, Ironic Lunch&lt;/h4&gt; &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/pULwNKpVhdF6v3e4MVWfMDR4LpmIS_vG712y3il8U98dPUp_pAZhM7mWODSD9cqxIUYDePngrWPGRQ=w750-h1334-no&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h4&gt;The Wait is Excruciating&lt;/h4&gt; &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/jvof0kJy-0WdJfXpVacQcv3Wad5_uGqSBjSqg-P0yZCiB949FdD47d-uw5yb7xWXwHjWSnhtKxitgw=w750-h1334-no&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h4&gt;The Plane has Landed!&lt;/h4&gt; &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/Oq_wZEZM9mUEzmD49xpEGgHsBAAZbUwMWqjnfEqxzXOBY8832uOsnT-gpPz9PcJgsT2IwbWkgQoJxw=w1030-h1372-no&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h4&gt;Busiest Time of Day&lt;/h4&gt; &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/zKDZBQ6_DyPykIbkGVJNqNaS9_GCQCqW_UA72WdY71xhPlUF4jlhLgfdYpzHR4pOgqu2ym6UQESxhg=w1030-h1372-no&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h4&gt;She&amp;#39;s Here!&lt;/h4&gt; &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/zQintpxRx8zj5NpvRDhAh0YUnfo1DR2586B3_hBFty7d10K8zCDrpsAANJ0jTL5sIX11Ou1qqfSaPw=w1030-h1372-no&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h4&gt;Confused?&lt;/h4&gt; &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/oDLo_MrcVdoQTTq2oN0mDOEKtjPmDcQcCwqx9DDMlM4sQboQKCkJlX6LY4rvUkq9Yk5vy88u5tYu-A=w960-h1280-no&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h4&gt;Proof - in the U.S.&lt;/h4&gt; &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/pmrnTNojliemaBuiEpFBycuntkbPIQ5QpDOVArbRS9WjIcLid1Fk7zHvlxnSPyWNxBLOElJsIYTf-Q=w1030-h1372-no&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h4&gt;Playing Dress-up&lt;/h4&gt; &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/v5plBg_Zj6namKB2EtbrBso03tHlqrF2v6nAbiaWebBi6LaVS0uV5AQYLh-CL7sDJ84URgqzzkuwKA=w1030-h1372-no&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h4&gt;And... Out.&lt;/h4&gt; &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/J2QYL2Va9P-TU_HqxF1a1Txbk0Pjh6UwJ2FUkjLrvaOC0mmvQAgToc87lvyxL4iqhEcWsP4ecm5I9w=w1830-h1372-no&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h4&gt;Playing with Mama&lt;/h4&gt; &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/mQXECZJiXoSzMQqp1qJGokFoswcbSSVCLg-Y_9qXsEmkJttXCW0xCXigQyAbSL7PcPMwnyA9RsJVjg=w1030-h1372-no&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h4&gt;Women, they be shoppin!&lt;/h4&gt; &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/hfMDCIc8_bLR7hh_qaZSLeMFkR0JVXYi6E3DMzPOGuA39cuAcWxcMAUaTMu5yN5Lsvkbhq0qDzfaKw=w1830-h1372-no&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h4&gt;Playing with Yaya&lt;/h4&gt; &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/kFLi3_pZq2O7j6fjv4eDbBYosc00XZ0WR5l318dTgPVfZhf23JO2YSrOfsK2WTheJj86YU4-gqr6wA=w1030-h1372-no&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h4&gt;Starting the Hair Restoration Project&lt;/h4&gt; &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Left on the red-eye on Saturday night.&#xA;Nothing open in the airport.&#xA;Arrived at Dulles at 4:00 AM.&#xA;Nothing open in the airport.&#xA;$25 cab ride to the hotel 7 miles away.&#xA;Couldn&amp;rsquo;t check me in.&#xA;I annoyed them into letting me check in early.&#xA;Napped for 2 hours.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
