<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Holidays on The Hydrant</title>
    <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/tags/holidays/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Holidays on The Hydrant</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2017 18:45:01 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://dogsbuttbrew.com/tags/holidays/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Elf on the Shelf</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/12/elf-on-the-shelf/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2017 18:45:01 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/12/elf-on-the-shelf/</guid>
      <description>There are many traditions that I&amp;rsquo;ve learned of since leaving the nest that my family was either ignorant to or just didn&amp;rsquo;t celebrate. One happened this morning, and has for the last 21 years of my marriage, yet I still forget to celebrate it - St. Nicholas&amp;rsquo;s Day. Jenny celebrated it year after year, yet I did not, so even though I&amp;rsquo;ve now been in my adult life much longer than I was ever in my parents&#39; home, I still forget&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thanksgiving 2017</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/12/thanksgiving-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2017 12:16:24 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/12/thanksgiving-2017/</guid>
      <description>Thanksgiving is literally my favorite holiday. I just love getting together with family and friends, cooking a delicious meal, eating said meal, just hanging out and napping with people. I think even more than Christmas, it is the most relaxing holiday out there!
This year, having already done the &amp;ldquo;Grady Christmas&amp;rdquo; several weeks earlier, our plan was to stay put for Thanksgiving. Luckily there are others in the greater Denver metropolitan area that are also too far away to spend the day with family, so they became our extended family for Thanksgiving.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thanksgiving, Colorado Style</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/12/thanksgiving-colorado-style/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2015 07:44:26 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/12/thanksgiving-colorado-style/</guid>
      <description>Our first major holiday in Colorado is my favorite of all holidays, Thanksgiving! While it&amp;rsquo;s difficult to not be able to spend it with family, we were able to make good memories of it by spending it in the Mountains at a ski resort. Hopefully this is something we will make a tradition out of, because it was a lot of fun!
We went up on Wednesday and left a little early in hopes of beating the traffic into the mountains.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
