<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Quin on The Hydrant</title>
    <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/tags/quin/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Quin on The Hydrant</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2014 10:37:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://dogsbuttbrew.com/tags/quin/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Big, Fat, and Stupid</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/big-fat-and-stupid/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2014 10:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/big-fat-and-stupid/</guid>
      <description>A couple of weeks ago I got an e-mail from an old co-worker who still worked at my old place of employment. It was a complimentary e-mail, fairly light in nature, which made it all the more mysterious why the e-mail header on my iPad read, &amp;ldquo;To: Big, Fat, and Stupid - From: &amp;lt;name omitted&amp;gt;&amp;rdquo;. Hmm&amp;hellip; I asked him why that was what he had called me in his address book and he claimed innocense.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adventures in Potty Training - again</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/adventures-in-potty-training---again/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2011 21:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/adventures-in-potty-training---again/</guid>
      <description>Boy, a week makes a big difference. As of today, Quin is a week without diapers (while conscious). Last Saturday, Quin finally decided that he really, REALLY wanted to wear his light-up shoes all the time. He woke up on Saturday morning and told me, &amp;ldquo;daddy, I want my light-up shoes.&amp;rdquo; I told him that he had to wear underwear if he wanted to do that, and he thought that was OK.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baby Driver</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/baby-driver/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2010 23:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/baby-driver/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;They call him baby driver.&amp;rdquo; My dad used to sing that song to us when we were young. I don&amp;rsquo;t know if I ever heard the real version, but I remember it almost as well as him saying &amp;ldquo;wake up and piss, the world&amp;rsquo;s on fire.&amp;rdquo; Anyway, I digress&amp;hellip;
It&amp;rsquo;s been a busy spring here at the Grady house. So busy, in fact, that we really haven&amp;rsquo;t had time to do any yard work besides the required lawn cutting so far.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2009 Update</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/2009-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2009 21:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/2009-update/</guid>
      <description>Happy New Year!
I hope you all had a wonderful 2008 and are ready to endure what is sure to be an interesting and trying 2009. I have mailed a &amp;ldquo;2008 Year in Review&amp;rdquo; to some of you, those that I knew could take it (it&amp;rsquo;s a 30 minute video of our family). If you would like one of your own and did not receive one, please e-mail me and I will be happy to send one out to you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Big Strides</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/big-strides/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2008 21:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/big-strides/</guid>
      <description>Quin has learned the fine art of movement. He still doesn&amp;rsquo;t really &amp;ldquo;crawl,&amp;rdquo; necessarily, but he lilts along like an army man. Actually he looks a little like Igor would look if he crawled. Since he&amp;rsquo;s been in motion, he&amp;rsquo;s bee quite happy and quite a handful. I don&amp;rsquo;t remember if Ethan got into as much when he was younger, but Quin really likes to get into everything!
Unfortunately, Quin&amp;rsquo;s also been sick for the last week or so.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A rough 36 hours...</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/a-rough-36-hours.../</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2008 21:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/a-rough-36-hours.../</guid>
      <description>It all started out innocently enough. We were going to church on Sunday morning, after which Ethan was supposed to attend a birthday party for a girl in his class. While in the &amp;ldquo;gathering place&amp;rdquo; after mass, Ethan was horsing around with a buddy of his when his head got bumped and one of his loose teeth started bleeding. On came the waterworks! He insisted that he was in no shape to go to the party.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Big Update</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/big-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2008 08:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/big-update/</guid>
      <description>Quin is 9 weeks old now!!! We&amp;rsquo;ve had a good couple of weeks with him so I thought I&amp;rsquo;d share with the lot of you.
First off, he&amp;rsquo;s now eating about 5 ounces at a time every 4 hours. Unfortunately, he&amp;rsquo;s still doing that at night as well. Although, some nights he&amp;rsquo;s been known to go 6 or more hours between feedings, and when he does wake up to eat, he&amp;rsquo;s very good about going back to sleep promptly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bringing Quin home</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/bringing-quin-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2008 18:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/bringing-quin-home/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday we got the call that Quin was going to be discharged from the hospital. It was going to be later in the day, so we took Ethan out of school around 12:30 and headed over to the hospital. When we walked into the nursery, we were surprised to find two doctors circumcising Quin. We thought that had happened already in the morning! Well, it was somewhat interesting to watch, but Ethan was not so impressed.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>