<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Quin on The Hydrant</title>
    <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/tags/quin/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Quin on The Hydrant</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2014 10:37:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://dogsbuttbrew.com/tags/quin/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Big, Fat, and Stupid</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/big-fat-and-stupid/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2014 10:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/big-fat-and-stupid/</guid>
      <description>A couple of weeks ago I got an e-mail from an old co-worker who still worked at my old place of employment. It was a complimentary e-mail, fairly light in nature, which made it all the more mysterious why the e-mail header on my iPad read, &amp;ldquo;To: Big, Fat, and Stupid - From: &amp;lt;name omitted&amp;gt;&amp;rdquo;. Hmm&amp;hellip; I asked him why that was what he had called me in his address book and he claimed innocense.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Halloween Update</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/halloween-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2012 21:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/halloween-update/</guid>
      <description>Adoption It&amp;rsquo;s all begun again. Jenny and I have started pursuing another adoption, this time an international one through the Democratic Republic of Congo (formerly Zaire). So far much has been the same as last time around - filling out paperwork, background checks, talking about my feelings - fun stuff. We&amp;rsquo;re getting to the point where we will be having a social worker come to the house to interview us, so we were explaining to Quinton what we were doing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Little Quinny</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/little-quinny/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2012 21:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/little-quinny/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever heard the &amp;ldquo;Little Johnny&amp;rdquo; jokes? For several reasons, I have a feeling that they might one day be replaced by &amp;ldquo;Little Quinny&amp;rdquo; jokes. Here&amp;rsquo;s an example of one - Little Johnny was in class learning his ABCs. The teacher was asking the class to name something with each letter of the alphabet in order. Little Johnny raised his hand for each letter, but she kept skipping him thinking that he would say something bad, like &amp;ldquo;ass&amp;rdquo; for A and &amp;ldquo;butt&amp;rdquo; for B.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Memorial Day!</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/happy-memorial-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 21:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/happy-memorial-day/</guid>
      <description>We had the opportunity to travel to Spread Eagle, WI near Iron Mountain, MI for Memorial Day this year. A friend of ours works for a company that owns a &amp;ldquo;cabin&amp;rdquo; on a lake up there, which they allow their employees to rent by the week during the year. When say cabin, I mean a 5 bedroom, 4000 square foot, modern home that is situated on a lake up north. So we joined 3 other families up there for the weekend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Mother&#39;s Day</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/happy-mothers-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 May 2012 21:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/happy-mothers-day/</guid>
      <description>My boys really don&amp;rsquo;t think much, normally, before a Hallmark Holiday like Mother&amp;rsquo;s Day. Last night, however, Ethan asked me (discretely) what mom&amp;rsquo;s favorite breakfast was. I told him that she liked an egg over easy with toast. He nodded, then said that he&amp;rsquo;d like to make that for her in the morning.
So this morning, Quin (and I, I suppose) woke up a little after 6:00. He watched Garfield while I watched the inside of my eyelids for an hour more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>January update</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/january-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2012 20:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/january-update/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s tough for me to write today because my favorite group of millionaires lost to somebody else&amp;rsquo;s favorite group of millionaires in a game I was sure would go my millionaire&amp;rsquo;s way. Oh well, we must persevere!
It&amp;rsquo;s been a typical busy couple of weeks. Today was one of Ethan&amp;rsquo;s last functions as a Cub Scout, the Pinewood Derby. For most kids this is an exciting event, but for Ethan and I, we sort of dread it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Catching up with Quinton</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/catching-up-with-quinton/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2011 20:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/catching-up-with-quinton/</guid>
      <description>Neither Jenny nor I are very good about creating content for a baby book. In fact, I know I could not tell you where either of my children&amp;rsquo;s baby books are - perhaps in the top of our closet collecting dust. To capture memories, though, I&amp;rsquo;ve turned to this &amp;lsquo;blog. It worked out pretty well with Ethan so far, and Quinton has been no different. This post, then, is going to be some quick hitters to get into Quinton&amp;rsquo;s virtual baby book.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adventures in Potty Training - again</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/adventures-in-potty-training---again/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2011 21:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/adventures-in-potty-training---again/</guid>
      <description>Boy, a week makes a big difference. As of today, Quin is a week without diapers (while conscious). Last Saturday, Quin finally decided that he really, REALLY wanted to wear his light-up shoes all the time. He woke up on Saturday morning and told me, &amp;ldquo;daddy, I want my light-up shoes.&amp;rdquo; I told him that he had to wear underwear if he wanted to do that, and he thought that was OK.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dancing Quin</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/dancing-quin/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2010 10:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/dancing-quin/</guid>
      <description>This video is hilarious, I think. Obviously there must be some degree of nature going on here as nobody of the non-adopted persuasion in our family can dance like this&amp;hellip;
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baby Driver</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/baby-driver/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2010 23:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/baby-driver/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;They call him baby driver.&amp;rdquo; My dad used to sing that song to us when we were young. I don&amp;rsquo;t know if I ever heard the real version, but I remember it almost as well as him saying &amp;ldquo;wake up and piss, the world&amp;rsquo;s on fire.&amp;rdquo; Anyway, I digress&amp;hellip;
It&amp;rsquo;s been a busy spring here at the Grady house. So busy, in fact, that we really haven&amp;rsquo;t had time to do any yard work besides the required lawn cutting so far.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lots of new words, and the Amish</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/lots-of-new-words-and-the-amish/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2010 10:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/lots-of-new-words-and-the-amish/</guid>
      <description>Quin&amp;rsquo;s been quite the learner the last few months. I think since our vacation in April he&amp;rsquo;s been picking up an average of a couple new words a day. He has his favorites, though. My latest favorites are &amp;ldquo;nan&amp;rdquo; which means &amp;ldquo;dance,&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;nonut,&amp;rdquo; which means &amp;ldquo;donut.&amp;rdquo;
Quin has a definite love of dancing. He has figured out how to turn on various CD players and radios throughout the house, and once they are on, he will come and grab one of us to come and &amp;ldquo;nan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kickles and Hillbillies</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/kickles-and-hillbillies/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2009 23:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/kickles-and-hillbillies/</guid>
      <description>Of course my wife reminded me of some things I forgot&amp;hellip; If only she knew how to blog!
The other day Ethan and I were driving to Soccer when we passed a section of road we frequently pass. On one side of the road is a pretty steep, tree-covered hill with a couple of houses on top. Ethan asked me, matter of factly, if the people living there were hillbillies. To be honest, I was laughing to myself, but calmly collected myself before explaining that they were not hillbillies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Freedom...</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/freedom.../</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2009 21:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/freedom.../</guid>
      <description>Quin climbed out of his crib the other day. We were working around the house and he was acting like he was tired. He generally doesn&amp;rsquo;t like to take naps during the day, but we like him to take naps. So I put him in his crib and began to let him &amp;ldquo;cry it out.&amp;rdquo; I went outside to take care of something, and a couple of minutes later came back inside to find Quin standing downstairs, smiling at me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kissing Cousins</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/kissing-cousins/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2009 20:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/kissing-cousins/</guid>
      <description>Kissing Cousins These pictures are from awhile ago, but I thought they were cute enough to post anyway!!! This is a picture of Quinton kissing his cousin. Man, he&amp;rsquo;s really going for it! OK, they are second cousins once removed, or third cousins or something (you&amp;rsquo;d have to ask Blaine for the exact designation), so that&amp;rsquo;s probably OK in most You can tell they are from awhile ago as they were for Jodi&amp;rsquo;s baby shower - and they&amp;rsquo;ve already had the baby!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cub Scout Camp</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/cub-scout-camp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jul 2009 21:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/cub-scout-camp/</guid>
      <description>Cub Scout Camp Last week, Ethan and I attended Cub Scout day camp for our second year. This year we went on the 3 day camp. Camp started at 9:00 AM and went until 4:00 PM. Besides the mosquitoes, it was a bona-fide blast for both of us. Ethan was able to do all sorts of different activities, including archery (which is is very good at), mini-golf (which he is not so good at), highlander games, knight&amp;rsquo;s quest, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fully Ambulatory</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/fully-ambulatory/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2009 09:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/fully-ambulatory/</guid>
      <description>As of last night, Quinton has become one of the walkers of the world. He took his first tenuous steps from Jenny to myself last night before bed. Everybody was very excited. Well, Ethan was a little disappointed since he was in the shower when it happened, but was excited nonetheless. Looks like it&amp;rsquo;s time to get the house to the next level of baby-proofness.
Another score for the &amp;ldquo;nurture&amp;rdquo; portion of the nature vs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2009 Update</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/2009-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2009 21:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/2009-update/</guid>
      <description>Happy New Year!
I hope you all had a wonderful 2008 and are ready to endure what is sure to be an interesting and trying 2009. I have mailed a &amp;ldquo;2008 Year in Review&amp;rdquo; to some of you, those that I knew could take it (it&amp;rsquo;s a 30 minute video of our family). If you would like one of your own and did not receive one, please e-mail me and I will be happy to send one out to you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Big Strides</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/big-strides/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2008 21:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/big-strides/</guid>
      <description>Quin has learned the fine art of movement. He still doesn&amp;rsquo;t really &amp;ldquo;crawl,&amp;rdquo; necessarily, but he lilts along like an army man. Actually he looks a little like Igor would look if he crawled. Since he&amp;rsquo;s been in motion, he&amp;rsquo;s bee quite happy and quite a handful. I don&amp;rsquo;t remember if Ethan got into as much when he was younger, but Quin really likes to get into everything!
Unfortunately, Quin&amp;rsquo;s also been sick for the last week or so.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Catching up.</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/catching-up./</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2008 19:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/catching-up./</guid>
      <description>I know that I&amp;rsquo;m getting behind because my wife has told me that I&amp;rsquo;m in trouble because of how infrequently I blog. I didn&amp;rsquo;t even know she knew I had a blog&amp;hellip; Oh well&amp;hellip;
Quin&amp;rsquo;s doing great! He&amp;rsquo;s 7 months old now and is quite mobile. No, he still doesn&amp;rsquo;t (really) crawl, but has developed a rolling technique that enables him to get pretty much wherever he wants to go. He&amp;rsquo;s also started to try out the &amp;ldquo;all fours&amp;rdquo; thing by getting up on his knees and lunching towards things that are slightly out of his reach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ethan the Triathlete</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/ethan-the-triathlete/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2008 20:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/ethan-the-triathlete/</guid>
      <description>This past weekend was the Pewaukee Sprint Triathlon. I ran in this event last year along with a team that we had assembled known as &amp;ldquo;Big Sky Multisport.&amp;rdquo; We had our own jerseys and a whole bunch of people. Ethan was so impressed when he came to watch! He wanted to be &amp;ldquo;on my team.&amp;rdquo;
This year we did it again, and they have a kid&amp;rsquo;s event.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dexterity</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/dexterity/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2008 20:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/dexterity/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m just sitting here doing some scout stuff and Quin is sitting right next to me in one of his bouncy chairs. What&amp;rsquo;s different than normal is that he is grabbing *everything* within reach. He has access to a bunch of toys within reach and he is studying each one of them intently. This is a first for him and quite exciting for us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A rough 36 hours...</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/a-rough-36-hours.../</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2008 21:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/a-rough-36-hours.../</guid>
      <description>It all started out innocently enough. We were going to church on Sunday morning, after which Ethan was supposed to attend a birthday party for a girl in his class. While in the &amp;ldquo;gathering place&amp;rdquo; after mass, Ethan was horsing around with a buddy of his when his head got bumped and one of his loose teeth started bleeding. On came the waterworks! He insisted that he was in no shape to go to the party.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Big Update</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/big-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2008 08:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/big-update/</guid>
      <description>Quin is 9 weeks old now!!! We&amp;rsquo;ve had a good couple of weeks with him so I thought I&amp;rsquo;d share with the lot of you.
First off, he&amp;rsquo;s now eating about 5 ounces at a time every 4 hours. Unfortunately, he&amp;rsquo;s still doing that at night as well. Although, some nights he&amp;rsquo;s been known to go 6 or more hours between feedings, and when he does wake up to eat, he&amp;rsquo;s very good about going back to sleep promptly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disney Day 5</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/disney-day-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2008 21:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/disney-day-5/</guid>
      <description>Morning Swim Finally, our last day at the parks. It&amp;rsquo;s been a pretty eventful week. A bit tiring, but definitely memorable. Today we had reservations at EPCOT early, 4:45, so we planned on spending the day there again. There was a lot at this park that we haven&amp;rsquo;t yet done. Also, mom and dad really like the world showcase, so there seemed plenty to do for the entire family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disney Day 4</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/disney-day-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2008 22:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/disney-day-4/</guid>
      <description>Late Start Quin was up during the night and we were getting tired, so we slept in a little bit this morning. Jenny and I got out for a run around the 1.4 mile running path that goes around the resort (we went twice around), we gave the kids baths, then we grabbed a leisurely breakfast at the Shutters food court at our resort. It was a good jumping off point for the rest of the day, which we planned on spending at Animal Kingdom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disney Day 3</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/disney-day-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2008 21:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/disney-day-3/</guid>
      <description>Magic Kingdom Part II Today we decided to try something a little different. Rather than sleeping in and dealing with the crowds of people, we thought we&amp;rsquo;d leave a little early in hopes of getting on some more rides in less confined areas. So we took off early for the bus (OK, I think we still got on the bus around 9:00) and headed for the Magic Kingdom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disney Day 2</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/disney-day-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2008 22:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/disney-day-2/</guid>
      <description>Good Night&amp;rsquo;s Sleep Our first night in the hotel was blissfully uneventful. My biggest worry coming to this resort with an infant was that he would be up and unconsolable in the night and he would wake people up. Turns out I had nothing to worry about all along. In fact, I would say that Quin probably slept better at the hotel than he does at home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disney Day 1</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/disney-day-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2008 22:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/disney-day-1/</guid>
      <description>A Note on These Posts I&amp;rsquo;m doing these posts a little out of sequence. I&amp;rsquo;ve written notes as things happened, but I&amp;rsquo;m going back and filling in the blanks as I get time to write them. At times it may seem a bit disjointed, so please forgive me. The dates will be posted as though they occurred on the days in which the events actually occurred, however they will not be written or posted on those actual days.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Loose teeth and doctor&#39;s visits</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/loose-teeth-and-doctors-visits/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2008 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/loose-teeth-and-doctors-visits/</guid>
      <description>Today, Quin is 16 days old. Almost like his golden birthday in days! Jenny had to go in to work today, so Quin and I worked from home, and let me tell you, he does better work than some of the interns I&amp;rsquo;ve had! I fed him once at 7:00, then he didn&amp;rsquo;t want to eat again until around noon (my mistake as I got lost in e-mails for awhile).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bringing Quin home</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/bringing-quin-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2008 18:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/bringing-quin-home/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday we got the call that Quin was going to be discharged from the hospital. It was going to be later in the day, so we took Ethan out of school around 12:30 and headed over to the hospital. When we walked into the nursery, we were surprised to find two doctors circumcising Quin. We thought that had happened already in the morning! Well, it was somewhat interesting to watch, but Ethan was not so impressed.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>