<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Brandon on The Hydrant</title>
    <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/tags/brandon/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Brandon on The Hydrant</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 11:35:19 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://dogsbuttbrew.com/tags/brandon/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>So - I got a new job...</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/02/so-i-got-a-new-job.../</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 11:35:19 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/02/so-i-got-a-new-job.../</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It doesn&amp;rsquo;t happen very often, thankfully, but I started a new job this month! It also doesn&amp;rsquo;t happen very often that I blog about myself. Both good things, I think!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;At the beginning of February, I started a new job with Twilio. Headquartered in San Francisco, I&amp;rsquo;m actually working in Downtown Denver where one of the largest non-HQ offices is located. There are so many new things that I&amp;rsquo;m experiencing, which is sort of the point, I guess. For one, It&amp;rsquo;s been a long time since I&amp;rsquo;ve worked at a company with more than 500 employees (Twilio has ~3000). Also, it&amp;rsquo;s been a LONG time since I&amp;rsquo;ve worked downtown anywhere, and the first time I&amp;rsquo;ve worked in downtown Denver. The obvious complication is commuting, which is something I&amp;rsquo;m still experimenting with. Denver is progressive enough to have a Light Rail system, which I&amp;rsquo;ve been taking advantage of. Jenny&amp;rsquo;s actually been kind enough to ferry me between the house and the light rail station a few miles from our house, so even two weeks in I can already feel my driving skills start to erode!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
