<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Quinton on The Hydrant</title>
    <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/tags/quinton/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Quinton on The Hydrant</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 19:23:27 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://dogsbuttbrew.com/tags/quinton/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Weakest Part of Every System...</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2021/04/the-weakest-part-of-every-system.../</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 19:23:27 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2021/04/the-weakest-part-of-every-system.../</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In the movies it is popular to portray computer hackers as these happy-go-lucky nerds who are mainly interested in whether they &lt;em&gt;can&lt;/em&gt; do something rather than whether than &lt;em&gt;should&lt;/em&gt; do something. In the movies they typically get in over their head, or go up against a rival hacker gang and&amp;hellip; get in over their head.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the real world, it&amp;rsquo;s hard to say that computer hackers are the same as the way they are portraid in the movies - at least the movies I remember. Sure, they are smart folks. But more often than not, at least for the vast majority of the hacking attempts, they are looking to exploit people to get access to their personal information so they can sell it to another bad actor who will then try to profit from having that information. Oh, and &lt;em&gt;most&lt;/em&gt; of the time, hackers are targeting the weakest part of every system - human beings!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex... Explained...</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/04/sex...-explained.../</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 09:47:40 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/04/sex...-explained.../</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Over the past several nights, in the midst of our Corona Quarantine, Quinton and I have started watching the show Locke and Key on Netflix together. It&amp;rsquo;s a nice time for the two of us to hang out, watch a pretty well done, suspenseful show together, and have some interesting banter and conversation as a matter of course.  Last night, the episode was a little shorter than normal, and to be honest, our sleeping routines are starting to trend later on either end of the sleep equation, so after our episode was done, the next thing Netflix recommended for me to watch was a show called Sex Explained. Quinton looked at me with a little grin&amp;hellip; Being the designated sex educator in the family, I made a command decision that it would be a fine thing for him to watch, though I hadn&amp;rsquo;t watched it myself, so I had no idea what the content might be like. It was rated TV-MA (which Quinton still pronounces TV &amp;ldquo;mah&amp;rdquo;) afterall.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COVID Reality - Day 2-9</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/03/covid-reality-day-2-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 10:50:59 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/03/covid-reality-day-2-9/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;COVID Reality Day 6 was the Grady&amp;rsquo;s breaking point. There was widespread dissent in the ranks, and those that are supposed to be even and get us through all this were SUPER crabby. Mireille had a big tantrum the likes that I haven&amp;rsquo;t seen in quite awhile, Quinton managed to squeek out some tears at some point, Ethan is cooped up and wants to see his friends and his girlfriend, and Jenny and I were basically not on speaking terms with one another most of the day. We were on yelling terms, just not speaking terms. Today seems to be better. The saving grace is that it&amp;rsquo;s very nice outside - spring weather makes everything seem a little better.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COVID Reality - Day 1</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/03/covid-reality-day-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 08:50:41 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/03/covid-reality-day-1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Today is the first day of what I&amp;rsquo;m calling &amp;ldquo;COVID Reality.&amp;rdquo; In Colorado, while we aren&amp;rsquo;t ordered to &amp;ldquo;shelter in place,&amp;rdquo; anything that would be worthwhile leaving the house for has been closed down, most notably all sporting events, theaters, churches, restaurants, breweries, and bars. Oh, and schools. These closures are setup right now for 4 weeks. We&amp;rsquo;ll see how long it actually ends up being (I doubt &lt;em&gt;shorter&lt;/em&gt; than 4 weeks). So we&amp;rsquo;re getting to know our family better, for better or worse. I&amp;rsquo;m working from home, the kids are doing school from home, Ethan is doing college from home (they closed the campus for the rest of the year), and Jenny has had to take on the new jobs of teacher and principal in addition to Janitor, Laundress, and overall house CEO.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big Update on Grady Kids</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/01/big-update-on-grady-kids/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2020 09:25:40 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/01/big-update-on-grady-kids/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s a broken record on this blog, but it&amp;rsquo;s again been a LONG time since I&amp;rsquo;ve done anything. There is definitely an ebb and flow to my state of mind that really dictates how much I observe of the world around me, and around the end of the year is a time of reflection for lots of people. So here it goes&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This post is going to read mostly as a Quinton post. It&amp;rsquo;s not that I don&amp;rsquo;t love my other kids, he&amp;rsquo;s just at a point where the things he does crack me up more than what I&amp;rsquo;m observing from my other kids right now. Ethan, Mireille, forgive me!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Catching up to 2019</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/02/catching-up-to-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2019 17:00:42 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/02/catching-up-to-2019/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A new year&amp;hellip; It went and happened again, and again I find myself in the position of having a resolution of writing more. It seems a yearly concern, but here goes the latest attempt.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;2018 was very kind to the Grady&amp;rsquo;s. Ethan wrecked a couple of cars, but has now had his latest one for over 6 months without incident (knock on wood). Brandon got a new (to me) car in the form of a 2017 Chevy Malibu - yeah, I can&amp;rsquo;t seem to break that mold. Hey, they&amp;rsquo;re nice cars!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zazu</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/12/zazu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 14:48:10 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/12/zazu/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We added a new family member this weekend.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/6kl4ED5ZDHrieDhBgvzXocqKi4A1QreGuLoI1aLxT0RqNuE531kSBHa3ObLrH9FIH0pZuDINgdB1qzoKuZxNOHzQoxc5XwC-tI2JW8gRRNq6yOiQ1qbwf3sphyGHy893pq39kmaJXpY=w1194-h1590-no&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h4&gt;Zaz and Quinton&lt;/h4&gt; &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Say hello to &amp;ldquo;Zazu,&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;Zaz&amp;rdquo; as Quinton likes to call him. Quinton has really wanted a pet of his own for awhile now. He has been trying to get us to get another dog and for me to leave the dog alone so I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be the &amp;ldquo;alpha male&amp;rdquo; to this one like I am to Heinz.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moab</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/11/moab/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2018 19:58:19 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/11/moab/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-trip&#34;&gt;The Trip&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Moab. Or as Mireille would pronounce it, Mo-Ab. Small city of 5000 some people in Southeast Utah, the land of Mormons, backwards liquor laws, and some spectacular natural landscapes. Since we&amp;rsquo;ve moved to the west we&amp;rsquo;ve always looked for a reason to get out here to take in these sights. Thanks to some early travel by Mom and Pop Grady, having come through Denver the weekend prior for Thanksgiving day festivities, we finally had our opportunity to check it out over the Thanksgiving day weekend, figuring it wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be quite as busy or quite as hot as it would in the peak months.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mireille the Observer</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/11/mireille-the-observer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 10:10:26 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/11/mireille-the-observer/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Mireille is far and away the most observant of our children. Ethan&amp;rsquo;s not bad - far better than myself. Quinton, well, he and I are about in the same boat, and it&amp;rsquo;s not a good boat. Mireille will notice just about anything, even if it seems inconsequential. For example, Jenny occasionally colors her hair, but in a subtle way such that color blind me will not notice. Mireille does, though. The other day, Jenny swapped out the pulls on our dressers in our room, and the first thing Mireille said when she walked in the room was &amp;ldquo;when did you get new ones of these?&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Catching Up</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/09/miscellaneous-catching-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Sep 2018 08:52:45 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/09/miscellaneous-catching-up/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It’s been awhile on a couple of these, so I figured I should jot them down before time erodes them from my memory.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This first story has been getting good traction in my friend and colleague circles. Before I can tell the story, I need to tee it up a little bit. Quinton is obviously a black male being raised among “the whites.” From time to time that causes some conflict in him. He really likes the idea of exploring black culture, but acknowledges that he doesn’t know much about it. One thing he likes to do to try to dip his toe into it is to listen to rap music. While there is a very deep collection of amazing rap songs, many, many of them delve into topics or language that is just a little rough to continually barrage the ears of our five year old, and ten year old as well.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2018 Boy&#39;s Trip - Day 2</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/07/2018-boys-trip-day-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 20:50:03 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/07/2018-boys-trip-day-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;day-2&#34;&gt;Day 2&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We started the day slowly, as any good boy&amp;rsquo;s trip would. Since we didn&amp;rsquo;t go to bed until later, we slept in until after 8:00. I sort of wanted to get going, so I got up and started cooking half of our 2 pounds of bacon and a dozen eggs. The smell was enough to wake Ethan up by 8:30, mainly because the apartment was so full of smoke that I think he started suffocating. No matter, he was up.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2018 Boy&#39;s Trip</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/07/2018-boys-trip/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2018 20:29:30 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/07/2018-boys-trip/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;day-1&#34;&gt;Day 1&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here we sit at 521 Elm St. in historic Leadville, CO, our VRBO for the weekend. Ethan, Quinton, and I are doing our first &amp;ldquo;boy&amp;rsquo;s weekend.&amp;rdquo; It was hard leaving Jenny and Mireille behind, but we stayed the course and are going through with it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The trip up here was rougher than expected. Traffic out of Denver to the mountains via I70 was somehow worse than it normally would be when we are coming up to ski, but we persevered. We even took a slight detour going over Loveland Pass, a route that we normally cut short by 30 minutes by going through the Eisenhower tunnel, but this weekend is about adventure and doing things that we wouldn&amp;rsquo;t normally be able to do when the girls are around!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Honor Roll</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/03/honor-roll/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 12:42:11 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/03/honor-roll/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Last Wednesday, I was able to witness the St. Pius X 2nd Trimester Honor Roll ceremony, and my favorite middle child was among the honorees. Quinton achieved all A- or better in the last trimester. In fact, he got all A&amp;rsquo;s with the exception of one A- which he got in Art.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Congratulations, Quinton!!!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/P-EV9sE9rOIKWk_qnewG_KJ9N0mPtppQopCnCnmJ1iuDUdHJwbqaiS3ojWPgjtGlaT5IcEl7RxCuaSHBFy4QfKaWcTZYKrhvpg2eXTl2sYm_WFyfZ7F1P94Apr30aj7RPx7EsB4f448=w1896-h1422-no&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h4&gt;Quinton and the Gold Honor Roll&lt;/h4&gt; &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Oh, and just because she is adorable, here is a picture of Mireille in her new soccer uniform.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christmas with the Tibbetts</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/02/christmas-with-the-tibbetts/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2018 10:50:09 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/02/christmas-with-the-tibbetts/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We live in Colorado. Our families, by and large, still dwell in places throughout the Midwest. Year after year this generates some degree of conflict, particularly when it comes time for celebrating the holidays. For this holiday season, we celebrated Grady Christmas on the ever traditional weekend of the first weekend of November. For the Tibbett holiday celebration, then, we coordinated an early January celebration. Actually, it was planned to coincide with my 45th birthday, because who wouldn&amp;rsquo;t want to travel to the frigid midwest to stay in remote, rural Wisconsin with his in-laws on their 45th birthday!!!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elf on the Shelf</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/12/elf-on-the-shelf/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2017 18:45:01 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/12/elf-on-the-shelf/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;There are many traditions that I&amp;rsquo;ve learned of since leaving the nest that my family was either ignorant to or just didn&amp;rsquo;t celebrate. One happened this morning, and has for the last 21 years of my marriage, yet I still forget to celebrate it - St. Nicholas&amp;rsquo;s Day. Jenny celebrated it year after year, yet I did not, so even though I&amp;rsquo;ve now been in my adult life much longer than I was ever in my parents&amp;rsquo; home, I still forget&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A perfect parent&#39;s weekend...</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/09/a-perfect-parents-weekend.../</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2017 09:38:40 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/09/a-perfect-parents-weekend.../</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This was a couple of weeks ago now, so it&amp;rsquo;s not as fresh in my mind as it was when it happened, but the event was important enough that I think it warrants documentation. You see, this was Mireille&amp;rsquo;s fifth birthday, her second in the United States.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For the weeks leading up to September 9, Mireille has been asking on a regular basis about her birthday party. She really wanted to have a party, with a bounce castle, and a cake, and presents! Hopefully she wasn&amp;rsquo;t disappointed. The only thing we didn&amp;rsquo;t really have was a cake, but we had a whole bunch of cupcakes! She didn&amp;rsquo;t seem too impressed, though, because it wasn&amp;rsquo;t a cake!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summer is here!</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/06/summer-is-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 14:52:46 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/06/summer-is-here/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Summer is finally upon us. Last week was a full week without school, except for Mireille, but that&amp;rsquo;s daycare - even though she calls it school. The temperatures as of last Thursday definitely represented a shift into the ungodly hot area, though in Denver, if you can find shade, you are in good shape since the humidity is very comfortable. As a family we are definitely settling in more and more as the years have gone by.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Potpourri</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/01/potpourri/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2017 17:02:48 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/01/potpourri/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As is typical now a days, I find myself delinquent in my posting. I blame my new job. Nothing more. Oh, and having three kids is hard. Not sure I&amp;rsquo;ve mentioned that. Still, they keep us on our toes, and I occasionally remember to write some of the remarkable things down that they do. The following is a small collection of the things I&amp;rsquo;ve remembered.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;mireille&#34;&gt;Mireille&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;on-language&#34;&gt;&amp;hellip;on language&amp;hellip;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Mireille&amp;rsquo;s pronoun usage continues to improve, though her favorite pronoun continues to be &amp;ldquo;him.&amp;rdquo; The possessive form of her version of the &amp;ldquo;super pronoun&amp;rdquo; is &lt;strong&gt;him&amp;rsquo;s&lt;/strong&gt;. I don&amp;rsquo;t know where she heard the song, but the other day she started singing an adorable rendition of Sir Mix-A-Lot&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Baby Got Back,&amp;rdquo; or at least the beginning of it. Her&amp;rsquo;s, however, went like this.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2016 - The Year in Review - First Trimester</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/12/2016-the-year-in-review-first-trimester/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2016 18:55:09 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/12/2016-the-year-in-review-first-trimester/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I can remember one year when we did the traditional &amp;ldquo;Holiday Letter.&amp;rdquo; It was the year that we were in the process of trying to adopt Quinton, so we were &amp;ldquo;marketing ourselves&amp;rdquo; to our family and friends that year. Looking back, it was a fun letter to do, even if it was not necessary from the salesman side of house. I thought it would be fun to condense 2016 into a bit of a letter to our family (thank you both of my readers) and so that future versions of ourselves might enjoy reading it as well. So, here it goes!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The First Snow of the Year</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/11/the-first-snow-of-the-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2016 09:31:29 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/11/the-first-snow-of-the-year/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Last week it snowed in Denver for the first time this season. It&amp;rsquo;s a mixed bag out here for snow. People don&amp;rsquo;t really care for it in the city, like most places, but love when it happens in the mountains, where it is supposed to be. My kids certainly love it, at least the first snow.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Mireille has been saying &amp;ldquo;snow&amp;rsquo;s coming?&amp;rdquo; since about August when Jenny showed her some snow boots she could wear. When it finally snowed last week, I picked her up from school and the first thing she said was &amp;ldquo;it&amp;rsquo;s snowing!&amp;rdquo; As soon as we got home, she wormed her way into her snow pants, coat, boots, hat, and gloves and demanded that I come outside with her so she could play in the snow.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Bloggable Offense</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/11/a-bloggable-offense/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2016 09:22:02 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/11/a-bloggable-offense/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Quinton loves his iPad, and he loves video games. Those are his leisure time activities, which is a funny thing to say, leisure time for an 8 year old! What he really loves to do is to enjoy both of them at the same time, which is something we try to limit for various reasons. It also presents itself as an opportunity for us when dolling out discipline.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Last week, Quinton had some egregious issue for which he had to be punished. The worst thing we can do to him is to take away his iPad. Since this escalated, we had to not only take away his iPad, but also limit video games for the weekend. Because he is stubborn he still managed to get his iPad from time to time, so I took additional measures to actually take away his network access, which I can do from the wireless router. This was effective, for a time&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quick Updates</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/10/quick-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2016 10:18:11 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/10/quick-updates/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;After five days of adult vacation in New Orleans, Jenny and I were happy to be back with our kids, and probably a bit surprised that five days wasn&amp;rsquo;t quite enough to really decompress! Things went back to normal very quickly.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Mirielle gas been constantly about three things - now, trick or treating, and the party that she was going to yesterday. The snow things is pretty funny. I seem to remember her not liking it very much when it showed up last spring, but just about every day she will ask us, very seriously, &amp;ldquo;snow coming?&amp;rdquo; I think she mainly wants to wear her snow boots that she found in her closet. Having a girl is weird!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quinton&#39;s Last Track Meet</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/07/quintons-last-track-meet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2016 21:27:10 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/07/quintons-last-track-meet/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Quinton joined the Aurora Recreational Track Team this summer. We were excited about this particular activity because it would be something Quinton couldn&amp;rsquo;t just partially do. We find that, often times during soccer or basketball, Quinton is perfectly content to move at about half pace. He is bigger and faster than most of the kids he plays against in those sports, so if he plays about half way, he can still be competitive but not sweat too much. Not so much with track - there, he has to run his butt off to compete!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Life of a Single Father</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/06/life-of-a-single-father/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2016 21:43:24 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/06/life-of-a-single-father/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s 9:44 PM on Thursday evening. I&amp;rsquo;ve finally settled down to my computer and&#xA;a bomber of my local&amp;rsquo;s double IPA. It&amp;rsquo;s the first time today that I&amp;rsquo;ve been&#xA;able to sit without somebody demanding something or me having to be preparing&#xA;something for somebody. You see, Jenny has been traveling for work since Monday&#xA;morning, leaving me, a single father of three.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve been a single father in the past. There&amp;rsquo;s something much more complicated&#xA;about being a single father now-a-days, however. Not only is it three kids,&#xA;which even though we&amp;rsquo;ve added only one child, the apparent number of children&#xA;seems to have risen exponentially. No, it&amp;rsquo;s not &lt;em&gt;just&lt;/em&gt; the third child, but the&#xA;fact that the third child is a three year old black girl! Let me explain.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ACHC Camp and English</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/06/achc-camp-and-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2016 07:58:48 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/06/achc-camp-and-english/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Last weekend we had to opportunity to go to the African-Caribbean&#xA;Heritage Camp. It is one of a set of camps put on by an organization in town&#xA;here that focuses on transracially formed families, specifically formed through&#xA;adoption. Yeah, they have organizations for everything! We had been to the camp&#xA;once before, two years ago, and enjoyed it so much that we decided to move to&#xA;Denver!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Over the course of the two and a half days of camp we were all immersed with&#xA;people in a very similar situation to our family. There were many speakers&#xA;and round tables which were both thought provoking and frustrating (mainly&#xA;the round tables), but in the end it was a great experience for our family to&#xA;be around other families that look just like ours. That just doesn&amp;rsquo;t happen&#xA;very often!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quinton the Actor</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/05/quinton-the-actor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2016 14:15:12 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/05/quinton-the-actor/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;For some reason, Quinton has decided lately that he wants to be an actor. He feels&#xA;he could be rich, and feels that he&amp;rsquo;s every bit as good as the people he&amp;rsquo;s seen on&#xA;TV and movies.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Yesterday on our trip back from Colorado Springs where we were watching soccer,&#xA;Quinton was going into great detail about what would happen when he&amp;rsquo;s an actor. First&#xA;I told him that he&amp;rsquo;d probably need to hire an agent. He said fine, but when I told&#xA;him that he&amp;rsquo;d have to pay one, he changed his mind. Eventually he decided that he&#xA;could just have me be his agent. I&amp;rsquo;m sure he figures I have great Hollywood&#xA;connections and would make a great agent. Of course, he wouldn&amp;rsquo;t have to pay me&amp;hellip;&#xA;When confronted with the fact that I would still need to pay for things, he came up&#xA;with some clever thoughts. I could live with him, for one thing. Jenny and Mireille&#xA;would still live in our house, but he and I would live in his mansion. Then we could&#xA;have a Mustang to drive around in since we wouldn&amp;rsquo;t have anybody else to drive&#xA;around, and he doesn&amp;rsquo;t intend to have a girlfriend or anything. He did say we could&#xA;get a truck - you know, for long trips&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Happy Birthday Quinton!</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/02/happy-birthday-quinton/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2016 08:26:05 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/02/happy-birthday-quinton/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;8 years ago yesterday, we were given a call that Quinton&amp;rsquo;s birth mother was&#xA;going into labor. By 10:30 AM on this morning, 8 years ago, Quinton was born!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s hard to believe that it&amp;rsquo;s been 8 years. Looking back on the pictures, so&#xA;much has happened. He has grown so much, made us laugh, made us cry, asked so&#xA;many important questions, and taught us things we never thought we even needed&#xA;to know. I don&amp;rsquo;t think he will ever know how lucky we are to have him as part&#xA;of our lives.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Mission Viejo Elementary Football League</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/01/the-mission-viejo-elementary-football-league/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2016 08:08:47 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/01/the-mission-viejo-elementary-football-league/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m pretty sure I posted about Quinton&amp;rsquo;s recent obsession with Football in a&#xA;prior post or two. If not, let me just say that Quinton has fallen HARD for&#xA;football and all things about it. It&amp;rsquo;s to the point where he will actually put&#xA;down his iPad (gasp) and ask me to turn on a football game when he knows one&#xA;will be on. If you know Quinton, you know that is not something to take&#xA;lightly.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kids these days</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/12/kids-these-days/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2015 11:21:28 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/12/kids-these-days/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Most days are pretty much the same. I get up at 5:30, shower, get Ethan up at&#xA;6:00, make breakfast for us, then leave around 6:30 to get him to School. After&#xA;that I&amp;rsquo;m not sure what typically happens as Jenny just takes care of it. Well,&#xA;last week I had the opportunity to walk Quinton to school because Ethan had&#xA;final exams and would be getting done around the time Quinton would normally&#xA;be going to school.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thanksgiving, Colorado Style</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/12/thanksgiving-colorado-style/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2015 07:44:26 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/12/thanksgiving-colorado-style/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Our first major holiday in Colorado is my favorite of all holidays, Thanksgiving!&#xA;While it&amp;rsquo;s difficult to not be able to spend it with family, we were able to&#xA;make good memories of it by spending it in the Mountains at a ski resort. Hopefully&#xA;this is something we will make a tradition out of, because it was a lot of fun!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We went up on Wednesday and left a little early in hopes of beating the traffic&#xA;into the mountains. One thing you will hear from people that live in Colorado is&#xA;that going into the mountains, while awesome, is severely compromised by the&#xA;traffic on I70. At only 2 lanes for a long ways, many, MANY resorts to&#xA;service by that road, and unpredictable weather, it can be tricky to navigate.&#xA;We were lucky and made it up in the basic standard, about 90 minutes from our&#xA;house (maybe a little more, but it was in that general timeframe).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Kitchen Discovery</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/11/a-kitchen-discovery/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2015 20:55:58 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/11/a-kitchen-discovery/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re redoing our kitchen right now. I have a long post queued up for some time&#xA;in the near future to go through some of the experience and show pictures. It&amp;rsquo;s&#xA;been fun, but it&amp;rsquo;s also been interesting.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Last weekend we finally got to the point where we could take out our old&#xA;lower cabinets and replace them with the new ones. The plan was to demolish&#xA;on Saturday and install on Sunday. For the most part this went off without&#xA;a hitch.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quinton&#39;s Christmas List</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/11/quintons-christmas-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2015 08:38:04 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/11/quintons-christmas-list/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Jenny had Quinton write a letter to Santa. Since he was also typing a thank&#xA;you letter to his grandparents on my e-mail, he decided to e-mail his letter&#xA;to Santa this year. I came across it in my drafts folder and found it amusing.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;dear santa i want a ps vita a dirt bike a soccer ball a trampoline football&#xA;gear mostly a dirt bike and a ps vita and halo 5 and ps 4 and 100 dollars and&#xA;a golden retreiver.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quinton and Fun With Words</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/11/quinton-and-fun-with-words/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2015 19:21:14 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/11/quinton-and-fun-with-words/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;New words for the dictionary:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;becept /bee * &amp;lsquo;cept/&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Origin - from what I can tell, a combination of except and besides. Perfectly&#xA;encapsulates the meaning of both in different situations.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Example: &amp;ldquo;Everyone is having fun becept me.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;w&amp;rsquo;bout /wuh * &amp;lsquo;bout/&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Origin - shortened version of &amp;ldquo;what about.&amp;rdquo; Not particularly interesting for&#xA;its meaning but rather it&amp;rsquo;s usage.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Example: &amp;ldquo;The moon doesn&amp;rsquo;t have it&amp;rsquo;s own light - it only reflects the sun&amp;rsquo;s&#xA;light.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>There, I Fixed It</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/10/there-i-fixed-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2015 21:34:14 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/10/there-i-fixed-it/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Quinton has really wanted a remote control airplane for quite some time. Uncle&#xA;Blaine bought him a remote control helicopter a little over a year ago that&#xA;he absolutely loved for the entirety of the 10 minutes before he lost it in&#xA;the trees. Over the years he&amp;rsquo;s amassed quite the aresnal of cheap, crappy&#xA;remote control things - cars, trucks, motorcycles - each one cheaper and&#xA;crappier than the last. So when he continually asked for an airplane, I continually&#xA;managed to push him off.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hide and Seek</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/10/hide-and-seek/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2015 09:52:05 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/10/hide-and-seek/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s hard to play Hide and Seek when you have a dog&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where the hell did they put them?</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/where-the-hell-did-they-put-them/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2008 21:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/where-the-hell-did-they-put-them/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Time is flying by.  Quin is starting to get more and more independent, which is nice as he was being a bit clingy for awhile there.  He is very good at rolling and can sometimes even roll from his back to his stomach.  His latest trick is to stay in a seated position if we put him in one to start with.  He&amp;rsquo;s also reaching for toys and other things that are out of reach, which I&amp;rsquo;m told is a developmental milestone.  So way to go, Quin.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
