<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kids on The Hydrant</title>
    <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/tags/kids/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Kids on The Hydrant</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 12:42:11 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://dogsbuttbrew.com/tags/kids/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Honor Roll</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/03/honor-roll/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 12:42:11 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/03/honor-roll/</guid>
      <description>Last Wednesday, I was able to witness the St. Pius X 2nd Trimester Honor Roll ceremony, and my favorite middle child was among the honorees. Quinton achieved all A- or better in the last trimester. In fact, he got all A&amp;rsquo;s with the exception of one A- which he got in Art.
Congratulations, Quinton!!!
  Quinton and the Gold Honor Roll   Oh, and just because she is adorable, here is a picture of Mireille in her new soccer uniform.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas with the Tibbetts</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/02/christmas-with-the-tibbetts/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2018 10:50:09 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/02/christmas-with-the-tibbetts/</guid>
      <description>We live in Colorado. Our families, by and large, still dwell in places throughout the Midwest. Year after year this generates some degree of conflict, particularly when it comes time for celebrating the holidays. For this holiday season, we celebrated Grady Christmas on the ever traditional weekend of the first weekend of November. For the Tibbett holiday celebration, then, we coordinated an early January celebration. Actually, it was planned to coincide with my 45th birthday, because who wouldn&amp;rsquo;t want to travel to the frigid midwest to stay in remote, rural Wisconsin with his in-laws on their 45th birthday!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elf on the Shelf</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/12/elf-on-the-shelf/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2017 18:45:01 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/12/elf-on-the-shelf/</guid>
      <description>There are many traditions that I&amp;rsquo;ve learned of since leaving the nest that my family was either ignorant to or just didn&amp;rsquo;t celebrate. One happened this morning, and has for the last 21 years of my marriage, yet I still forget to celebrate it - St. Nicholas&amp;rsquo;s Day. Jenny celebrated it year after year, yet I did not, so even though I&amp;rsquo;ve now been in my adult life much longer than I was ever in my parents&amp;rsquo; home, I still forget&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thanksgiving 2017</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/12/thanksgiving-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2017 12:16:24 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/12/thanksgiving-2017/</guid>
      <description>Thanksgiving is literally my favorite holiday. I just love getting together with family and friends, cooking a delicious meal, eating said meal, just hanging out and napping with people. I think even more than Christmas, it is the most relaxing holiday out there!
This year, having already done the &amp;ldquo;Grady Christmas&amp;rdquo; several weeks earlier, our plan was to stay put for Thanksgiving. Luckily there are others in the greater Denver metropolitan area that are also too far away to spend the day with family, so they became our extended family for Thanksgiving.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A perfect parent&#39;s weekend...</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/09/a-perfect-parents-weekend.../</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2017 09:38:40 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/09/a-perfect-parents-weekend.../</guid>
      <description>This was a couple of weeks ago now, so it&amp;rsquo;s not as fresh in my mind as it was when it happened, but the event was important enough that I think it warrants documentation. You see, this was Mireille&amp;rsquo;s fifth birthday, her second in the United States.
For the weeks leading up to September 9, Mireille has been asking on a regular basis about her birthday party. She really wanted to have a party, with a bounce castle, and a cake, and presents!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mireille Funnies</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/09/mireille-funnies/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 11:52:46 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/09/mireille-funnies/</guid>
      <description>Jenny was talking to Mireille on Sunday about things that girls talk about. I wasn&amp;rsquo;t privvy to the details of the entire conversation, because that wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be appropriate - I&amp;rsquo;m a boy. One little nugget Jenny shared with me was when Mireille admitted to her, &amp;ldquo;I wish I was a unicorn. But I&amp;rsquo;m just Mireille&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;
Then, yesterday, our little Unicorn proved she listens and absorbs way more than she ever lets on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Colorado Adventure Series - Snow Mountain Ranch Day 4</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/08/colorado-adventure-series---snow-mountain-ranch-day-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2017 17:52:46 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/08/colorado-adventure-series---snow-mountain-ranch-day-4/</guid>
      <description>Day 4 Today started out much the same as the last. I got up &amp;ldquo;early&amp;rdquo; and headed out for a quick run around the campus. The main difference today was that Ethan decided he would come with me! He&amp;rsquo;s training for soccer and was supposed to run 5 miles over the weekend. He decided that 3.2 at 9000 feet was a rough equivalent of 5 at 5280, which I&amp;rsquo;m inclined to agree with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Colorado Adventure Series - Snow Mountain Ranch Day 3</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/08/colorado-adventure-series---snow-mountain-ranch-day-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2017 16:52:46 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/08/colorado-adventure-series---snow-mountain-ranch-day-3/</guid>
      <description>Day 3 Day three started out later than day 2. With nothing really pushing us out of bed, the room slept in. I got up &amp;ldquo;early&amp;rdquo; around 7:00 or so and circumnavigated the property on a &amp;ldquo;run&amp;rdquo; of sorts. Not sure you can really call it a run. Jogging occured, but a lot of walking also occurred. It was very brisk to start the day, at only 36 degF, and a bit of fog made it a little spooky, but it was good to get out and about and get the blood pumping earlyish.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Colorado Adventure Series - Snow Mountain Ranch Day 2</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/08/colorado-adventure-series---snow-mountain-ranch-day-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2017 21:52:46 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/08/colorado-adventure-series---snow-mountain-ranch-day-2/</guid>
      <description>Day 2 Our first full day of vacation! Today is exciting because it will be most of our first time whitewater rafting. We were to be in Kremmling, about 45 miles away, by 8:30 for our half day whitewater rafting adventure. So we set an alarm for 6:30, which was fine with everybody considering we were all in bed early the night before, got dressed, had breakfast at the cafeteria, and headed west on 40 to the bustling metropolis of Kremmling via Granby.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Colorado Adventure Series - Snow Mountain Ranch Day 1</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/08/colorado-adventure-series---snow-mountain-ranch-day-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2017 20:52:46 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/08/colorado-adventure-series---snow-mountain-ranch-day-1/</guid>
      <description>Prelude When we first moved to Colorado two years ago, we made a point of being &amp;ldquo;tourists in our own state.&amp;rdquo; It seems so often that we live somewhere and never really get to experience it like somebody who visits. Life always seems to catch up with us. Lord Soccer demands attention, work, school, the house&amp;hellip; It&amp;rsquo;s a never ending cycle of demands on our time. So we&amp;rsquo;ve tried to keep it more fresh here in Colorado, since there is so much to see out here (despite there not being any measurable amount of recreational water anywhere out here).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mireille&#39;s English Progression</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/05/mireilles-english-progression/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2017 15:18:41 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/05/mireilles-english-progression/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been over a year, and Mireille continues to grow and develop. Outside of some difficulties in identifying colors (something I can&amp;rsquo;t really fault her here) and a current disinterest in letters or numbers, she&amp;rsquo;s developing quite on par with what I would expect. She does continue to have some interesting phrases, usages, and interactions from time to time that merit documentation.
Recently she has started using a phrase whenever people do something that she really doesn&amp;rsquo;t understand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>October 2016 - Big Update!</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/10/october-2016---big-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2016 19:39:06 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/10/october-2016---big-update/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s October! October has been a busy month, but what month hasn&amp;rsquo;t been, really. So it&amp;rsquo;s been awhile since there&amp;rsquo;s been an update of much substance. So, while my family answers the door to greet and treat Halloween visitors in full costume, I thought I would take a few minutes (or 60) and update the world on the goings on in the Grady Household.
Adoption - Complete I don&amp;rsquo;t have to restate how much work and waiting it&amp;rsquo;s been to complete this, our second adoption.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Sh!tty Morning</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/03/a-shtty-morning/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2016 07:40:04 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/03/a-shtty-morning/</guid>
      <description>Mireille&amp;rsquo;s been home with us for two weeks today. Many of you are probably looking for some post that goes through that in some detail. This is not that post. I&amp;rsquo;m working up a larger post, but interestingly, going from two to three kids, and having that new kid be 3.5 years old, well, it changes how you can spend your time. Ah, material for another post. This post deals with an acute familial incident that happened to involve the entire family in one way or another&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>