<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kids on The Hydrant</title>
    <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/tags/kids/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Kids on The Hydrant</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 13:00:03 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://dogsbuttbrew.com/tags/kids/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Naughty</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2023/07/naughty/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 13:00:03 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2023/07/naughty/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Apparently all my kids are naughty! In the online world, dealing with bullies and hate speech is constantly a topic. It&amp;rsquo;s very easy in an anonymized world to pop off to people in ways that you might not if you were in the same room. Quinton has shown us that for years, though he was pretty inventive about it. At one point, I think he had 5 or 6 different free email addresses that he would use to sign back up for services that he got banned from because he was bullying or harassing people. I never in my life thought that my demure, perfect little daughter would be up to the same shenanigans&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best Mother So Far</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2023/06/best-mother-so-far/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 14:43:30 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2023/06/best-mother-so-far/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;One of the best parts of being a parent, in my estimation, is watching my kids&amp;rsquo; sense of humor develop. Early on, it&amp;rsquo;s at once fun and annoying to watch them try new things out and see what type of reaction they get. The annoying part comes with things like the constant use of the word &amp;ldquo;diarhea&amp;rdquo; that Mireille currently thinks is funny. The fun part, though, is seeing Ethan tell his grandmother, who had recently burst a blood vessel in her eye, that she could potentially remediate it with a quick trip to the Halloween Store.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hair</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2023/05/hair/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 09:38:11 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2023/05/hair/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hair is really important to my daughter. This is something I learned early on in her life with us. When she came to us from Congo, she had extensions in her hair and, though she coudln&amp;rsquo;t say anything in English, she conveyed very clearly that she liked them. She wasn&amp;rsquo;t very happy when we took them out a few days later (well, she wasn&amp;rsquo;t very happy about anything, really).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Over the years, she has been very vocal about wanting long hair and the types of things she would do with it. Jenny has done wonders caring for Mireille&amp;rsquo;s hair, but there&amp;rsquo;s just not much you can do with hair as curly as hers to make it long like she wanted it!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Catching up</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2023/04/catching-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 20:12:26 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2023/04/catching-up/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s been a minute&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Today, Bryce introduced me to a friend of his that is planning an RV trip. Rather than just answering a bunch of questions, I pointed him to this blog, which caused me to go back and re-read it, which reminded me how much fun it was to have these things written down. So here we are.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Well, what&amp;rsquo;s happened&amp;hellip; Oh, I got laid off! Yeah, the great startup experiment didn&amp;rsquo;t go the way I had hoped. I mean, I really enjoyed working there, and the pace of work was a lot of fun and all, but the downturn in the market along with the introduction of &lt;a href=&#34;https://openai.com/blog/chatgpt&#34;&gt;ChatGPT&lt;/a&gt;, as well as ALL of the tech companies laying people off, combined for the perfect storm to mean that I got to experience my very first layoff from the &lt;em&gt;being&lt;/em&gt; layed off perspective. I have to say, not a fan. Anyway, after 87 interviews with more than 20 companies, I finally landed at &lt;a href=&#34;https://tempo.io&#34;&gt;Tempo Software&lt;/a&gt; and I couldn&amp;rsquo;t be happier. The product mix is really quite interesting to me - they deal in Agile planning and tracking tools, which are things that I really enjoy working with!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mary the Tooth Fairy</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/06/mary-the-tooth-fairy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 13:03:38 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/06/mary-the-tooth-fairy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Parenting can be hard, obviously. And sometimes we (read I) don&amp;rsquo;t really live up to the challenge. I&amp;rsquo;m hoping this has happened to others&amp;hellip; The last time Mireille lost a tooth was in January. For Mireille, losing a tooth is a somewhat difficult exercise. For some reason, her teeth are very stubborn, and new teeth come up all over the place and don&amp;rsquo;t always displace the tooth they are supposed to replace! So for a few of her teeth, I&amp;rsquo;ve tried my dad-best to extract them, only to end up in tears (both of us, actually), and she&amp;rsquo;s had to go to the dentist to get them out. That&amp;rsquo;s what had happened in January the last time she lost one!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mireille the Observer</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/11/mireille-the-observer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 10:10:26 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/11/mireille-the-observer/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Mireille is far and away the most observant of our children. Ethan&amp;rsquo;s not bad - far better than myself. Quinton, well, he and I are about in the same boat, and it&amp;rsquo;s not a good boat. Mireille will notice just about anything, even if it seems inconsequential. For example, Jenny occasionally colors her hair, but in a subtle way such that color blind me will not notice. Mireille does, though. The other day, Jenny swapped out the pulls on our dressers in our room, and the first thing Mireille said when she walked in the room was &amp;ldquo;when did you get new ones of these?&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Honor Roll</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/03/honor-roll/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 12:42:11 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/03/honor-roll/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Last Wednesday, I was able to witness the St. Pius X 2nd Trimester Honor Roll ceremony, and my favorite middle child was among the honorees. Quinton achieved all A- or better in the last trimester. In fact, he got all A&amp;rsquo;s with the exception of one A- which he got in Art.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Congratulations, Quinton!!!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/P-EV9sE9rOIKWk_qnewG_KJ9N0mPtppQopCnCnmJ1iuDUdHJwbqaiS3ojWPgjtGlaT5IcEl7RxCuaSHBFy4QfKaWcTZYKrhvpg2eXTl2sYm_WFyfZ7F1P94Apr30aj7RPx7EsB4f448=w1896-h1422-no&#34;&#xA;   height=400px &#xA;  &#xA;  /&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h4&gt;Quinton and the Gold Honor Roll&lt;/h4&gt; &#xA;  &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Oh, and just because she is adorable, here is a picture of Mireille in her new soccer uniform.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christmas with the Tibbetts</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/02/christmas-with-the-tibbetts/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2018 10:50:09 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/02/christmas-with-the-tibbetts/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We live in Colorado. Our families, by and large, still dwell in places throughout the Midwest. Year after year this generates some degree of conflict, particularly when it comes time for celebrating the holidays. For this holiday season, we celebrated Grady Christmas on the ever traditional weekend of the first weekend of November. For the Tibbett holiday celebration, then, we coordinated an early January celebration. Actually, it was planned to coincide with my 45th birthday, because who wouldn&amp;rsquo;t want to travel to the frigid midwest to stay in remote, rural Wisconsin with his in-laws on their 45th birthday!!!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elf on the Shelf</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/12/elf-on-the-shelf/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2017 18:45:01 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/12/elf-on-the-shelf/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;There are many traditions that I&amp;rsquo;ve learned of since leaving the nest that my family was either ignorant to or just didn&amp;rsquo;t celebrate. One happened this morning, and has for the last 21 years of my marriage, yet I still forget to celebrate it - St. Nicholas&amp;rsquo;s Day. Jenny celebrated it year after year, yet I did not, so even though I&amp;rsquo;ve now been in my adult life much longer than I was ever in my parents&amp;rsquo; home, I still forget&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thanksgiving 2017</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/12/thanksgiving-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2017 12:16:24 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/12/thanksgiving-2017/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Thanksgiving is literally my favorite holiday. I just love getting together with family and friends, cooking a delicious meal, eating said meal, just hanging out and napping with people. I think even more than Christmas, it is the most relaxing holiday out there!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This year, having already done the &amp;ldquo;Grady Christmas&amp;rdquo; several weeks earlier, our plan was to stay put for Thanksgiving. Luckily there are others in the greater Denver metropolitan area that are also too far away to spend the day with family, so they became our extended family for Thanksgiving. On the menu was the traditional Thanksgiving faire, turkey, rolls, potatoes and gravy, stuffing, scalloped corn, pie (lots of pie), macaronni and cheese, gouda roll-ups, bean dip - you know, the traditional stuff! One of the reasons I like hosting so much is because I get to keep the leftovers, so I planned ahead. For the nine people that were at our meal we cooked 28 pounds of turkey!!!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A perfect parent&#39;s weekend...</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/09/a-perfect-parents-weekend.../</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2017 09:38:40 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/09/a-perfect-parents-weekend.../</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This was a couple of weeks ago now, so it&amp;rsquo;s not as fresh in my mind as it was when it happened, but the event was important enough that I think it warrants documentation. You see, this was Mireille&amp;rsquo;s fifth birthday, her second in the United States.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For the weeks leading up to September 9, Mireille has been asking on a regular basis about her birthday party. She really wanted to have a party, with a bounce castle, and a cake, and presents! Hopefully she wasn&amp;rsquo;t disappointed. The only thing we didn&amp;rsquo;t really have was a cake, but we had a whole bunch of cupcakes! She didn&amp;rsquo;t seem too impressed, though, because it wasn&amp;rsquo;t a cake!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mireille Funnies</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/09/mireille-funnies/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 11:52:46 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/09/mireille-funnies/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Jenny was talking to Mireille on Sunday about things that girls talk about. I wasn&amp;rsquo;t privvy to the details of the entire conversation, because that wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be appropriate - I&amp;rsquo;m a boy. One little nugget Jenny shared with me was when Mireille admitted to her, &amp;ldquo;I wish I was a unicorn. But I&amp;rsquo;m just Mireille&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Then, yesterday, our little Unicorn proved she listens and absorbs way more than she ever lets on. Since moving to Colorado we&amp;rsquo;ve had some difficulty adapting to the local colloqualisms. It&amp;rsquo;s not too different here, but the differences that do exist between here and Milwaukee are hard, particularly for adults. The one that seems most stubborn for Jenny and I is calling the last meal of the day dinner (CO) instead of supper (WI). Any time Jenny will say it in front of Maylee, she will make a big deal of correcting her. Just yesterday, Jenny and I were sitting on our newly completed deck with Mireille and discussing what we should do for supper. Mireille looked seriously at Jenny and said quietly, &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s dinner mom, not supper.&amp;rdquo; Maylee is so proud, and now I am double thinking anything I say in front of her.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colorado Adventure Series - Snow Mountain Ranch Day 4</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/08/colorado-adventure-series-snow-mountain-ranch-day-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2017 17:52:46 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/08/colorado-adventure-series-snow-mountain-ranch-day-4/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;day-4&#34;&gt;Day 4&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Today started out much the same as the last. I got up &amp;ldquo;early&amp;rdquo; and headed out for a quick run around the campus. The main difference today was that Ethan decided he would come with me! He&amp;rsquo;s training for soccer and was supposed to run 5 miles over the weekend. He decided that 3.2 at 9000 feet was a rough equivalent of 5 at 5280, which I&amp;rsquo;m inclined to agree with.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colorado Adventure Series - Snow Mountain Ranch Day 3</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/08/colorado-adventure-series-snow-mountain-ranch-day-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2017 16:52:46 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/08/colorado-adventure-series-snow-mountain-ranch-day-3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;day-3&#34;&gt;Day 3&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Day three started out later than day 2. With nothing really pushing us out of bed, the room slept in. I got up &amp;ldquo;early&amp;rdquo; around 7:00 or so and circumnavigated the property on a &amp;ldquo;run&amp;rdquo; of sorts. Not sure you can really call it a run. Jogging occured, but a lot of walking also occurred. It was very brisk to start the day, at only 36 degF, and a bit of fog made it a little spooky, but it was good to get out and about and get the blood pumping earlyish. As part of my run I found the Heritage farm, a turn of the century farm that has been preserved and now they hold horse riding breakfasts there. There are also some llamas there. The nicest part was the view from Piano Prairie, though. Framed just right, you could almost imagine what it might look like if there were no roads or dwellings of any kind.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colorado Adventure Series - Snow Mountain Ranch Day 2</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/08/colorado-adventure-series-snow-mountain-ranch-day-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2017 21:52:46 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/08/colorado-adventure-series-snow-mountain-ranch-day-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;day-2&#34;&gt;Day 2&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our first full day of vacation! Today is exciting because it will be most of our first time whitewater rafting. We were to be in Kremmling, about 45 miles away, by 8:30 for our half day whitewater rafting adventure. So we set an alarm for 6:30, which was fine with everybody considering we were all in bed &lt;strong&gt;early&lt;/strong&gt; the night before, got dressed, had breakfast at the cafeteria, and headed west on 40 to the bustling metropolis of Kremmling via Granby. Fortunately for Jenny, we quickly passed a Starbucks at a City Market in Granby so she was able to feed her addiction while in deep rural Colorado.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colorado Adventure Series - Snow Mountain Ranch Day 1</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/08/colorado-adventure-series-snow-mountain-ranch-day-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2017 20:52:46 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/08/colorado-adventure-series-snow-mountain-ranch-day-1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;prelude&#34;&gt;Prelude&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When we first moved to Colorado two years ago, we made a point of being &amp;ldquo;tourists in our own state.&amp;rdquo; It seems so often that we live somewhere and never really get to experience it like somebody who visits. Life always seems to catch up with us. Lord Soccer demands attention, work, school, the house&amp;hellip; It&amp;rsquo;s a never ending cycle of demands on our time. So we&amp;rsquo;ve tried to keep it more fresh here in Colorado, since there is so much to see out here (despite there not being any measurable amount of recreational water anywhere out here).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mireille&#39;s English Progression</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/05/mireilles-english-progression/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2017 15:18:41 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/05/mireilles-english-progression/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s been over a year, and Mireille continues to grow and develop. Outside of some difficulties in identifying colors (something I can&amp;rsquo;t really fault her here) and a current disinterest in letters or numbers, she&amp;rsquo;s developing quite on par with what I would expect. She does continue to have some interesting phrases, usages, and interactions from time to time that merit documentation.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Recently she has started using a phrase whenever people do something that she really doesn&amp;rsquo;t understand. Not that she doesn&amp;rsquo;t understand what they are saying or doing, but doesn&amp;rsquo;t understand why a person would do that in the first place! As you can imagine, this is something that happens a lot with her American family, particularly her dense father and brothers. The phrase she attributes to this is, &amp;ldquo;What your problem is?&amp;rdquo; The look on her face is impossible to properly document, but it&amp;rsquo;s pretty hilarious any time she does it - funny enough that it hasn&amp;rsquo;t started bothering me quite yet.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>October 2016 - Big Update!</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/10/october-2016-big-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2016 19:39:06 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/10/october-2016-big-update/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s October! October has been a busy month, but what month hasn&amp;rsquo;t been, really. So it&amp;rsquo;s been awhile since there&amp;rsquo;s been an update of much substance. So, while my family answers the door to greet and treat Halloween visitors in full costume, I thought I would take a few minutes (or 60) and update the world on the goings on in the Grady Household.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;adoption---complete&#34;&gt;Adoption - Complete&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;rsquo;t have to restate how much work and waiting it&amp;rsquo;s been to complete this, our second adoption. It&amp;rsquo;s been long. This past Friday, though, we hit a big milestone. Mireille had her day in court, and she is now officially adopted in the United States, meaning she if officially a Grady! I wish that meant we were all done! But alas, this is yet another milestone. It marks our ability to complete more paperwork, and pay out more money for interesting new bureaucratic processes. But, it is a reason to celebrate, at least for the fact that this part of the process has come to a close.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Sh!tty Morning</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/03/a-shtty-morning/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2016 07:40:04 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/03/a-shtty-morning/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Mireille&amp;rsquo;s been home with us for two weeks today. Many of you are probably&#xA;looking for some post that goes through that in some detail. This is not that&#xA;post. I&amp;rsquo;m working up a larger post, but interestingly, going from two to three&#xA;kids, and having that new kid be 3.5 years old, well, it changes how you can&#xA;spend your time. Ah, material for another post. This post deals with an&#xA;acute familial incident that happened to involve the entire family in one way&#xA;or another&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
