<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>TMI on The Hydrant</title>
    <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/tags/tmi/</link>
    <description>Recent content in TMI on The Hydrant</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2014 11:22:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://dogsbuttbrew.com/tags/tmi/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Quin Quickies</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/quin-quickies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2014 11:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/quin-quickies/</guid>
      <description>The Circumcision This weekend, my brother-in-law turned 50 and we were invited to his party. On the 30 minute drive to his house, Jenny and I were behaving like the good parents that we are and allowing the kids to listen to the Comedy Central channel on Sirius Satellite Radio, something of which we are currently enjoying a free trial. The content on the station isn&amp;rsquo;t all that, well, appropriate, but we count on the kids not listening much like they don&amp;rsquo;t listen to us - ever.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Little Quinny</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/little-quinny/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2012 21:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/little-quinny/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever heard the &amp;ldquo;Little Johnny&amp;rdquo; jokes? For several reasons, I have a feeling that they might one day be replaced by &amp;ldquo;Little Quinny&amp;rdquo; jokes. Here&amp;rsquo;s an example of one - Little Johnny was in class learning his ABCs. The teacher was asking the class to name something with each letter of the alphabet in order. Little Johnny raised his hand for each letter, but she kept skipping him thinking that he would say something bad, like &amp;ldquo;ass&amp;rdquo; for A and &amp;ldquo;butt&amp;rdquo; for B.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quinnie Quickie - TMI</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/quinnie-quickie---tmi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2011 21:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/quinnie-quickie---tmi/</guid>
      <description>File this one under TMI (that&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;too much information&amp;rdquo; for those not in the know). I believe I&amp;rsquo;ve discussed how Quin and I have pee races in this blog in the past. On Friday I went on a field trip with Ethan, and to make a very long story much shorter, I didn&amp;rsquo;t have much to drink during the day. When I got home, Quin wanted to have a pee race.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
