<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Hydrant</title>
    <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on The Hydrant</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2020 09:03:44 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://dogsbuttbrew.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>College - Year 2</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/09/college-year-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2020 09:03:44 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/09/college-year-2/</guid>
      <description>Ahh, COVID. I guess life goes on, or we try to do so, anyway. Ethan, after spending the last 5+ months at home (bonus Ethan time for us!) has now completed his transfer to Colorado State University and we have moved him into his dwelling for the upcoming school year! Even though this is Ethan&amp;rsquo;s second year of school, this year seemed almost worse in some ways than moving him in last year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mary the Tooth Fairy</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/06/mary-the-tooth-fairy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 13:03:38 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/06/mary-the-tooth-fairy/</guid>
      <description>Parenting can be hard, obviously. And sometimes we (read I) don&amp;rsquo;t really live up to the challenge. I&amp;rsquo;m hoping this has happened to others&amp;hellip; The last time Mireille lost a tooth was in January. For Mireille, losing a tooth is a somewhat difficult exercise. For some reason, her teeth are very stubborn, and new teeth come up all over the place and don&amp;rsquo;t always displace the tooth they are supposed to replace!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mireille&#39;s Channel - Peace Out!</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/05/mireilles-channel-peace-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2020 09:03:58 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/05/mireilles-channel-peace-out/</guid>
      <description>For the vast majority of this blog&amp;rsquo;s audience (Hi mom and dad!), you probably don&amp;rsquo;t know much about the Youtube generation and what types of things go on here. I can&amp;rsquo;t say I know much more outside of what I observe from my children as they are interacting with these sites, but let me try to explain. In today&amp;rsquo;s day and age, being a &amp;ldquo;Youtuber&amp;rdquo; is an actual profession that people aspire towards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mireille, the runner and COVID haircuts</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/04/mireille-the-runner-and-covid-haircuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Apr 2020 09:14:58 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/04/mireille-the-runner-and-covid-haircuts/</guid>
      <description>And it continues&amp;hellip;
I believe we are about 8 weeks in to this new reality now. Funny how initially I had all these ideas of things I would do &amp;ldquo;every day&amp;rdquo; during this situation. I was going to blog every day, that seemed like a funny and interesting idea. I was also going to draw something every day, which was fun for awhile, and I&amp;rsquo;ve continued it on a far less frequent basis, but I&amp;rsquo;m definitely not doing anything on a daily basis other than just living.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sex... Explained...</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/04/sex...-explained.../</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 09:47:40 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/04/sex...-explained.../</guid>
      <description>Over the past several nights, in the midst of our Corona Quarantine, Quinton and I have started watching the show Locke and Key on Netflix together. It&amp;rsquo;s a nice time for the two of us to hang out, watch a pretty well done, suspenseful show together, and have some interesting banter and conversation as a matter of course. Last night, the episode was a little shorter than normal, and to be honest, our sleeping routines are starting to trend later on either end of the sleep equation, so after our episode was done, the next thing Netflix recommended for me to watch was a show called Sex Explained.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>COVID Reality - Day 2-9</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/03/covid-reality-day-2-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 10:50:59 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/03/covid-reality-day-2-9/</guid>
      <description>COVID Reality Day 6 was the Grady&amp;rsquo;s breaking point. There was widespread dissent in the ranks, and those that are supposed to be even and get us through all this were SUPER crabby. Mireille had a big tantrum the likes that I haven&amp;rsquo;t seen in quite awhile, Quinton managed to squeek out some tears at some point, Ethan is cooped up and wants to see his friends and his girlfriend, and Jenny and I were basically not on speaking terms with one another most of the day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>COVID Reality - Day 1</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/2020-03-covid-reality-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 08:50:41 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/2020-03-covid-reality-1/</guid>
      <description>Today is the first day of what I&amp;rsquo;m calling &amp;ldquo;COVID Reality.&amp;rdquo; In Colorado, while we aren&amp;rsquo;t ordered to &amp;ldquo;shelter in place,&amp;rdquo; anything that would be worthwhile leaving the house for has been closed down, most notably all sporting events, theaters, churches, restaurants, breweries, and bars. Oh, and schools. These closures are setup right now for 4 weeks. We&amp;rsquo;ll see how long it actually ends up being (I doubt shorter than 4 weeks).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spring Break - COVID-19 Edition - Chapter 4 - Home</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/2020-03-sringbreak-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 19:39:41 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/2020-03-sringbreak-4/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;re cutting our vacation short! Today was originally supposed to be the day we took a trip on the narrow gauge railroad, but alas, they canceled their trips starting today. We were then going to go up to Telluride to take in the scenery there as well as do some snowmobiling, but threats of weather in the mountains and continued restaurant closures convinced us otherwise. As I write this, the county in which Telluride resides has just issued a &amp;ldquo;Shelter In Place&amp;rdquo; order, which is even more reason to be happy we didn&amp;rsquo;t end up there this morning!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spring Break - COVID-19 Edition - Chapter 3 - Closed</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/03/spring-break-covid-19-edition-chapter-3-closed/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 19:39:41 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/03/spring-break-covid-19-edition-chapter-3-closed/</guid>
      <description>Happy St. Patrick&amp;rsquo;s Day!!!
We had a plan for the day, but we needed first to get some breakfast. That would come in the form of McDonalds and Starbucks, both of which were open, but neither of which would allow you to eat or consume there, abiding by the governor&amp;rsquo;s orders! Quinton discovered the mediocraty but sufficiency of the McDonald&amp;rsquo;s breakfast burritos (better with hot sauce) while Mireille enjoyed her Hot Cakes and sausage, which are&amp;hellip; fine&amp;hellip; The best part about where we are staying is that it is walking distance to so many places - mostly restaurants!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spring Break - COVID-19 Edition - Chapter 2 - The Drive</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/03/spring-break-covid-19-edition-chapter-2-the-drive/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 19:39:32 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/03/spring-break-covid-19-edition-chapter-2-the-drive/</guid>
      <description>On Monday at 7:45, we left home, without the animals (Ethan&amp;rsquo;s college canceled their classes the first three days of this week, so the animals could stay with him). We first stopped at Mireille&amp;rsquo;s school to pickup her packet of &amp;ldquo;school at home&amp;rdquo; papers. Then we headed west through the mountains towards Durango, CO.
For the first few hours, we listened to public radio. After about 2 hours of that, we had had enough of the Coronavirus talk, so we listened to a podcast about the space race.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spring Break - COVID-19 Edition - Chapter 1 - Preamble</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/03/spring-break-covid-19-edition-chapter-1-preamble/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2020 21:12:18 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/03/spring-break-covid-19-edition-chapter-1-preamble/</guid>
      <description>Spring Break!!! Woo!!!
Actually, as the years go on, the event has become more and more complicated. Three kids in two different schools last year was one thing - but this year, three kids in three different schools increased the complexity. And add to that the fact that I just started a new job&amp;hellip; No worries - we would ignore the adult child, and that will simplify things!!! Well, sort of.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>So - I got a new job...</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/02/so-i-got-a-new-job.../</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 11:35:19 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/02/so-i-got-a-new-job.../</guid>
      <description>It doesn&amp;rsquo;t happen very often, thankfully, but I started a new job this month! It also doesn&amp;rsquo;t happen very often that I blog about myself. Both good things, I think!
At the beginning of February, I started a new job with Twilio. Headquartered in San Francisco, I&amp;rsquo;m actually working in Downtown Denver where one of the largest non-HQ offices is located. There are so many new things that I&amp;rsquo;m experiencing, which is sort of the point, I guess.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Big Update on Grady Kids</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/01/big-update-on-grady-kids/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2020 09:25:40 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/01/big-update-on-grady-kids/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s a broken record on this blog, but it&amp;rsquo;s again been a LONG time since I&amp;rsquo;ve done anything. There is definitely an ebb and flow to my state of mind that really dictates how much I observe of the world around me, and around the end of the year is a time of reflection for lots of people. So here it goes&amp;hellip;
This post is going to read mostly as a Quinton post.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Dead Cat Saga</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/09/the-dead-cat-saga/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2019 14:51:03 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/09/the-dead-cat-saga/</guid>
      <description>A couple of weekends ago, Quinton and I, on a whim, went outside to play catch with a baseball. It&amp;rsquo;s sort of odd that we would do that. Most of Quin&amp;rsquo;s time at home involves playing XBox, and most of my time involves yelling at Quinton about playing XBox, but on this occassion we both decided to do something a little different.
Flash back to earlier that morning, upon waking up I saw that our doorbell camera had gone off a couple of times during the night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>College</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/08/college/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2019 20:24:15 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/08/college/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday, I had to mow my own lawn. Actually I wasn&amp;rsquo;t even that sad about that - it only takes about an hour to really do a number on my lawn. I do the mowing, of course, along with regular mower maintenance. Then I get the trimmer out and move the infringing grass back off of the cement walkways and what-not. Heck, I even took the time to fertilize. It was all done while I walked, contemplating what had just happened.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Firsts, and a Conversation with Mireille</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/08/firsts-and-a-conversation-with-mireille/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 09:50:50 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/08/firsts-and-a-conversation-with-mireille/</guid>
      <description>Quinton started middle school this week. For some reason, middle school scares the hell out of me on behalf of my children. To boot, he&amp;rsquo;s been actively and heavily lobbying to be moved to the public school from our relatively more comfortable private school middle school situation. Well, he made pretty good arguments, so we relented, so now he has started school at Laredo Public Middle School, right next to where Ethan has spent his last 4 years at Smoky Hill.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adult Child</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/08/adult-child/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2019 13:18:08 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/08/adult-child/</guid>
      <description>Is that a contradiction? I suppose it doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter - that is what we have now. Ethan, as of last Friday, is considered by this society to be &amp;ldquo;an adult.&amp;rdquo; He is now able to drin&amp;hellip; Well, he can rent a ca&amp;hellip; Hmm&amp;hellip; He can be drafted, and he can vote, and if he were to do something bad, he can be punished like the hardened adult criminal that he would undoubtedly be.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hawaii Vacation 2019 - Day 8</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/06/hawaii-vacation-2019-day-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2019 20:38:50 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/06/hawaii-vacation-2019-day-8/</guid>
      <description>Day 8 - Is it time to go home yet? While we love Hawai&amp;rsquo;i, we are all ready to go home. We started the day like most others, coffee at the hotel lobby. We then collected the spawn and did some swimming before showering and heading back to Hale&amp;rsquo;iwa for lunch at &amp;ldquo;Killer Tacos.&amp;rdquo;
After lunch, we decided to do some more beach stuff. We got some stuff, though not as much as we did yesterday, and headed off on the .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hawaii Vacation 2019 - Day 7</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/06/hawaii-vacation-2019-day-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2019 19:55:11 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/06/hawaii-vacation-2019-day-7/</guid>
      <description>Day 7 - Submarine Morning Day 7 - this vacation is getting long!!! Still fun stuff to do, and so much that we haven&amp;rsquo;t even done yet! Today we had an appointment in Waikiki at 10:00 to go on a submarine! The trip there is about 90 minutes with morning traffic, so we left by 8:00 to get down there.
We took the standard mid-island route this time which looked much different this time!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hawaii Vacation 2019 - Day 6</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/06/hawaii-vacation-2019-day-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 18:09:33 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/06/hawaii-vacation-2019-day-6/</guid>
      <description>Day 6 - Relax Morning at Turtle Bay Thursday, I think. It&amp;rsquo;s sometimes hard to keep track on vacation - especially one this long! So we&amp;rsquo;ll go with Thursday. We didn&amp;rsquo;t have any excursions planned for this day, but that sort of made Jenny nervous that we would sit around the condo all day and play video games. She was probably correct&amp;hellip; That said, we began the morning with some Smash Brothers, as is now becoming a thing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hawaii Vacation 2019 - Day 5</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/06/hawaii-vacation-2019-day-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2019 22:19:47 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/06/hawaii-vacation-2019-day-5/</guid>
      <description>Day 5 - Polynesian Cultural Center Morning Well, we are certainly adjusted to the timezone by now. Nobody stirred until well after 6:00 AM, and nobody got out of bed until after 7:00. It seems pretty easy to acclimate to westernbound timezones, at least to a point. I remember the adjustment being very difficult in Manila, but here it&amp;rsquo;s been a breeze!!!
Jenny, Mireille, and I went over to the hotel lobby and got some morning drinks and a croissant while the boys continued sleeping.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hawaii Vacation 2019 - Day 4</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/06/hawaii-vacation-2019-day-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2019 21:51:32 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/06/hawaii-vacation-2019-day-4/</guid>
      <description>Day 4 - Koalua Ranch Morning Shenanigans The day still started earlyish. Jenny and I were out of bed and walking to the hotel lobby for some &amp;ldquo;coffee&amp;rdquo; before 7:00. We then went on a little walk of the grounds to see what we could see. Unfortunately it wasn&amp;rsquo;t much!!! There are a lot of trails on the property. Good for walking, biking, horse riding, etc. We probably did about 2 miles, but needed to get back to the kids and make sure they weren&amp;rsquo;t killing each other.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hawaii Vacation 2019 - Day 3</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/06/hawaii-vacation-2019-day-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2019 16:41:27 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/06/hawaii-vacation-2019-day-3/</guid>
      <description>Day 3 - Pearl Harbor Sunrise After our busted sunset last night, both boys were all into the idea of waking up this morning and seeing the sunrise. As it stood, I was able to convince Mireille to come with me! We had a nice walk, but ultimately our quest to see a sunrise failed due to clouds. Oh well!!!
  Bah - clouds!!!     Mireille on our sunrise walk   Windward Drive Our excursion for the day was to Pearl Harbor - perhaps you&amp;rsquo;ve heard of it!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hawaii Vacation 2019 - Day 2</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/06/hawaii-vacation-2019-day-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2019 20:54:53 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/06/hawaii-vacation-2019-day-2/</guid>
      <description>Day 2 - Turtle Bay Resort Birthday!!! Before I say anything, I have acknowledge the celebration of another year for my beautiful wife and mother of our children. 46, er, 39!!! Happy Birthday, Jenny!!!
  The Birthday girl at Breakfast with Mireille and Quinton   Sunrise After crashing &amp;ldquo;early&amp;rdquo; Hawaii time, I managed to wake up &amp;ldquo;early&amp;rdquo; Hawaii time again. Though I had only 6 or so hours of sleep, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t get it out of my head that I wanted to see a sunrise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hawaii Vacation 2019 - Day 1</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/06/hawaii-vacation-2019-day-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2019 00:44:45 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/06/hawaii-vacation-2019-day-1/</guid>
      <description>Day 1 - Travel DIA In typical Grady fashion, we arrived at the airport area about three hours in advance of our 2:30 departure time. Don’t want to be hurried!!! We were able to secure parking for the week+ for around $60 at an off site lot, and even got upgraded to indoor parking since all of the outdoor spots were taken!
  Shuttle on the way to DIA     Shuttle on the way to DIA     Shuttle on the way to DIA   The morning went pretty easily.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quin Said a Bad Word</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/05/quin-said-a-bad-word/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 13:18:08 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/05/quin-said-a-bad-word/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s graduation week. I have a longer, more sentimental post that I&amp;rsquo;m working through, but I had to jot this one down quickly before it was lost to history. Since it is graduation week, we have family that have started arriving to help Ethan celebrate and to help remind us how old we are.
Last night, my parents, Ethan and his girlfriend Rachel, and Jenny and I were sitting around the table just talking about different things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teeth, Hoops, and Firsts</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/04/teeth-hoops-and-firsts/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 09:38:11 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/04/teeth-hoops-and-firsts/</guid>
      <description>Mireille finally lost that first tooth! It was a few weeks ago, now. She was walking around the kitchen, and I asked her, like I had been every day for quite a few weeks, how her teeth were doing. Her two front teeth on the bottom were coming in behind the baby teeth. On that fateful night, one of them was finally loose enough that I felt confident enough to give it a little tug and evict it from its spot that the other tooth so badly wanted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Big Man on Campus - a tall tale by Quinton</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/02/big-man-on-campus-a-tall-tale-by-quinton/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 09:58:38 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/02/big-man-on-campus-a-tall-tale-by-quinton/</guid>
      <description>Quinton had an assignment to write a tall tale. Coincidental with getting the assignment, Quin had learned about a competition that his cousin, Graham, had recently done with his uncle, Bruce. For those that don&amp;rsquo;t know them, Graham is a 10 year old, not particularly big, and Bruce, his uncle, is about 5&amp;rsquo; 2&amp;rdquo; and weighs probably about 130 pounds. Anyway, Graham challenged uncle Bruce to a plank challenge. Bruce was able to plank for 5 minutes, but Graham was able to do it for 30 minutes!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Catching up to 2019</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/02/catching-up-to-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2019 17:00:42 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2019/02/catching-up-to-2019/</guid>
      <description>A new year&amp;hellip; It went and happened again, and again I find myself in the position of having a resolution of writing more. It seems a yearly concern, but here goes the latest attempt.
2018 was very kind to the Grady&amp;rsquo;s. Ethan wrecked a couple of cars, but has now had his latest one for over 6 months without incident (knock on wood). Brandon got a new (to me) car in the form of a 2017 Chevy Malibu - yeah, I can&amp;rsquo;t seem to break that mold.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zazu</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/12/zazu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 14:48:10 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/12/zazu/</guid>
      <description>We added a new family member this weekend.
  Zaz and Quinton   Say hello to &amp;ldquo;Zazu,&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;Zaz&amp;rdquo; as Quinton likes to call him. Quinton has really wanted a pet of his own for awhile now. He has been trying to get us to get another dog and for me to leave the dog alone so I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be the &amp;ldquo;alpha male&amp;rdquo; to this one like I am to Heinz.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moab</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/11/moab/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2018 19:58:19 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/11/moab/</guid>
      <description>The Trip Moab. Or as Mireille would pronounce it, Mo-Ab. Small city of 5000 some people in Southeast Utah, the land of Mormons, backwards liquor laws, and some spectacular natural landscapes. Since we&amp;rsquo;ve moved to the west we&amp;rsquo;ve always looked for a reason to get out here to take in these sights. Thanks to some early travel by Mom and Pop Grady, having come through Denver the weekend prior for Thanksgiving day festivities, we finally had our opportunity to check it out over the Thanksgiving day weekend, figuring it wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be quite as busy or quite as hot as it would in the peak months.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mireille the Investigator</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/11/mireille-the-investigator/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 19:58:19 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/11/mireille-the-investigator/</guid>
      <description>I couldn&amp;rsquo;t find my toothbrush this morning. That may not sound that strange, but I have one of those big Sonicare toothbrushes that would seem very difficult to lose. In fact, where my toothbrush was supposed to be, Jenny&amp;rsquo;s had taken its place, a similar Sonicare but different color.
I had no idea where it could be. Initially I blamed Jenny for hiding it on me. She came home angry last night for reasons unknown, and was argumentative.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mireille the Observer</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/11/mireille-the-observer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 10:10:26 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/11/mireille-the-observer/</guid>
      <description>Mireille is far and away the most observant of our children. Ethan&amp;rsquo;s not bad - far better than myself. Quinton, well, he and I are about in the same boat, and it&amp;rsquo;s not a good boat. Mireille will notice just about anything, even if it seems inconsequential. For example, Jenny occasionally colors her hair, but in a subtle way such that color blind me will not notice. Mireille does, though. The other day, Jenny swapped out the pulls on our dressers in our room, and the first thing Mireille said when she walked in the room was &amp;ldquo;when did you get new ones of these?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous Catching Up</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/09/miscellaneous-catching-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Sep 2018 08:52:45 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/09/miscellaneous-catching-up/</guid>
      <description>It’s been awhile on a couple of these, so I figured I should jot them down before time erodes them from my memory.
This first story has been getting good traction in my friend and colleague circles. Before I can tell the story, I need to tee it up a little bit. Quinton is obviously a black male being raised among “the whites.” From time to time that causes some conflict in him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Francisco - 2018 - Day 6</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/07/san-francisco-2018-day-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2018 20:18:26 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/07/san-francisco-2018-day-6/</guid>
      <description>Flying home is tough, but today was tougher than normal since our flight wasn&amp;rsquo;t until 8:30. I think I would almost prefer a midday flight. We theoretically had enough time to do some stuff, but we managed to accomplish all that we had set out to do in the prior 5 days. So it was going to be awkward. As I sit here, we were 3 hours early for our 8:30 PM flight to Denver, but it has been delayed by an hour, so we will be sitting here for some time!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Francisco - 2018 - Day 5</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/07/san-francisco-2018-day-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2018 20:18:22 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/07/san-francisco-2018-day-5/</guid>
      <description>Our penultimate day of vacation started out early-ish. Of course, we got out to Starbucks and had some donut holes from our new favorite donut shop in California, the creatively named &amp;ldquo;Jelly Donut,&amp;rdquo; where I can&amp;rsquo;t say I ever saw a jelly donut there&amp;hellip; I was a little nervous to be going to the wharf today because it was a weekend, so tourist traffic would be high. Our ultimate goal was to get to our whale watching tour by 3:00 which took off at the wharf, and the website gave instructions to places where you could park inexpensively for $50 a day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Francisco - 2018 - Day 4</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/07/san-francisco-2018-day-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2018 20:18:16 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/07/san-francisco-2018-day-4/</guid>
      <description>Day 4 - I finally was able to get up in time to hit the road for a run. While I&amp;rsquo;m quite out of shape, I was still able to cut 25 seconds per mile off of my new-normal running speed while in the oxygen rich California air! Almost enough to get me to go out and do it again on this trip&amp;hellip; Almost&amp;hellip;
Much like yesterday, today was about doing the things that Jenny and I had planned on doing on our last trip but were prevented from doing due to the wildfires in Wine Country.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Francisco - 2018 - Day 3</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/07/san-francisco-2018-day-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2018 22:16:20 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/07/san-francisco-2018-day-3/</guid>
      <description>Friday was all about Muir Woods. Jenny and I had planned to visit here when we came to the area last September but weren&amp;rsquo;t able to make it due to the wildfires at the time. We were lucky to have seen a sign that warned visitors that they needed a parking reservation prior to visiting. We had secured a noon parking reservation for the day, but we were a little early.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Francisco - 2018 - Day 2</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/07/san-francisco-2018-day-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2018 22:16:15 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/07/san-francisco-2018-day-2/</guid>
      <description>After some much needed sleep, we woke up fairly early-ish and took in the world famous Embassy Suites complimentary breakfast! Well, most of us did. Despite getting up in time, Ethan decided not to partake.
The first order of business, feed the addiction, off to the local Starbucks. Once that was out of the way, we were free to head downtown for a day in the city. Our first stop was Fisherman&amp;rsquo;s Wharf.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Francisco - 2018 - Day 1</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/07/san-francisco-2018-day-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 21:48:18 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/07/san-francisco-2018-day-1/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been traveling WAY too much lately. After a brief trip to Jacksonville, the boys and I went into the mountains last weekend, then I boarded a plane to Chicago on Monday only to return on Tuesday in anticipation of an early Wednesday departure to San Francisco. I&amp;rsquo;m happy I&amp;rsquo;m not sick!!! Can&amp;rsquo;t say the same for Quinton, however. Jenny called me on Monday evening to inform me that Quinton had been throwing up all day and into the evening.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018 Boy&#39;s Trip - Day 2</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/07/2018-boys-trip-day-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 20:50:03 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/07/2018-boys-trip-day-2/</guid>
      <description>Day 2 We started the day slowly, as any good boy&amp;rsquo;s trip would. Since we didn&amp;rsquo;t go to bed until later, we slept in until after 8:00. I sort of wanted to get going, so I got up and started cooking half of our 2 pounds of bacon and a dozen eggs. The smell was enough to wake Ethan up by 8:30, mainly because the apartment was so full of smoke that I think he started suffocating.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018 Boy&#39;s Trip</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/07/2018-boys-trip/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2018 20:29:30 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/07/2018-boys-trip/</guid>
      <description>Day 1 Here we sit at 521 Elm St. in historic Leadville, CO, our VRBO for the weekend. Ethan, Quinton, and I are doing our first &amp;ldquo;boy&amp;rsquo;s weekend.&amp;rdquo; It was hard leaving Jenny and Mireille behind, but we stayed the course and are going through with it.
The trip up here was rougher than expected. Traffic out of Denver to the mountains via I70 was somehow worse than it normally would be when we are coming up to ski, but we persevered.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Old Blog Reclaimed!</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/05/old-blog-reclaimed/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 14:45:58 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/05/old-blog-reclaimed/</guid>
      <description>I have a small project going on right now. I&amp;rsquo;ve downloaded my old blog from Blogspot and have started persisting it here, in a more controlled fashion - everything all in one place! Since I had over 180 posts on that blog, it will take some time to reclaim all of the old posts and reformat them to properly work here, but the work has begun. It is tedious work, involving some level of digital archaeology, but I think it is worthwhile and will make this blog much more portable in the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spring Break 2018 - Day Three</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/03/spring-break-2018-day-three/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Mar 2018 20:15:04 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/03/spring-break-2018-day-three/</guid>
      <description>Taos Our third day was dedicated to Taos. Having slept in a little, but not quite as much as the prior day, we had a little extra time to do some swimming in hopes of getting away from the crowds in the pool. We weren&amp;rsquo;t successful in avoiding crowds, but we did get about 45 minutes of swimming in before we left the hotel. Mireille, Quinton, and I played some hide and seek (it&amp;rsquo;s more fun than you would think).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spring Break 2018 - Day Two</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/03/spring-break-2018-day-two/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 21:34:29 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/03/spring-break-2018-day-two/</guid>
      <description>Los Alamos Thank goodness, today started out MUCH later than the prior one. Nobody really stirred until 9:00, giving Mireille a much needed 13 hours, and Quinton an even more needed 11.5. Of course, I was also happy to finally get 10 myself, though I was up several times in the night for the &amp;ldquo;old man pee.&amp;rdquo; While we all got ready, Jenny and Mireille went to get some coffee at the very convenient on presmises Starbucks in the lobby.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spring Break 2018 - Day One</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/03/spring-break-2018-day-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2018 21:00:53 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/03/spring-break-2018-day-one/</guid>
      <description>AM As we suspected, and as is typical, we were up way too early. Mireille woke up around 7:00 the first time, Quinton followed about 7:30. While Mireille was able to fall back to sleep for a bit, Quinton was screaming for food by 8:00, so we were up! We left Ethan to sleep while the rest of us went down to one of the dozen or so restaurants the hotel had to offer for a nice buffet breakfast.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spring Break 2018 - The Drive</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/03/spring-break-2018-the-drive/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 22:29:27 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/03/spring-break-2018-the-drive/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Are we going to the hotel tonight?&amp;rdquo; This is the question repeated at least nightly for the last two weeks by our youngest, Mireille. For some reason she just loves hotels! I think it has something to do with the swimming pools. Perhaps she just likes to travel! At any rate, it had been a constant anthem for the last several weeks - &amp;ldquo;are we going to the hotel?&amp;rdquo;
The day before we left, we dropped the &amp;ldquo;Flex-car&amp;rdquo; off at Rack Attack to get rails and a luggage rack installed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Honor Roll</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/03/honor-roll/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 12:42:11 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/03/honor-roll/</guid>
      <description>Last Wednesday, I was able to witness the St. Pius X 2nd Trimester Honor Roll ceremony, and my favorite middle child was among the honorees. Quinton achieved all A- or better in the last trimester. In fact, he got all A&amp;rsquo;s with the exception of one A- which he got in Art.
Congratulations, Quinton!!!
  Quinton and the Gold Honor Roll   Oh, and just because she is adorable, here is a picture of Mireille in her new soccer uniform.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Website</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/03/new-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Mar 2018 12:26:58 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/03/new-website/</guid>
      <description>I know, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t look any different. That&amp;rsquo;s sort of the beauty of this story. I&amp;rsquo;m going to warn you, if you normally come here for my amusing anecdotes about my kids, or perhaps to be regaled about my home improvement exploits, this story will probably seem somewhat dull. However, I owe this entry to the greater technological community, as there might be somebody, somewhere, that thinks even a little bit like me and are trying to do something similar to what I&amp;rsquo;m trying to do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Next Renovation</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/02/the-next-renovation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2018 09:36:02 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/02/the-next-renovation/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been awhile since we&amp;rsquo;ve done any major remodeling work to our house (yeah, right!), so it was time for us to embark on our next gigantic project. The thought was that we would do both upstairs bathrooms at more or less the same time. The kid&amp;rsquo;s bathroom was supposed to be &amp;ldquo;easy&amp;rdquo; since I was going to leave the shower pretty much alone, just update the fixtures and the shower head, but concentrate mostly on the floor, toilet, and vanity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas with the Tibbetts</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/02/christmas-with-the-tibbetts/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2018 10:50:09 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2018/02/christmas-with-the-tibbetts/</guid>
      <description>We live in Colorado. Our families, by and large, still dwell in places throughout the Midwest. Year after year this generates some degree of conflict, particularly when it comes time for celebrating the holidays. For this holiday season, we celebrated Grady Christmas on the ever traditional weekend of the first weekend of November. For the Tibbett holiday celebration, then, we coordinated an early January celebration. Actually, it was planned to coincide with my 45th birthday, because who wouldn&amp;rsquo;t want to travel to the frigid midwest to stay in remote, rural Wisconsin with his in-laws on their 45th birthday!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elf on the Shelf</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/12/elf-on-the-shelf/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2017 18:45:01 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/12/elf-on-the-shelf/</guid>
      <description>There are many traditions that I&amp;rsquo;ve learned of since leaving the nest that my family was either ignorant to or just didn&amp;rsquo;t celebrate. One happened this morning, and has for the last 21 years of my marriage, yet I still forget to celebrate it - St. Nicholas&amp;rsquo;s Day. Jenny celebrated it year after year, yet I did not, so even though I&amp;rsquo;ve now been in my adult life much longer than I was ever in my parents&amp;rsquo; home, I still forget&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thanksgiving 2017</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/12/thanksgiving-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2017 12:16:24 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/12/thanksgiving-2017/</guid>
      <description>Thanksgiving is literally my favorite holiday. I just love getting together with family and friends, cooking a delicious meal, eating said meal, just hanging out and napping with people. I think even more than Christmas, it is the most relaxing holiday out there!
This year, having already done the &amp;ldquo;Grady Christmas&amp;rdquo; several weeks earlier, our plan was to stay put for Thanksgiving. Luckily there are others in the greater Denver metropolitan area that are also too far away to spend the day with family, so they became our extended family for Thanksgiving.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Epic of the Flex</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/11/the-epic-of-the-flex/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2017 16:16:59 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/11/the-epic-of-the-flex/</guid>
      <description>If you are familiar with our family, you know that we don&amp;rsquo;t really place a high value on vehicles. Basically whatever can get us from point A to point B reliably and without a whole lot of money in maintenance will do. In our particular family, we now have three vehicles, two Chevy Malibu&amp;rsquo;s that have a combined age approaching 30 years, and a &amp;ldquo;new&amp;rdquo; Ford Flex that is only 3 years old, but is approaching 100,000 miles itself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Suburban Archeologist</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/10/suburban-archeologist/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2017 08:42:44 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/10/suburban-archeologist/</guid>
      <description>Not an interesting update for those that are looking for news on my adorable and smart children, but something I&amp;rsquo;m documenting for posterity, and for my own purposes.
We do quite a lot of home improvement. I&amp;rsquo;ve always been the type that likes to try something on my own before calling a professional in to do it correctly and quickly. Last weekend, a couple of long running &amp;ldquo;curiosity&amp;rdquo; type projects finally had some major movement, which, since I&amp;rsquo;m kind of a dork, made me pretty excited!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A perfect parent&#39;s weekend...</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/09/a-perfect-parents-weekend.../</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2017 09:38:40 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/09/a-perfect-parents-weekend.../</guid>
      <description>This was a couple of weeks ago now, so it&amp;rsquo;s not as fresh in my mind as it was when it happened, but the event was important enough that I think it warrants documentation. You see, this was Mireille&amp;rsquo;s fifth birthday, her second in the United States.
For the weeks leading up to September 9, Mireille has been asking on a regular basis about her birthday party. She really wanted to have a party, with a bounce castle, and a cake, and presents!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mireille Funnies</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/09/mireille-funnies/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 11:52:46 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/09/mireille-funnies/</guid>
      <description>Jenny was talking to Mireille on Sunday about things that girls talk about. I wasn&amp;rsquo;t privvy to the details of the entire conversation, because that wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be appropriate - I&amp;rsquo;m a boy. One little nugget Jenny shared with me was when Mireille admitted to her, &amp;ldquo;I wish I was a unicorn. But I&amp;rsquo;m just Mireille&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;
Then, yesterday, our little Unicorn proved she listens and absorbs way more than she ever lets on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Colorado Adventure Series - Snow Mountain Ranch Day 4</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/08/colorado-adventure-series-snow-mountain-ranch-day-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2017 17:52:46 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/08/colorado-adventure-series-snow-mountain-ranch-day-4/</guid>
      <description>Day 4 Today started out much the same as the last. I got up &amp;ldquo;early&amp;rdquo; and headed out for a quick run around the campus. The main difference today was that Ethan decided he would come with me! He&amp;rsquo;s training for soccer and was supposed to run 5 miles over the weekend. He decided that 3.2 at 9000 feet was a rough equivalent of 5 at 5280, which I&amp;rsquo;m inclined to agree with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Colorado Adventure Series - Snow Mountain Ranch Day 3</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/08/colorado-adventure-series-snow-mountain-ranch-day-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2017 16:52:46 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/08/colorado-adventure-series-snow-mountain-ranch-day-3/</guid>
      <description>Day 3 Day three started out later than day 2. With nothing really pushing us out of bed, the room slept in. I got up &amp;ldquo;early&amp;rdquo; around 7:00 or so and circumnavigated the property on a &amp;ldquo;run&amp;rdquo; of sorts. Not sure you can really call it a run. Jogging occured, but a lot of walking also occurred. It was very brisk to start the day, at only 36 degF, and a bit of fog made it a little spooky, but it was good to get out and about and get the blood pumping earlyish.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Colorado Adventure Series - Snow Mountain Ranch Day 2</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/08/colorado-adventure-series-snow-mountain-ranch-day-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2017 21:52:46 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/08/colorado-adventure-series-snow-mountain-ranch-day-2/</guid>
      <description>Day 2 Our first full day of vacation! Today is exciting because it will be most of our first time whitewater rafting. We were to be in Kremmling, about 45 miles away, by 8:30 for our half day whitewater rafting adventure. So we set an alarm for 6:30, which was fine with everybody considering we were all in bed early the night before, got dressed, had breakfast at the cafeteria, and headed west on 40 to the bustling metropolis of Kremmling via Granby.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Colorado Adventure Series - Snow Mountain Ranch Day 1</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/08/colorado-adventure-series-snow-mountain-ranch-day-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2017 20:52:46 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/08/colorado-adventure-series-snow-mountain-ranch-day-1/</guid>
      <description>Prelude When we first moved to Colorado two years ago, we made a point of being &amp;ldquo;tourists in our own state.&amp;rdquo; It seems so often that we live somewhere and never really get to experience it like somebody who visits. Life always seems to catch up with us. Lord Soccer demands attention, work, school, the house&amp;hellip; It&amp;rsquo;s a never ending cycle of demands on our time. So we&amp;rsquo;ve tried to keep it more fresh here in Colorado, since there is so much to see out here (despite there not being any measurable amount of recreational water anywhere out here).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Logitech K810 Reset</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/07/logitech-k810-reset/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2017 08:26:10 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/07/logitech-k810-reset/</guid>
      <description>I have been using the same external keyboard for my last three Macs, an excellent little Bluetooth keyboard from Logitech called the Logitech K810. It&amp;rsquo;s meant to be a keyboard for a Windows machine, but it works perfectly well for my Mac as well as my various iDevices.
This morning when I came in to start working for the day, I found the keyboard had lost its mind! None of the keys worked properly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Driver Out There</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/06/new-driver-out-there/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2017 14:52:46 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/06/new-driver-out-there/</guid>
      <description>As of Monday, June 26, the world has a new driver. Ethan passed his driver&amp;rsquo;s test last Friday and made it official with the DMV (and our insurance agent) on Monday. It was actually a nice thing today. It&amp;rsquo;s Bike to Work day here in Denver, so I rode my bike in. About 2 miles from home, one of my tires popped, and I didn&amp;rsquo;t have a repair kit with me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summer is here!</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/06/summer-is-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 14:52:46 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/06/summer-is-here/</guid>
      <description>Summer is finally upon us. Last week was a full week without school, except for Mireille, but that&amp;rsquo;s daycare - even though she calls it school. The temperatures as of last Thursday definitely represented a shift into the ungodly hot area, though in Denver, if you can find shade, you are in good shape since the humidity is very comfortable. As a family we are definitely settling in more and more as the years have gone by.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mireille&#39;s English Progression</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/05/mireilles-english-progression/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2017 15:18:41 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/05/mireilles-english-progression/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been over a year, and Mireille continues to grow and develop. Outside of some difficulties in identifying colors (something I can&amp;rsquo;t really fault her here) and a current disinterest in letters or numbers, she&amp;rsquo;s developing quite on par with what I would expect. She does continue to have some interesting phrases, usages, and interactions from time to time that merit documentation.
Recently she has started using a phrase whenever people do something that she really doesn&amp;rsquo;t understand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Mother&#39;s Day</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/05/happy-mothers-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2017 11:04:40 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/05/happy-mothers-day/</guid>
      <description>Happy Mother&amp;rsquo;s Day to my kids&amp;rsquo; mom, and of course my wife, who luckily happen to be the same person! This year we celebrated by going to a brunch at one of our favorite places, Bull and Bush Brewpub! It&amp;rsquo;s a difficult thing to get all of our kids both out of the house and behaving in a public place, but for the most part they held it together through brunch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bathroom Remodel</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/02/bathroom-remodel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2017 08:26:10 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/02/bathroom-remodel/</guid>
      <description>Our house was built in the 80s, 1982 to be exact. Many, if not most things have not really been touched since then. Sure, fresh paint has been applied to the walls and carpet occasionally replaced, but the &amp;ldquo;bones&amp;rdquo; of the house have remained unchanged for the last 35 years.
That changed immediately when we moved in almost 2 years ago. It started with windows, moved to the kitchen (which is still awesome, btw), moved on to doors, and now has passed to the biggest thorn remaining on the first floor, the bathroom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Potpourri</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/01/potpourri/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2017 17:02:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2017/01/potpourri/</guid>
      <description>As is typical now a days, I find myself delinquent in my posting. I blame my new job. Nothing more. Oh, and having three kids is hard. Not sure I&amp;rsquo;ve mentioned that. Still, they keep us on our toes, and I occasionally remember to write some of the remarkable things down that they do. The following is a small collection of the things I&amp;rsquo;ve remembered.
Mireille &amp;hellip;on language&amp;hellip; Mireille&amp;rsquo;s pronoun usage continues to improve, though her favorite pronoun continues to be &amp;ldquo;him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2016 - The Year in Review - First Trimester</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/12/2016-the-year-in-review-first-trimester/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2016 18:55:09 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/12/2016-the-year-in-review-first-trimester/</guid>
      <description>I can remember one year when we did the traditional &amp;ldquo;Holiday Letter.&amp;rdquo; It was the year that we were in the process of trying to adopt Quinton, so we were &amp;ldquo;marketing ourselves&amp;rdquo; to our family and friends that year. Looking back, it was a fun letter to do, even if it was not necessary from the salesman side of house. I thought it would be fun to condense 2016 into a bit of a letter to our family (thank you both of my readers) and so that future versions of ourselves might enjoy reading it as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mireille&#39;s English - now with Pronouns!!!</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/12/mireilles-english-now-with-pronouns/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2016 20:47:29 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/12/mireilles-english-now-with-pronouns/</guid>
      <description>Mireille has been in the US for right around 8 months now, and she still has yet to stop amazing me with how quickly she is adjusting. It&amp;rsquo;s not only just the English, though that is remarkable, but everything else as well. I don&amp;rsquo;t think I can really explain it better than I can show it with the picture below which I believe encapsulates the completeness of Mireille&amp;rsquo;s Westernization.
  Westernized Mireille   Beyond device usage and creature comforts, Mireille continues to pickup English at an alarming rate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The First Snow of the Year</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/11/the-first-snow-of-the-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2016 09:31:29 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/11/the-first-snow-of-the-year/</guid>
      <description>Last week it snowed in Denver for the first time this season. It&amp;rsquo;s a mixed bag out here for snow. People don&amp;rsquo;t really care for it in the city, like most places, but love when it happens in the mountains, where it is supposed to be. My kids certainly love it, at least the first snow.
Mireille has been saying &amp;ldquo;snow&amp;rsquo;s coming?&amp;rdquo; since about August when Jenny showed her some snow boots she could wear.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Bloggable Offense</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/11/a-bloggable-offense/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2016 09:22:02 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/11/a-bloggable-offense/</guid>
      <description>Quinton loves his iPad, and he loves video games. Those are his leisure time activities, which is a funny thing to say, leisure time for an 8 year old! What he really loves to do is to enjoy both of them at the same time, which is something we try to limit for various reasons. It also presents itself as an opportunity for us when dolling out discipline.
Last week, Quinton had some egregious issue for which he had to be punished.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>October 2016 - Big Update!</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/10/october-2016-big-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2016 19:39:06 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/10/october-2016-big-update/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s October! October has been a busy month, but what month hasn&amp;rsquo;t been, really. So it&amp;rsquo;s been awhile since there&amp;rsquo;s been an update of much substance. So, while my family answers the door to greet and treat Halloween visitors in full costume, I thought I would take a few minutes (or 60) and update the world on the goings on in the Grady Household.
Adoption - Complete I don&amp;rsquo;t have to restate how much work and waiting it&amp;rsquo;s been to complete this, our second adoption.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mireille the Magician</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/10/mireille-the-magician/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2016 20:34:27 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/10/mireille-the-magician/</guid>
      <description>Quick one today. I need to document this, because it cracks me up. Lately Mireille has been doing magic tricks. Yes, you read that correctly - my four year old knows how to do magic tricks. Well, she knows a single trick, but she&amp;rsquo;s OK at it, and is working at it and trying to perfect it.
What she does is she takes an item and puts it in her hand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick Updates</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/10/quick-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2016 10:18:11 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/10/quick-updates/</guid>
      <description>After five days of adult vacation in New Orleans, Jenny and I were happy to be back with our kids, and probably a bit surprised that five days wasn&amp;rsquo;t quite enough to really decompress! Things went back to normal very quickly.
Mirielle gas been constantly about three things - now, trick or treating, and the party that she was going to yesterday. The snow things is pretty funny. I seem to remember her not liking it very much when it showed up last spring, but just about every day she will ask us, very seriously, &amp;ldquo;snow coming?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mireille&#39;s Birthday!</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/09/mireilles-birthday/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2016 08:39:35 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/09/mireilles-birthday/</guid>
      <description>Mireille on her Fourth Birthday   Our little girl turned four!!! This was a pretty special birthday for us. It&amp;rsquo;s the first one we got to celebrate with her! We have sent her gifts for each birthday in the Congo, but I&amp;rsquo;m pretty sure she hated all of those gifts. It was a weird thing - it&amp;rsquo;s very expensive to send stuff to the Congo, so we would just send one of our agency&amp;rsquo;s lawyers money and ask them to purchase something local for her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Colorado Adventure Series - Crested Butte</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/08/colorado-adventure-series-crested-butte/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2016 21:38:05 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/08/colorado-adventure-series-crested-butte/</guid>
      <description>A couple of weeks ago, friends of ours from Wisconsin contacted us and asked if we wanted to spend some time with them in Crested Butte. They have a condo there that they were going to be visiting, and we decided it would be fun to check it out. I have to say, I&amp;rsquo;m glad we did.
Crested Butte is quite a long drive from our home. At about 4.5 hours, it&amp;rsquo;s by far the furthest we&amp;rsquo;ve traveled for this summer&amp;rsquo;s adventures, but we couldn&amp;rsquo;t pass up the opportunity to check it out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Theme!!!</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/08/new-theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2016 19:04:39 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/08/new-theme/</guid>
      <description>You may have noticed something new when you browsed here today. No, I didn&amp;rsquo;t adopt another kid&amp;hellip; I didn&amp;rsquo;t have to shovel 12 inches of snow&amp;hellip; It&amp;rsquo;s a new theme for the website! I&amp;rsquo;m sure you are as excited as I am about the change&amp;hellip; Doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter - this is my blog, and I can put whatever I want here.
This theme is awhile in the making. I&amp;rsquo;ve been doing web development for probably 17 years (well, I&amp;rsquo;ve been pretending to do it for that long - much of that time has been dedicated to managing web developers, but let&amp;rsquo;s not split hairs), and in the time I&amp;rsquo;ve been doing it, it has changed mightily.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More English</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/08/more-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2016 09:19:33 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/08/more-english/</guid>
      <description>I was amused by these so I had to post them. Mireille is learning English really quickly. Not all is worthy of recording as most is mundane, but there are a few&amp;hellip;
She loves to eat! And she loves to try new food - but she doesn&amp;rsquo;t always like the food that she&amp;rsquo;s trying. When she happens to try something that she doesn&amp;rsquo;t like she says &amp;ldquo;I like this uh-uh.&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Family Hikes</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/07/family-hikes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2016 21:04:51 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/07/family-hikes/</guid>
      <description>Last summer when we moved to CO, we weren&amp;rsquo;t very busy initially, so we took the opportunity to explore our great new state. This summer, after track has ended and we&amp;rsquo;ve buttoned up most of our backlog of home improvements, we have decided to do the same thing.
Two weekends ago we went to Frisco for the weekend with Maylee and Steve. While there we stayed at a hotel, did a little shopping, visited three breweries (yeah), but the main event was a 20 mile bike ride, 10 miles each way between Frisco and Breckenridge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ethan Driving Lessons</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/07/ethan-driving-lessons/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2016 21:27:19 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/07/ethan-driving-lessons/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s fun having somebody to drive you around, I&amp;rsquo;m finding. Since getting his permit, Ethan has logged a little over 5 hours of driving of the 50 that he needs to log by June next year in order to obtain his driver&amp;rsquo;s license. When he started driving, and after seeing the number of hours he would have to drive, I told him that there were over 300 breweries in Colorado, and the way he was going to learn how to drive was to take me to as many of them as he could&amp;hellip; Last night he told me that it was time to drive, and that I should grab my Pub Pass and we would stop for a beer somewhere.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quinton&#39;s Last Track Meet</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/07/quintons-last-track-meet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2016 21:27:10 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/07/quintons-last-track-meet/</guid>
      <description>Quinton joined the Aurora Recreational Track Team this summer. We were excited about this particular activity because it would be something Quinton couldn&amp;rsquo;t just partially do. We find that, often times during soccer or basketball, Quinton is perfectly content to move at about half pace. He is bigger and faster than most of the kids he plays against in those sports, so if he plays about half way, he can still be competitive but not sweat too much.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More English with Mireille</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/07/more-english-with-mireille/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2016 21:27:01 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/07/more-english-with-mireille/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been nearly 5 months now, and Mireille has really amped up her mastery of the English language. We recently went on vacation with the whole family to Wisconsin, so I had the opportunity to spend a lot of focused time with her. As the week went on, I started to see how she is systematically adding new words to her vocabulary all the time. First, she will point at something and ask you what it is (she says &amp;ldquo;Ques at?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life of a Single Father</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/06/life-of-a-single-father/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2016 21:43:24 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/06/life-of-a-single-father/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s 9:44 PM on Thursday evening. I&amp;rsquo;ve finally settled down to my computer and a bomber of my local&amp;rsquo;s double IPA. It&amp;rsquo;s the first time today that I&amp;rsquo;ve been able to sit without somebody demanding something or me having to be preparing something for somebody. You see, Jenny has been traveling for work since Monday morning, leaving me, a single father of three.
I&amp;rsquo;ve been a single father in the past.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ACHC Camp and English</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/06/achc-camp-and-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2016 07:58:48 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/06/achc-camp-and-english/</guid>
      <description>Last weekend we had to opportunity to go to the African-Caribbean Heritage Camp. It is one of a set of camps put on by an organization in town here that focuses on transracially formed families, specifically formed through adoption. Yeah, they have organizations for everything! We had been to the camp once before, two years ago, and enjoyed it so much that we decided to move to Denver!
Over the course of the two and a half days of camp we were all immersed with people in a very similar situation to our family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Father-In-Law</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/05/my-father-in-law/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2016 10:33:43 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/05/my-father-in-law/</guid>
      <description>This post got lost in the draft folder. So I&amp;rsquo;m posting it about three weeks late. Just for context&amp;hellip; Last weekend, my father-in-law, Bruce Tom Tibbett, passed away. It was a difficult thing to comprehend, somebody that we&amp;rsquo;ve been so close to for so long will no longer be with us. I&amp;rsquo;m sure I heard it somewhere how Freud describes the death of a parent - it reminds us of our mortality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quinton the Actor</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/05/quinton-the-actor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2016 14:15:12 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/05/quinton-the-actor/</guid>
      <description>For some reason, Quinton has decided lately that he wants to be an actor. He feels he could be rich, and feels that he&amp;rsquo;s every bit as good as the people he&amp;rsquo;s seen on TV and movies.
Yesterday on our trip back from Colorado Springs where we were watching soccer, Quinton was going into great detail about what would happen when he&amp;rsquo;s an actor. First I told him that he&amp;rsquo;d probably need to hire an agent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy 15th Birthday, Ethan!</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/05/happy-15th-birthday-ethan/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2016 07:42:46 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/05/happy-15th-birthday-ethan/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s not often that I blog about our oldest son, Ethan. He&amp;rsquo;s not cute and little anymore. He doesn&amp;rsquo;t say stupid things innocently so that I can have poignant teaching moments with him&amp;hellip; Well, he doesn&amp;rsquo;t do that as often, and he would probably take exception to me announcing them to the world now that he&amp;rsquo;s all social media savvy and all.
Ethan has grown into quite the young man. Though he is only 15, he has already learned many of life&amp;rsquo;s most important lessons, mainly the ones about treating others as you would want to be treated - he excels at that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning English</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/05/learning-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2016 07:57:13 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/05/learning-english/</guid>
      <description>Mireille has been in the US for around 2 months now and by all accounts is doing pretty well. One thing that we constantly worry about is whether she is picking up English quickly enough. Of course we are on all these Facebook groups and we constantly hear about how much English people&amp;rsquo;s kids are picking up and Mireille has been a bit slow on that front. I tend to think many of those people are embellishing their stories quite a bit, but whatever - she is a strong willed girl and she&amp;rsquo;s going to speak Lingala, dammit!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mireille Quickies</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/04/mireille-quickies/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2016 08:30:03 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/04/mireille-quickies/</guid>
      <description>I have a couple of &amp;ldquo;novels&amp;rdquo; in the works. Sometimes I let those clog up the works when I should be doing smaller, more frequent updates. So this is one of those smaller, more frequent updates. I&amp;rsquo;m finding my available time much harder to come by with the addition of the third child. I&amp;rsquo;m sure that will normalize out at some point, right? Those with three or more kids, back me up here!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Sh!tty Morning</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/03/a-shtty-morning/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2016 07:40:04 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/03/a-shtty-morning/</guid>
      <description>Mireille&amp;rsquo;s been home with us for two weeks today. Many of you are probably looking for some post that goes through that in some detail. This is not that post. I&amp;rsquo;m working up a larger post, but interestingly, going from two to three kids, and having that new kid be 3.5 years old, well, it changes how you can spend your time. Ah, material for another post. This post deals with an acute familial incident that happened to involve the entire family in one way or another&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two Days on the Hill</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/02/two-days-on-the-hill/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2016 10:15:09 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/02/two-days-on-the-hill/</guid>
      <description>Preamble I briefly considered titling this &amp;ldquo;Mr. Grady Goes to Washington,&amp;rdquo; but I didn&amp;rsquo;t like it for a couple of reasons. First, I don&amp;rsquo;t really think of myself as Mr. Grady. And more importantly, I have never really seen the movie, and I hate giving false information.
This is a story about a number of things&amp;hellip; Adoption, politics, travel, weather&amp;hellip; Hold on to your seats, and grab some NoDoze. This might get boring!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>She&#39;s Coming Home!!!</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/02/shes-coming-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2016 07:59:33 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/02/shes-coming-home/</guid>
      <description>Riding to my Red Eye     Dulles Airport     Empty International Arrival Terminal     UA 951 from Brussels     At at DGM, Ironic Lunch     The Wait is Excruciating     The Plane has Landed!     Busiest Time of Day     She&amp;#39;s Here!     Confused?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Birthday Quinton!</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/02/happy-birthday-quinton/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2016 08:26:05 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/02/happy-birthday-quinton/</guid>
      <description>8 years ago yesterday, we were given a call that Quinton&amp;rsquo;s birth mother was going into labor. By 10:30 AM on this morning, 8 years ago, Quinton was born!
It&amp;rsquo;s hard to believe that it&amp;rsquo;s been 8 years. Looking back on the pictures, so much has happened. He has grown so much, made us laugh, made us cry, asked so many important questions, and taught us things we never thought we even needed to know.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The &#34;Hack&#34; Font</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/02/the-hack-font/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2016 10:53:23 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/02/the-hack-font/</guid>
      <description>Sorry, no cute stories about Quinton and the funny things he says today. No interesting tales about Ethan and his quest to become a driver one day in the next year or so&amp;hellip; Today I thought I&amp;rsquo;d take an aside and post a public service announcement on the &amp;ldquo;Hack&amp;rdquo; font.
Why do you care? You likely do not. However, if you&amp;rsquo;ve found this post and are still reading, let me tell you why I like Hack.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>January Ski Weekend</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/01/january-ski-weekend/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2016 07:41:50 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/01/january-ski-weekend/</guid>
      <description>As a sort of late birthday present, a few of our Wisconsin friends came out and enjoyed a ski weekend with us at Copper Mountain, the resort where we have our season passes. Tim Z. was the first to arrive on Friday afternoon. After dropping off the dog, then picking Tim up from the airport, we headed west through typically terrible Denver traffic - perhaps leaving at 4:30 was a poor decision.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DRC Update</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/01/drc-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2016 08:04:12 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/01/drc-update/</guid>
      <description>So&amp;hellip; There are a couple of updates, but we&amp;rsquo;re still stuck.
The US sent a delegation of congressmen to the DRC to talk specifically about this issue. As has become typical, the DRC responded with things that we want to hear. I won&amp;rsquo;t go into details, but I wanted to document, for posterity, the letter I wrote to my congressmen in Colorado. I&amp;rsquo;ve been interacting with their offices for the past couple of months and have a fairly good rapport going with my contacts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Mission Viejo Elementary Football League</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/01/the-mission-viejo-elementary-football-league/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2016 08:08:47 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2016/01/the-mission-viejo-elementary-football-league/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m pretty sure I posted about Quinton&amp;rsquo;s recent obsession with Football in a prior post or two. If not, let me just say that Quinton has fallen HARD for football and all things about it. It&amp;rsquo;s to the point where he will actually put down his iPad (gasp) and ask me to turn on a football game when he knows one will be on. If you know Quinton, you know that is not something to take lightly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kids these days</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/12/kids-these-days/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2015 11:21:28 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/12/kids-these-days/</guid>
      <description>Most days are pretty much the same. I get up at 5:30, shower, get Ethan up at 6:00, make breakfast for us, then leave around 6:30 to get him to School. After that I&amp;rsquo;m not sure what typically happens as Jenny just takes care of it. Well, last week I had the opportunity to walk Quinton to school because Ethan had final exams and would be getting done around the time Quinton would normally be going to school.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>There, I fixed it - plumbing edition</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/12/there-i-fixed-it-plumbing-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2015 07:27:08 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/12/there-i-fixed-it-plumbing-edition/</guid>
      <description>One of these days I will get around to posting the epic project that we&amp;rsquo;ve undertaken of redoing our kitchen. It&amp;rsquo;s been about 4 months in the making and we&amp;rsquo;re hitting the final stretch! Last week the countertops were installed so we finally got our new sink installed. Unfortunately, the countertop guys don&amp;rsquo;t do plumbing, so that&amp;rsquo;s my job!
I had budgeted three trips to the hardware store, and I was right on the money!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thanksgiving, Colorado Style</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/12/thanksgiving-colorado-style/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2015 07:44:26 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/12/thanksgiving-colorado-style/</guid>
      <description>Our first major holiday in Colorado is my favorite of all holidays, Thanksgiving! While it&amp;rsquo;s difficult to not be able to spend it with family, we were able to make good memories of it by spending it in the Mountains at a ski resort. Hopefully this is something we will make a tradition out of, because it was a lot of fun!
We went up on Wednesday and left a little early in hopes of beating the traffic into the mountains.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Grady Farm</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/11/the-grady-farm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2015 09:37:32 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/11/the-grady-farm/</guid>
      <description>Grady Family Farm - circa 1980   The picture is of the farm I grew up on that is 13 miles north and west of Marquette, Iowa- The present owners took down the barn, chicken house, granary, and corn crib- but curiously left the outhouse that is south of the house. The picture is looking to the west and the farm my mother grew up on is the one in the distant west, just in viewing- you can not see the church and cemetery that is less than on quarter of a mile to the right in the picture- St Pius V Catholic Church, Cherry Mound where my Mom and Dad are buried and where I mowed every summer for about six years- I knew every tombstone in the cemetery and when someone wanted to know where their relative was buried, the priest would contact me and I would show them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Casa Bonita</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/11/casa-bonita/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2015 20:49:12 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/11/casa-bonita/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to a new section of the blog, the Weekends section. These entries will cover things that we do as a family on the weekends. From hikes to restaurants to whatever else. Since we&amp;rsquo;re new to the area, most things we do here are new to us!
Casa Bonita Last weekend&amp;rsquo;s destination was Casa Bonita, &amp;ldquo;The Most Entertaining Restaurant In The World.&amp;rdquo;
  Casa Bonita   That&amp;rsquo;s their tag line, anyway.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bike Hangar Idea</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/11/bike-hangar-idea/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2015 20:02:33 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/11/bike-hangar-idea/</guid>
      <description>Thought I would put this out there as I had never thought of this before. We needed to hang our bikes in the garage. I didn&amp;rsquo;t really want to spend too much money on hardware, so we just got the cheap hooks that you can get at Home Depot - they were like $1.50 each. I typically don&amp;rsquo;t like using those hooks because it&amp;rsquo;s a pain to find studs to drill and put them into, and then when you do, it rarely lines up with the thing you want to hang.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adoption Woes</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/11/adoption-woes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2015 10:22:35 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/11/adoption-woes/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;ve known us for any amount of time, you know that we are, and have been in the process of adopting from the Democratic Republic of Congo for the past 3 years. It has been a long, LONG process.
TL;DR; Last month, the Congolese government has dashed our hopes of completing this adoption in the near timeframe. It is questionable if we will ever be able to complete it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quinton&#39;s Snowboard</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/11/quintons-snowboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Nov 2015 21:44:52 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/11/quintons-snowboard/</guid>
      <description>We are first year Coloradoans, so we are behaving like them. We purchased season ski passes, even though it is next to impossible to get into the mountains due to all the traffic. We are in the process of upgrading all of our equipment because no Coloradoan would be caught dead with the 10 year old skis that we have!
Since we are planning on going to the mountains for our first trip over Thanksgiving, we needed to get some equipment for Quinton and Ethan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Kitchen Discovery</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/11/a-kitchen-discovery/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2015 20:55:58 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/11/a-kitchen-discovery/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;re redoing our kitchen right now. I have a long post queued up for some time in the near future to go through some of the experience and show pictures. It&amp;rsquo;s been fun, but it&amp;rsquo;s also been interesting.
Last weekend we finally got to the point where we could take out our old lower cabinets and replace them with the new ones. The plan was to demolish on Saturday and install on Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quinton&#39;s Christmas List</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/11/quintons-christmas-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2015 08:38:04 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/11/quintons-christmas-list/</guid>
      <description>Jenny had Quinton write a letter to Santa. Since he was also typing a thank you letter to his grandparents on my e-mail, he decided to e-mail his letter to Santa this year. I came across it in my drafts folder and found it amusing.
 dear santa i want a ps vita a dirt bike a soccer ball a trampoline football gear mostly a dirt bike and a ps vita and halo 5 and ps 4 and 100 dollars and a golden retreiver.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Blog Home</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/new-blog-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Nov 2015 10:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/new-blog-home/</guid>
      <description>Announcing (DogsButtBrew.com)[http://dogsbuttbrew.com]! It&amp;rsquo;s with some degree of excitement that I announce that I am retiring e-and-quin.blogspot.com. Over the years, the Blogger platform has served me well. It has captured many memories that I enjoy reading and re-reading.
No, I&amp;rsquo;m not giving up blogging. In fact, I&amp;rsquo;m doubling down on it! I&amp;rsquo;m just giving up on Blogger. As I said, it has served me well, but my interests have moved on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Now With Comments</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/11/now-with-comments/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2015 10:12:59 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/11/now-with-comments/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;re here, great! I&amp;rsquo;m not sure how you found it because I haven&amp;rsquo;t yet linked the old blog to this one, nor have I done any advertisement or anything (I probably won&amp;rsquo;t ever advertise).
There will be a larger series on how the new blog was constructed and some of the technical ins and outs, but I wanted to quickly mention that the blog is soft-launched, and today I added the ability to comment using Discus, a SaaS based commenting and discuussion platform.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quinton and Fun With Words</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/11/quinton-and-fun-with-words/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2015 19:21:14 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/11/quinton-and-fun-with-words/</guid>
      <description>New words for the dictionary:
becept /bee * &amp;lsquo;cept/
Origin - from what I can tell, a combination of except and besides. Perfectly encapsulates the meaning of both in different situations.
Example: &amp;ldquo;Everyone is having fun becept me.&amp;rdquo;
w&amp;rsquo;bout /wuh * &amp;lsquo;bout/
Origin - shortened version of &amp;ldquo;what about.&amp;rdquo; Not particularly interesting for its meaning but rather it&amp;rsquo;s usage.
Example: &amp;ldquo;The moon doesn&amp;rsquo;t have it&amp;rsquo;s own light - it only reflects the sun&amp;rsquo;s light.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>There, I Fixed It</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/10/there-i-fixed-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2015 21:34:14 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/10/there-i-fixed-it/</guid>
      <description>Quinton has really wanted a remote control airplane for quite some time. Uncle Blaine bought him a remote control helicopter a little over a year ago that he absolutely loved for the entirety of the 10 minutes before he lost it in the trees. Over the years he&amp;rsquo;s amassed quite the aresnal of cheap, crappy remote control things - cars, trucks, motorcycles - each one cheaper and crappier than the last.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skype with Mireille</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/10/skype-with-mireille/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2015 09:53:21 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/10/skype-with-mireille/</guid>
      <description>We got to Skype with Mireille this morning. It&amp;rsquo;s always bittersweet talking with her. On the one hand, you want to make sure you keep in touch so she at least has some sort of connection, but on another hand it just sort of hurts to talk with her. When we talk with her, we are reminded of the situation that we&amp;rsquo;re in, whereas other times we can sort of ignore it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hide and Seek</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/10/hide-and-seek/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2015 09:52:05 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2015/10/hide-and-seek/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s hard to play Hide and Seek when you have a dog&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2015 21:45:01 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/about/</guid>
      <description>About The Hydrant The Hydrant is the home space for me, Brandon Grady. It represents my random musings about things in which I have interest.
Myself, I am a married father of three living in the greater Denver, CO area. I like to brew my own beer, watch movies, officiate high school football games, program stuff using Ruby, Go, and JavaScript. We do a lot of home improvements. My wife and I like to run and try to stay fit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Glenwood Springs, CO</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/glenwood-springs-co/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2015 10:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/glenwood-springs-co/</guid>
      <description>A few weeks ago (well, over a month ago now), we took a trip to Glenwood Springs, CO. It was a trip to celebrate the end of summer and to get away for a little bit before the kids started school the next week. It was a nice long weekend, though the traffic coming down from the mountains left little to be desired.
At a high level, we walked around, went on some long bike rides along the Colorado River, visited a wild west theme park on the top of a mountain, took a cave tour, and did the hike at Hanging Lake.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>So... We moved to Colorado...</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/so...-we-moved-to-colorado.../</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2015 13:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/so...-we-moved-to-colorado.../</guid>
      <description>In case you haven&amp;rsquo;t been following the blog&amp;hellip; Er, wait&amp;hellip;
So we moved to Colorado. We&amp;rsquo;ve been eyeing a move up for awhile. This was the year to do it when Ethan was transitioning to High School and before Quin got too entrenched in his activities and the area. So we set out to do something new, and Colorado won out.
The thing that allowed us to do all of this was a company that decided to hire me as, get this, the Executive Director of Technology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Congo Children&#39;s Fund</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/congo-childrens-fund/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2015 10:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/congo-childrens-fund/</guid>
      <description>This won&amp;rsquo;t really benefit Mireille, but a family in much the same situation we are in has started a fund to help bring food to orphans in need in Kinshasa. We&amp;rsquo;re planning on doing some fund raising to help this organization. Despite your feelings on international adoption, it&amp;rsquo;s hard to disagree with helping children to get nutritious food and water.
Please consider donating.
http://www.congochildrensfund.org
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Now with Video!!!</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/now-with-video/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2015 18:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/now-with-video/</guid>
      <description>Update the video permissions have been changed and should work now. Thanks for your patience while I learn to use computers&amp;hellip;
As my brother pointed out, my Congo posts came out with images that looked like they should be videos. They were supposed to be videos! I&amp;rsquo;ve gone through the lot and switched them out for YouTube videos where applicable. Please go through from Day 1 and see some motion you may not have seen the first time through!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Great Congolese Caper - Day 8 - On the way home</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-great-congolese-caper-day-8-on-the-way-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2015 14:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-great-congolese-caper-day-8-on-the-way-home/</guid>
      <description>Kinshasa - Day 7 My last day. I feel bad, but I was looking forward to this in some ways. Over the last 5 days, Mireille has turned into a typical 2 year old, and taking care of 2 year olds is HARD! Particularly by yourself. Luckily, when you have nothing else to do, it makes it much easier. It&amp;rsquo;s much easier to completely invest in what the child is saying and doing, which I did - once I got done showering, washing the dishes, and packing (I&amp;rsquo;m such an adult).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Great Congolese Caper - Day 7 - Kinshasa</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-great-congolese-caper-day-7-kinshasa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2015 11:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-great-congolese-caper-day-7-kinshasa/</guid>
      <description>Kinshasa - Day 6 Getting down to it! Today I&amp;rsquo;m nervous again, but that hasn&amp;rsquo;t changed much from day 1 here, or day -2 for that matter.
Last night started out rough. Mireille was restless. She didn&amp;rsquo;t fall out of bed, but was up like 3 times up until about 1:00 AM. She didn&amp;rsquo;t cry or anything, but she got out of bed and asked me to hold her. After rocking her to sleep the other two times, I convinced her to just sleep in my bed with me the last time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Great Congolese Caper - Day 6 - Kinshasa</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-great-congolese-caper-day-6-kinshasa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2015 11:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-great-congolese-caper-day-6-kinshasa/</guid>
      <description>Kinshasa - Day 5 It&amp;rsquo;s a hotel day - all day at the hotel. It&amp;rsquo;s a good and a bad thing. Getting out would be nice simply to stave off the boredom, but it also allows for a very concentrated, focused time for just hanging out with your child - something I&amp;rsquo;m not sure I ever did so much with the boys, or at the very least don&amp;rsquo;t do it anymore…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Great Congolese Caper - Day 5 - Kinshasa and Surrounding Areas</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-great-congolese-caper-day-5-kinshasa-and-surrounding-areas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2015 09:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-great-congolese-caper-day-5-kinshasa-and-surrounding-areas/</guid>
      <description>Kinshasa - Day 4 Bad habits I&amp;rsquo;m already allowing my daughter to develop, because, hey, she&amp;rsquo;s under a lot of stress just hanging out with me. I hope I&amp;rsquo;m not setting myself up for bad things later:
 Drinking soda - this is a big no-no for the sub-40ers in our household, but Mireille has already had soda every day I&amp;rsquo;ve been with her. She likes it. Not brushing her teeth - it&amp;rsquo;s difficult enough to get her to open her mouth for me, much less brush.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Great Congolese Caper - Day 3 - Kinshasa</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-great-congolese-caper-day-3-kinshasa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2015 08:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-great-congolese-caper-day-3-kinshasa/</guid>
      <description>Kinshasa - Day 2 After a rough night night, I managed to get up and get myself together by 9:00, when Papa John was schedule to show up so we could go grocery shopping. By the time he showed up, though, it was 10:30. Traffic… Common problem in Kinshasa! By then, we took off to ShopRite, a local, modern supermarket, where I purchased my groceries for the week. It was a little nerve wracking buying groceries for the week, let me tell you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Great Congolese Caper - Day 4 - Kinshasa</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-great-congolese-caper-day-4-kinshasa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2015 08:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-great-congolese-caper-day-4-kinshasa/</guid>
      <description>Kinshasa - Day 3 Today, I met my daughter! Yes, I met her yesterday, but that version of Mireille was guarded, afraid, and sullen. She&amp;rsquo;s asleep now - hopefully for the night. Today we made very good progress, and I am beyond excited!
The morning started out not so well. I slept terribly last night, by that I mean I didn&amp;rsquo;t really sleep at all. I fell asleep around 10:00, but Mireille fell out of bed at 10:45, and I didn&amp;rsquo;t sleep after that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Great Congolese Caper - Day 2 - Kinshasa</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-great-congolese-caper-day-2-kinshasa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2015 08:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-great-congolese-caper-day-2-kinshasa/</guid>
      <description>Kinshasa - Day 1 - Airport to the Hotel I was happy when I landed in Paris that I finally got a text message back from my guide, Papa John. That made me feel much more comfortable about landing in Kinshasa, seeing as how I’ve read many bad stories about the experience.
It is 6:30 local time on Sunday evening as I land, and it is completely dark already. Since I was in the middle of the plane, I didn’t get a good look at the landing, but what I could see, there didn’t seem to be too many lights.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Great Congolese Caper - Day 2 - Paris, France</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-great-congolese-caper-day-2-paris-france/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2015 08:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-great-congolese-caper-day-2-paris-france/</guid>
      <description>Paris - Charles De Gaul Airport I landed around 8:00 local time in Charles De Gaul Airport outside of Paris, France. For my first trip to France, it was a little underwhelming. I suppose it’s true what they say that you don’t really visit a country when you visit the airport…
After disembarking my flight, I followed the hallways and signage to where my next flight was taking off, Terminal 2E the K gates (I think).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Great Congolese Caper - Day 1 - In the Air</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-great-congolese-caper-day-1-in-the-air/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2015 08:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-great-congolese-caper-day-1-in-the-air/</guid>
      <description>Seat 9a to MSP Leg one is done. Yes, the easiest leg, but significant nonetheless. My seat wasn&amp;rsquo;t bad - I was on the window next to an older woman who didn&amp;rsquo;t take up too much room, so that was good.
Things I learned from this step of the journey:
 My earbuds suck. So much so that I have already replaced them with some cheap on ear headphones so I don&amp;rsquo;t have to monkey with them the whole time on the next two flights.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Great Congolese Caper - Day 2 - In the Air</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-great-congolese-caper-day-2-in-the-air/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2015 08:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-great-congolese-caper-day-2-in-the-air/</guid>
      <description>Seat 33G to Kinshasa I&amp;rsquo;m Tired!
Despite there only being like 50 people in the gate area, this flight is completely full! I&amp;rsquo;m on the aisle in the middle section among the cattle again. The seat&amp;rsquo;s not bad, though there&amp;rsquo;s little leg room due to a heater or some box that is in my leg area. This is a cutting edge plane&amp;hellip; from the 90s. It has screens in each of the seatbacks that are touch sensitive (sort of) and retain the old 4:3 aspect ration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Great Congolese Caper - Day 1 - Milwaukee</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-great-congolese-caper-day-1-milwaukee/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2015 08:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-great-congolese-caper-day-1-milwaukee/</guid>
      <description>Saturday, 7-Feb-2015, Milwaukee, WI, USA So it begins… The trip I&amp;rsquo;ve been both dreading and anticipating has finally started. As I sit here in General Mitchell International Airport, I am anxious and hopeful at what the next week will bring.
        We&amp;rsquo;re adopting a child from the Democratic Republic of Congo. Mireille is her name, and she is 2 and a half years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mireille</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/mireille/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2014 15:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/mireille/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m outing us to the world. Well, Jenny outed us on Facebook about a month ago, but this post makes it official - we are in the process of adopting a little girl from the Democratic Republic of Congo. In fact, we&amp;rsquo;ve been matched with our daughter for 18 months, and are in fact her legal parents by that country&amp;rsquo;s laws. In a very strange combination of power plays and international politics, however, we are unable to bring her home to the United States.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Great Mouse Caper</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-great-mouse-caper/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2014 15:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-great-mouse-caper/</guid>
      <description>History Quin loves pets. Ignore the fact that Heinz is our pet and he rarely is very nice to him. In fact, the nicest he typically is to him is when he ignores him. But if he finds a toad in the yard, or a stray bug on a window, he gets his ice cream pale, fills it with a little water and some leaves, and puts the poor thing in there until we force him to release the poor animal before they become a dead animal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quin Quickies</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/quin-quickies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2014 11:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/quin-quickies/</guid>
      <description>The Circumcision This weekend, my brother-in-law turned 50 and we were invited to his party. On the 30 minute drive to his house, Jenny and I were behaving like the good parents that we are and allowing the kids to listen to the Comedy Central channel on Sirius Satellite Radio, something of which we are currently enjoying a free trial. The content on the station isn&amp;rsquo;t all that, well, appropriate, but we count on the kids not listening much like they don&amp;rsquo;t listen to us - ever.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Older Kids...</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/older-kids.../</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2014 10:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/older-kids.../</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been awhile since I&amp;rsquo;ve written anything about Ethan. He&amp;rsquo;s getting older, as you might guess. It&amp;rsquo;s actually been quite shocking of late. In a year&amp;rsquo;s time he passed his mother up in height and weight and his voice has reached a near approximation of a man&amp;rsquo;s voice - a small man maybe, but a man&amp;rsquo;s voice nonetheless. His shoulders and arms bear resemblance to the Tibbett side I can only assume since they have grown muscular despite him not really doing much in the line of working them out, and he can grow a fair mustache.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Big, Fat, and Stupid</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/big-fat-and-stupid/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2014 10:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/big-fat-and-stupid/</guid>
      <description>A couple of weeks ago I got an e-mail from an old co-worker who still worked at my old place of employment. It was a complimentary e-mail, fairly light in nature, which made it all the more mysterious why the e-mail header on my iPad read, &amp;ldquo;To: Big, Fat, and Stupid - From: &amp;lt;name omitted&amp;gt;&amp;rdquo;. Hmm&amp;hellip; I asked him why that was what he had called me in his address book and he claimed innocense.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summer Vacation 2014 - Day 5 - Saturday</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/summer-vacation-2014-day-5-saturday/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2014 21:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/summer-vacation-2014-day-5-saturday/</guid>
      <description>That&amp;rsquo;s right, we&amp;rsquo;re going a little Tarantino here with the time jumping and what-not. By now it&amp;rsquo;s been nearly two weeks and the scars are just starting to form. This will be a blissfully short retrospective on the fifth day of our summer vacation, lest it is lost for all time to the memory of the harrowing experience of the trip home.
Saturday was not at all unlike Friday in most regards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summer Vacation 2014 - There and Back Again</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/summer-vacation-2014-there-and-back-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2014 23:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/summer-vacation-2014-there-and-back-again/</guid>
      <description>Introduction 9:30 on Monday, June 30, 2014. We&amp;rsquo;re all showered, Quin is in bed, Jenny&amp;rsquo;s powering through another bout with Facebook, I&amp;rsquo;m watching The Wolverine with Ethan&amp;hellip; It&amp;rsquo;s easy to forget about the events of the last 36 hours. It&amp;rsquo;s taken me an hour to type up the summary on this page, so I can only imagine how long the actual account will take me. This will be an epic, to be sure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summer Vacation 2014 - Day 4 - Friday</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/summer-vacation-2014-day-4-friday/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2014 23:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/summer-vacation-2014-day-4-friday/</guid>
      <description>Friday started our first full day at camp. We had hoped to get a vacation run in this morning, but alas, it was not meant to be. We were able to get moving in time for our 8:30 breakfast meet-up for new families. New families were quite the thing this year with the camp doubling in size or so over the last couple of years.
After breakfast we dropped the kids off with their age appropriate groups, each color coded by shirt color.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summer Vacation 2014 - Days 1-3 - Tuednesday and Thursday</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/summer-vacation-2014-days-1-3-tuednesday-and-thursday/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2014 00:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/summer-vacation-2014-days-1-3-tuednesday-and-thursday/</guid>
      <description>This year&amp;rsquo;s edition of summer vacation is to the Mile High City where we are attending an African and Caribbean Heritage Camp. It&amp;rsquo;s been a few years since we&amp;rsquo;ve been in Denver in the summer, so we were pretty excited to get things started.
The plan was to make the 15 hour drive from Tuesday through Wednesday morning. After 2/3 day of work, we packed up the car and&amp;hellip; waited for Target to deliver some new patio furniture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spring Break 2014 - Home!</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/spring-break-2014-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2014 22:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/spring-break-2014-home/</guid>
      <description>Raining again this morning. As we were packing our room, I was thinking on my post from last night and how I had forgotten to put some important color on it. After the mall, the three boys (Ethan, Quin, and Loudon) and I went swimming in the pool. After we had swum for awhile, a couple of young girls came in - I would estimate they were around 10 or 11 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spring Break 2014 - Mall of America</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/spring-break-2014-mall-of-america/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2014 22:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/spring-break-2014-mall-of-america/</guid>
      <description>The day started REALLY late this morning. The plan was to meet Uncle Bryce and Loudon at the Mall of America (MOA) at 10:00 to do rides and other fun stuff. When 9:00 rolled around and we were still having difficulty getting Quin out of bed, we knew we were going to have to delay a bit. It seems that vacation finally caught up to the 6 year old, who went to bed at midnight the night previous and hadn&amp;rsquo;t slept much to date.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spring Break 2014 - The Museum</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/spring-break-2014-the-museum/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2014 21:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/spring-break-2014-the-museum/</guid>
      <description>Ethan and I knocked one of our meager goals for this vacation off this morning, we had breakfast at Taco Bell! Yeah, we have lofty goals. We piled down a couple of waffle tacos and breakfast burritos each and headed into St. Paul to take in the Minnesota Museum of Science.
The MMS is one of the better science museums I&amp;rsquo;ve been to, quite honestly. We easily spent 3.5 hours there without even doing a movie!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spring Break 2014 - Minnesota</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/spring-break-2014-minnesota/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2014 22:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/spring-break-2014-minnesota/</guid>
      <description>We departed Neillsville sometime between 9:00 and 10:00 AM, right on schedule. Jenny&amp;rsquo;s plans didn&amp;rsquo;t have us overtaxing ourselves today. The plan was to hit a couple of tourist stops south of the Twin Cities, then drive up to spend the late afternoon/evening at Blaine&amp;rsquo;s in Inver Grove Heights.
Our first stop was at (LARK Toys)[http://www.larktoys.com/] in Kellogg Minnesota. This was not our typical drive for a vacation as it involved ZERO interstate time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vacation - The Emergency</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/vacation-the-emergency/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2014 23:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/vacation-the-emergency/</guid>
      <description>Vacation just isn&amp;rsquo;t vacation until there&amp;rsquo;s a trip to the E.R. So today officially started our vacation!
This afternoon was pretty nice outside. It was around 60 degrees, not too much wind, so the kids went outside and played baseball. They were chasing the balls all around the property, including through some longer brush and what-not.
After a long day of playing, and a long night the night before, Quin was pretty tired.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spring Break 2014 - Happy Easter!</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/spring-break-2014-happy-easter/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2014 13:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/spring-break-2014-happy-easter/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Grady Spring Break, 2014! The itenerary is quite extensive, to be sure, and the destinations exotic!
The trip started yesterday where we left the house in the van around 9:00 AM, heading north! Yes, you read that correctly, we headed NORTH for spring break. Didn&amp;rsquo;t say we were all that bright! The first stop was probably just off of MTV&amp;rsquo;s list of destinations for this year&amp;rsquo;s spring break, Neillsville, WI.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>6 years ago today...</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/6-years-ago-today.../</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2014 07:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/6-years-ago-today.../</guid>
      <description>It was Saturday. I don&amp;rsquo;t remember many of the details of the day, unfortunately, but what I do remember is that we got the call that the birth mother had finally completed the harrowing experience of giving birth to who would come to be our child through the institution of domestic adoption. Over the years we&amp;rsquo;ve found that we&amp;rsquo;ve been given the gift of a wonderful, healthy, smart, and strong boy with whom we get to spend time with, learn from, be perplexed and frustrated by, and love on a day to day basis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quinny Quickies</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/quinny-quickies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2014 21:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/quinny-quickies/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the new year! With a new year comes a renewed hope that I will actually keep this thing up to date. Here goes this week&amp;rsquo;s attempt!
Quin continues to grow up fast. Despite that, he still has the occasional accident at night where he wets his bed - and when he does, he wets it epically (his word). So we typically put him in a pull-up in the evening, which he takes like a good sport.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Couple of Quick Updates</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/couple-of-quick-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2013 16:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/couple-of-quick-updates/</guid>
      <description>We just got back from a vacation in our nation&amp;rsquo;s capital. This post is not about that, however, but I wanted to warn you that an update&amp;rsquo;s coming about that in the coming days/weeks.
A couple of quick ones, though. First, Ethan has had a couple of milestones in the last few weeks. As a seventh grader, Ethan decided he was going to run for his school&amp;rsquo;s student council as the vice president.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Too funny to pass up...</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/too-funny-to-pass-up.../</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2013 17:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/too-funny-to-pass-up.../</guid>
      <description>I haven&amp;rsquo;t blogged in awhile. Part of it is sheer laziness. That compounds on itself in that there are just too many things to blog about so I just can&amp;rsquo;t find the time to get it done. I&amp;rsquo;m in that situation right now. But something happened a couple of weeks ago that was too funny not to document - so here goes.
We went to Noah&amp;rsquo;s Ark - America&amp;rsquo;s Largest Waterpark - last week for a last ditch summer celebration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sweet Vacation - Alabama</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/sweet-vacation-alabama/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2013 22:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/sweet-vacation-alabama/</guid>
      <description>Home at last! Strange way to start a blog about our vacation to Alabama, but I ended up not really writing during the vacation - something I&amp;rsquo;m sure I&amp;rsquo;ll regret in the end as I&amp;rsquo;m sure there is some level of excruciating detail that I will miss out on by not doing this in real time, but in the end I&amp;rsquo;m sure it will save you, dear reader, from the droning on that would undoubtedly result from a real-time, blow-by-blow that I would have otherwise forced you to endure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Late February Update</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/late-february-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2013 20:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/late-february-update/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;He&amp;rsquo;s On Fire!&amp;rdquo; When I was in college, one of my favorite games on the Sega Genesis was NBA Jam. It was great. You could crank out a game in 15 minutes, everybody could play, and best of all, most of the time, I would win. A couple of weekends ago I got nostalgic. Ethan has all sorts of time to play all these complicated games. I want nothing more than to do that, but have other priorities than an 11 year old boy does (getting old sucks).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Four Eyes!</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/four-eyes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2013 08:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/four-eyes/</guid>
      <description>n has finally succumb to the fates of his genes, or I suppose since we&amp;rsquo;re (yes, that was intentional) learning about heredity in science right now, the alleles that he&amp;rsquo;s been gifted from Jenny and I, and has gotten glasses. His prescription is very mild - he only needs them for class, pretty much, not for sports or basically anything else. But it has begun. Later this year we will probably be putting him in braces (for his teeth, not his legs).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#39;Cause I like to party...</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/cause-i-like-to-party.../</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jan 2013 20:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/cause-i-like-to-party.../</guid>
      <description>I have a running joke with the boys. Any time they ask me a question that begs me to define reasons for behavior, I like to answer, &amp;ldquo;&amp;lsquo;cause I like to party.&amp;rdquo; It&amp;rsquo;s a brilliant quote from Talladega Nights - if you&amp;rsquo;re not familiar, check it out here:
  Anyway, like most things I&amp;rsquo;d prefer they didn&amp;rsquo;t, both boys have started using it in daily conversations, with improving timing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick Updates</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/quick-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2013 18:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/quick-updates/</guid>
      <description>Quin&amp;rsquo;s stretches
Toronto phone call - pless 2. Want to talk to Heinzie?
Halloween casinova.
Ethan&amp;rsquo;s soccer tourney
The booby man.
Editorial Note - I&amp;rsquo;m leaving this in here since it came across. I do remember a couple of things from it, but not nearly enough. I should always finish my blogs&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Halloween Update</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/halloween-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2012 21:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/halloween-update/</guid>
      <description>Adoption It&amp;rsquo;s all begun again. Jenny and I have started pursuing another adoption, this time an international one through the Democratic Republic of Congo (formerly Zaire). So far much has been the same as last time around - filling out paperwork, background checks, talking about my feelings - fun stuff. We&amp;rsquo;re getting to the point where we will be having a social worker come to the house to interview us, so we were explaining to Quinton what we were doing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Little Triathetes</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/my-little-triathetes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Aug 2012 20:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/my-little-triathetes/</guid>
      <description>Last weekend was the annual &amp;ldquo;Tri-ing for Children&amp;rsquo;s Triathlon,&amp;rdquo; a weekend long set of triathlons to benefit Children&amp;rsquo;s Hospital here in town. Jenny and I were both signed up to do the sprint triathlon, a 1/4 mile swim, 15 mile bike, then 3.1 mile run. We&amp;rsquo;ve done it a few years in a row now, so that&amp;rsquo;s not what I&amp;rsquo;m writing about - this year we decided to let our kids participate in the kid&amp;rsquo;s event on the Saturday prior to the adult races.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Little Quinny</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/little-quinny/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2012 21:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/little-quinny/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever heard the &amp;ldquo;Little Johnny&amp;rdquo; jokes? For several reasons, I have a feeling that they might one day be replaced by &amp;ldquo;Little Quinny&amp;rdquo; jokes. Here&amp;rsquo;s an example of one - Little Johnny was in class learning his ABCs. The teacher was asking the class to name something with each letter of the alphabet in order. Little Johnny raised his hand for each letter, but she kept skipping him thinking that he would say something bad, like &amp;ldquo;ass&amp;rdquo; for A and &amp;ldquo;butt&amp;rdquo; for B.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quinny the Spy</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/quinny-the-spy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2012 22:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/quinny-the-spy/</guid>
      <description>Quin and I were at home together the other day - I can&amp;rsquo;t remember why. Jenny and Ethan were out somewhere, I think to get Ethan a haircut. We opened the garage and heard something flying around in there. Before long, Quin had spotted the culprit - a bird had gotten itself stuck in the garage. He was having a hard time finding his way out, and Quin was enthralled! I went into the house and started putting things away from my day&amp;rsquo;s work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Memorial Day!</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/happy-memorial-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 21:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/happy-memorial-day/</guid>
      <description>We had the opportunity to travel to Spread Eagle, WI near Iron Mountain, MI for Memorial Day this year. A friend of ours works for a company that owns a &amp;ldquo;cabin&amp;rdquo; on a lake up there, which they allow their employees to rent by the week during the year. When say cabin, I mean a 5 bedroom, 4000 square foot, modern home that is situated on a lake up north. So we joined 3 other families up there for the weekend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Mother&#39;s Day</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/happy-mothers-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 May 2012 21:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/happy-mothers-day/</guid>
      <description>My boys really don&amp;rsquo;t think much, normally, before a Hallmark Holiday like Mother&amp;rsquo;s Day. Last night, however, Ethan asked me (discretely) what mom&amp;rsquo;s favorite breakfast was. I told him that she liked an egg over easy with toast. He nodded, then said that he&amp;rsquo;d like to make that for her in the morning.
So this morning, Quin (and I, I suppose) woke up a little after 6:00. He watched Garfield while I watched the inside of my eyelids for an hour more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Westward Expansion</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/westward-expansion/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2012 07:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/westward-expansion/</guid>
      <description>I had an interesting experience as a parent last night and had to share it with the world, because that&amp;rsquo;s what we do in the day and age of over sharing&amp;hellip; Ethan has a test in Social Studies today. They are covering early history of the United states, from Washington&amp;rsquo;s presidency through the war of 1812. As an aside, I make a way better fifth grader as a 39 year old than I ever did as a 10 year old&amp;hellip; That is to say that this information is way more interesting to me today than it ever was 30 years ago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Potpourri</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/potpourri/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Mar 2012 22:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/potpourri/</guid>
      <description>The Big Update First, for the prerequisite apology. My wife and my mother both have scolded me for not having an update out here for going on 2 months now, so here is the big update.
Quin Does Music Over the last 2 months, Quin has put his musical skills on display. He enjoys listening to music on his CD player in his room - last night he told his babysitter all about the music player he had in his room with at least 10 CDs!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>January update</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/january-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2012 20:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/january-update/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s tough for me to write today because my favorite group of millionaires lost to somebody else&amp;rsquo;s favorite group of millionaires in a game I was sure would go my millionaire&amp;rsquo;s way. Oh well, we must persevere!
It&amp;rsquo;s been a typical busy couple of weeks. Today was one of Ethan&amp;rsquo;s last functions as a Cub Scout, the Pinewood Derby. For most kids this is an exciting event, but for Ethan and I, we sort of dread it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Great West Adventure - Day 9 - Travel day</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/great-west-adventure-day-9-travel-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2011 22:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/great-west-adventure-day-9-travel-day/</guid>
      <description>The last day of vacation is always the dreaded travel day. We were lucky enough to be able to get some laundry done at mom and dad&amp;rsquo;s before we left (OK, Jenny got it done), so we (Jenny) would not have to do it when we (Jenny) got home. But travel days are always a pain. Most of the morning was spent biding time until our flight. We departed pretty early for the airport - we had a 1:00 flight and arrived at the airport at 11:00, so we had plenty of time to get some pizza and wait at the gate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Great West Adventure - Day 8 - Don&#39;t look down...</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/great-west-adventure-day-8-dont-look-down.../</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2011 00:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/great-west-adventure-day-8-dont-look-down.../</guid>
      <description>Day 8 was to be a relaxing day! In that right, it wasn&amp;rsquo;t too bad. Mom and dad wanted to show off their new winter home state to us, though, so we headed out of town on Arizona 88 around 10:30 to catch up on some history and engineering marvels. Our first stop was Tortilla Flat, a (very) small stop on the way up to the Roosevelt Dam on the Salt River.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Great West Adventure - Day 7 - Permission to Board</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/great-west-adventure-day-7-permission-to-board/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2011 23:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/great-west-adventure-day-7-permission-to-board/</guid>
      <description>There was no plan in the works for today other than to drive back to Phoenix at some point. Small portion of the day, only 6.5 hours&amp;hellip; Surprisingly, though, it seemed relaxed since we didn&amp;rsquo;t have an itinerary. So we started out the day like we did any other day on vacation, we ate at a local breakfast establishment. This time we found a local favorite, Panera Bread. Excellent bagels and sandwiches - oh who am I kidding, we just wanted something fast.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Great West Adventure - Day 6 - It&#39;s a zoo out there</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/great-west-adventure-day-6-its-a-zoo-out-there/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2011 11:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/great-west-adventure-day-6-its-a-zoo-out-there/</guid>
      <description>In case there was any question to the subtitle of yesterday&amp;rsquo;s post, we were watching the weather where the cute weather lady exclaimed that the clouds were pretty moist and deep, and that she wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be surprised to see them start to rain at any time. I found that amusing - I suppose I&amp;rsquo;ve never really progressed past the age of 12 as far as my maturity level goes&amp;hellip;
I again find myself 3 days tardy in posting this, so I think this will be pretty short.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Great West Adventure - Day 5 - Moist and Deep</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/great-west-adventure-day-5-moist-and-deep/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2011 23:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/great-west-adventure-day-5-moist-and-deep/</guid>
      <description>Man, I have to start doing these as they happen. This is my third log today!!! To get me through it, I&amp;rsquo;ve gone to the fridge to finish off my San Diego brew sampler with a Karl Strauss Brewing Company Boardwalk Black Rye. Tasty!!!
Today&amp;rsquo;s plan was to go to Seaworld. We figured we would do things a little differently today since we completely missed supper yesterday, so we opted for a smaller breakfast of Subway sandwiches and Starbucks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Great West Adventure - Day 4 - A Ton of Bricks</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/great-west-adventure-day-4-a-ton-of-bricks/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2011 23:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/great-west-adventure-day-4-a-ton-of-bricks/</guid>
      <description>Day 4 - San Diego. Today started out early with Quin waking around 6:00 - he&amp;rsquo;s getting better. He and I passed time playing iOS games on the iPhone and iPad in the second room of our suite while Jenny and Ethan grabbed 90 more minutes of sleep. By 7:30, Jenny got up and I hit the road for a quick run along the water.
By 9:00 we were off for a full day of vacationing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Great West Adventure - Day 3</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/great-west-adventure-day-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2011 22:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/great-west-adventure-day-3/</guid>
      <description>Since we were up by 6:00 anyway, we decided to try to get an early start at things, so we got ready and left by 8:00. My parents graciously lent us their vehicle - they are currently going without any sort of motorized vehicle of their own, relying instead on pedal power and favors from friends - so we loaded it up and took off on our 6 and 1/2 hour drive to San Diego.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Great West Adventure - Day 2</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/great-west-adventure-day-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2011 22:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/great-west-adventure-day-2/</guid>
      <description>As should probably be expected, since Quin went to bed at around 6:00 local time, he woke up around 4:30 local. I suppose the day was going to start early! We aimed to do quite a bit during this day, but ultimately decided to back it off a bit seeing as how we were still a bit groggy from the previous day&amp;rsquo;s travels. We did manage to get to the (Superstition Mountain Museum)[http://www.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Great West Adventure - Day 1</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/great-west-adventure-day-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2011 22:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/great-west-adventure-day-1/</guid>
      <description>3:45 AM - the alarm called out the start of our Great West Adventure. We were ticketed for a 7:00 departure from Milwaukee&amp;rsquo;s General Mitchell Airport. With 3 and 10 year old in tow, we didn&amp;rsquo;t want to leave anything to risk. So we all showered the night before, set the alarm for 3:45, and aimed to leave by 4:15.
The plan went off without a hitch - the crew was excited for the trip.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Staying in Shape</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/staying-in-shape/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2011 19:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/staying-in-shape/</guid>
      <description>Four years ago I ran in my first organized race since I graduated from high school when I participated in a sprint level triathlon. Since then I got in shape, got out of shape, lost 30 pounds, and have been in pretty decent shape since then. I&amp;rsquo;ve also managed to run in a half marathon, 2-200 mile relays, a number of 5Ks, 10Ks, a 20K, trail runs, road runs, you name it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome our new Family Member</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/welcome-our-new-family-member/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2011 07:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/welcome-our-new-family-member/</guid>
      <description>A big welcome to Heinz Doofenshmirtz Grady, our new puppy! Heinz comes to us from Little Buddies Rescue where he was dropped off from a puppy mill. We originally went there intending to adopt his sister, but she had already been spoken for by the time we got there. No worries! Heinz immediately endeared himself to us by fetching a toy for Ethan - a sure way to his heart!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Catching up with Quinton</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/catching-up-with-quinton/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2011 20:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/catching-up-with-quinton/</guid>
      <description>Neither Jenny nor I are very good about creating content for a baby book. In fact, I know I could not tell you where either of my children&amp;rsquo;s baby books are - perhaps in the top of our closet collecting dust. To capture memories, though, I&amp;rsquo;ve turned to this &amp;lsquo;blog. It worked out pretty well with Ethan so far, and Quinton has been no different. This post, then, is going to be some quick hitters to get into Quinton&amp;rsquo;s virtual baby book.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Buyer Beware</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/buyer-beware/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2011 21:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/buyer-beware/</guid>
      <description>A couple of weeks ago I ran a Webelos Scout Camp for Ethan and his Cub Scout cohorts (I know, the scouts are an intolerant bunch, but that doesn&amp;rsquo;t have to affect Ethan&amp;rsquo;s learning - let&amp;rsquo;s keep this among adults, shall we). The camp was pretty enjoyable - the boys were tasked with setting up the tents and camp themselves, had to take part in meal prep and cleanup, etc. Part of each camp is doing some kind of craft.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quin&#39;s First Movie</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/quins-first-movie/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2011 10:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/quins-first-movie/</guid>
      <description>Cars 2 is out! We&amp;rsquo;ve been waiting for awhile for this event as I had unofficially earmarked it as the first movie I would attempt to take Quinton to. I&amp;rsquo;m happy to report that there was nothing out of the ordinary that happened&amp;hellip; Yeah, boring blog post, but I&amp;rsquo;ll take it. I&amp;rsquo;d say he was as good as, if not a little better than Ethan when we took him to his first movie (I don&amp;rsquo;t recall which movie that was right now).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Mac is actually a Slot Machine!!!</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/my-mac-is-actually-a-slot-machine/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2011 21:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/my-mac-is-actually-a-slot-machine/</guid>
      <description>The other day, Jenny wanted me to burn a DVD for her to give to a person at church. I told her no problem, grabbed a blank DVD which I promptly attempted to insert into my Mac superdrive. I was somewhat surprised to find that I could not put the DVD into the drive, however. The computer did not say there was anything in the drive&amp;hellip; Quite strange, I thought. I suppose that there could be a disc in there that the OS didn&amp;rsquo;t know about somehow, a computer glitch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quinnie Quickie - TMI</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/quinnie-quickie-tmi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2011 21:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/quinnie-quickie-tmi/</guid>
      <description>File this one under TMI (that&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;too much information&amp;rdquo; for those not in the know). I believe I&amp;rsquo;ve discussed how Quin and I have pee races in this blog in the past. On Friday I went on a field trip with Ethan, and to make a very long story much shorter, I didn&amp;rsquo;t have much to drink during the day. When I got home, Quin wanted to have a pee race.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ethan&#39;s 10th Birthday Party</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/ethans-10th-birthday-party/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2011 14:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/ethans-10th-birthday-party/</guid>
      <description>My son is 10 years old! It&amp;rsquo;s tough really to get my head around that fact. I can only imagine what it is like for my parents to think about each year one of their aging children reaches another annual milestone.
9 was a pretty good year. Ethan&amp;rsquo;s shown a lot of improvement in school, thanks to his mother&amp;rsquo;s constant prodding and encouragement, he&amp;rsquo;s begun to really shine at the piano, and is starting to show real promise at soccer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Not my friend...</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/not-my-friend.../</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2011 18:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/not-my-friend.../</guid>
      <description>Quinton has experimented with lots of different ways to express his anger with people when they don&amp;rsquo;t do things he likes. Initially he liked to call people &amp;ldquo;poopy butt,&amp;rdquo; but we quickly tried to squash that. He then moved on to calling people &amp;ldquo;stupid,&amp;rdquo; which I think I like worse than poopy-butt. Lately he has categorized you as either his friend or not his friend. If he likes you particularly, or if he wants something from you, he tells you, &amp;ldquo;you&amp;rsquo;re my best friend (he pronounces it fwond).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More Adventures with Potty Training</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/more-adventures-with-potty-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2011 11:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/more-adventures-with-potty-training/</guid>
      <description>So - potty training boys&amp;hellip; Yeah&amp;hellip; Well, we&amp;rsquo;re still doing pretty well, but something new has reared its ugly head. Now that Quin knows when he has to go to the bathroom, and no longer does it in his pants, he has decided that he wants to find other things to pee on other than the toilet. Jenny caught him peeing in the bathtub the other day. Yesterday I stopped him from going in the garbage can and in the refrigerator, while Jenny caught him trying to spray down the plunger in the bathroom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adventures in Potty Training - again</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/adventures-in-potty-training-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2011 21:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/adventures-in-potty-training-again/</guid>
      <description>Boy, a week makes a big difference. As of today, Quin is a week without diapers (while conscious). Last Saturday, Quin finally decided that he really, REALLY wanted to wear his light-up shoes all the time. He woke up on Saturday morning and told me, &amp;ldquo;daddy, I want my light-up shoes.&amp;rdquo; I told him that he had to wear underwear if he wanted to do that, and he thought that was OK.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adventures in Potty Training</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/adventuresinpottytraining/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2011 21:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/adventuresinpottytraining/</guid>
      <description>I hate potty training. Jenny does, too, for the record. We&amp;rsquo;re no good at it. We rarely stay at home long enough to actually get our children into a rhythm of going every so often, we constantly forget to ask, and, well, it&amp;rsquo;s just pretty convenient to not have to worry about one of the four bladders in our posse at any given time of day. That said, we have (finally) started attempting some degree of potty training with Quin&amp;hellip; It&amp;rsquo;s not going so well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ski Vacation - Part II</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/ski-vacation-part-ii/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2011 20:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/ski-vacation-part-ii/</guid>
      <description>Tuesday was another ski day. This time it was adult ski day. Quin was going back to school, and Ethan was enrolled in Woodward, an indoor extreme ski and snowboard school. The warehouse is immense with fake snow ramps that empty into foam pits and trampoline sections to teach people how to tumble with ease through the air. I think Ethan was in for a fun day!
Ethan and I went down to Woodward to drop him off while Jenny dropped Quin off at school.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ski Trip - Interlude</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/ski-trip-interlude/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2011 16:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/ski-trip-interlude/</guid>
      <description>OK, I hope this goes away like almost all other things, because if it comes back and is something serious, I will look like a schmuck. But Ethan had his little spell with sickness yesterday, during which he thought he was going to throw up. He is a fan of the drama! Today, he has a low grade headache as far as I can tell, because he&amp;rsquo;s running around, tubing, and being a general 9 year old menace, but after sitting on the couch for 30 minutes drinking water and eating popcorn he started complaining of a headache again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ski Trip - Part I</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/skitripparti/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2011 10:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/skitripparti/</guid>
      <description>As I sit here in our rented condo, Ethan and Jenny are sitting on the couch studying social studies (Jenny struggles, so they need to study), Quin is watching Monsters, Inc. on the iPad, it is brisk and snowing outside while the gas fire burns warmly in the fireplace. Our first ski vacation in 7 years is in full swing!
This vacation finds us in the beautiful US Rocky Mountains outside of Denver, CO.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dancing Quin</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/dancing-quin/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2010 10:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/dancing-quin/</guid>
      <description>This video is hilarious, I think. Obviously there must be some degree of nature going on here as nobody of the non-adopted persuasion in our family can dance like this&amp;hellip;
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>6 Feet of Air</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/6-feet-of-air/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2010 13:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/6-feet-of-air/</guid>
      <description>Ethan belongs to the ski club at school. Last week we went skiing for the first time this year. Since Alpine is close to some friends of ours, we were able to meet up with them and their two kids, one of which, Justin, is Ethan&amp;rsquo;s age.
Justin and Ethan were having a blast! Justin snow boards, but Ethan skied. Of course, as soon as he saw Justin snow boarding, he immediately wanted to try that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmastime</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/christmastime/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2010 19:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/christmastime/</guid>
      <description>Wow, it&amp;rsquo;s been a long time again! I hope to post multiple times this week to get caught up. So much to talk about!
Well, it started a few weeks ago with Quin getting sick. The sickness eventually spread throughout the house but Quin got it first. The poor guy was just listless, throwing up, no fever, but sick. Every time he threw up over the course of several hours he just did it over the bucket, no crying or anything.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pre-puberty...</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/pre-puberty.../</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2010 07:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/pre-puberty.../</guid>
      <description>My relationship with my oldest son seems to be changing quite rapidly of late. This morning after getting out of the shower I noticed a can of Axe body spray sitting on the sink intended for me.
Let me rewind a little bit - over the past couple of months it has become evident to us that we had &amp;ldquo;the stinky kid&amp;rdquo; in school. Ethan would get into the car, or just walk near us, and you could certainly tell he was there!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monsters</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/monsters/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2010 19:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/monsters/</guid>
      <description>Quinny and I played &amp;ldquo;monsters&amp;rdquo; tonight. That little boy has quite an imagination. First he pestered me until I came to &amp;ldquo;play me.&amp;rdquo; So I followed him upstairs where he declared that he saw a monster. For the next 30 minutes we were hiding, kicking, and even kissing the poor monster until his daddy put him to bed (both monsters). Good times&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>St. Germain - Day 4</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/st.-germain-day-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2010 19:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/st.-germain-day-4/</guid>
      <description>It was windy and cool today, and I am training for a 1/2 marathon, so I picked today to do my long run of the week. I mapped out a route before we left that took me around the entire lake. While I was supposed to run only 10 miles, the prospect and symmetry of running around the entire lake was too good to pass up, so Tim Z. and I ended up running a little over 11.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>St. Germain - Day 5</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/st.-germain-day-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2010 19:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/st.-germain-day-5/</guid>
      <description>Still a little cool to start the day, so Quin and I made bacon and egg sandwiches for breakfast before we headed out fishing with Tim and Logan Ziegler. The fishing wasn&amp;rsquo;t all that great, but we did have a close encounter with an eagle. It was pretty awesome, actually. We heard something heavy in the trees, then the eagle flew just above the water not more than about 20 feet from the boat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>St. Germain - Day 6</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/st.-germain-day-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2010 19:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/st.-germain-day-6/</guid>
      <description>Last night was an early one - we were all pretty beat from 5 days of vacation, so by 10:00 pretty much everybody was in bed already.
Today started warmer, but still windy. After Jenny and I each had a run we ran into town to get some chai tea and a smoothie. We then ventured into Eagle River to hit the liquor store. All that took a surprisingly long time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>St. Germain - Day 7</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/st.-germain-day-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2010 19:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/st.-germain-day-7/</guid>
      <description>It was my morning to get up with Quin. He didn&amp;rsquo;t go to bed until 10:00 last night, so it was a bit of a surprise when he got up at 6:00 like normal. Luckily I just convinced him to lay down and within about 10 seconds he fell back to sleep until 8:00. By that time his diaper was a wreck! I was changing the mess that had accumulated saying something about &amp;ldquo;stinky poop&amp;rdquo; or something, and Quin said &amp;ldquo;I poop potty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>St. Germain - Summary</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/st.-germain-summary/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2010 19:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/st.-germain-summary/</guid>
      <description>All good things must come to an end. We pretty much just got up and left first thing on Sunday morning. It was looking like a very hot day, and the time we did spend outside packing the cars found us swatting at a lot of mosquitoes which had been very sparse the rest of the week.
Lots of interesting things happened during the week, but here is a quick summary of some of the more memorable things:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>St. Germain - Day 1</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/st.-germain-day-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2010 19:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/st.-germain-day-1/</guid>
      <description>The trip started out somewhat inauspiciously. I had neglected to pack anything - Jenny packed all the kids&amp;rsquo; stuff as well as mine, but there was still a pile of things that I needed to take care of the morning of our departure. My parents, Blaine, and Brett along with respective lady friends of each of theirs joined us the day prior to celebrate mom and dad&amp;rsquo;s 39th wedding anniversary by going to IrishFest in Milwaukee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>St. Germain - Day 2</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/st.-germain-day-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2010 19:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/st.-germain-day-2/</guid>
      <description>Day 2 was a lazy day. The weather was beautiful and sunny, so we did a lot of swimming and hanging out at the campsite. Along with your usual swimming, running, eating drinking, and sunshine activities, the following things stuck out:
 Quin introduced the world to his &amp;ldquo;booty-butt.&amp;rdquo; Somewhere along the line he picked up the term &amp;ldquo;booty&amp;rdquo; as a word for his bottom, but he never really dropped the &amp;ldquo;butt&amp;rdquo; part.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>St. Germain - Day 3</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/st.-germain-day-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2010 19:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/st.-germain-day-3/</guid>
      <description>Jenny&amp;rsquo;s parents stayed with us last night, so Ethan went to sleep at Jacob&amp;rsquo;s cabin with the Abholds. That didn&amp;rsquo;t last too long, unfortunately. At about 1:30 we heard somebody talking to us through our window - it was Micky telling us that Jacob had gotten sick and that Ethan was now feeling sick, so she was returning him to us for the night. So much for that idea&amp;hellip;
By morning, Ethan was feeling fine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick Hitters</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/quick-hitters/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2010 22:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/quick-hitters/</guid>
      <description>The other day we were at a party where we stayed pretty late. On the way home, Ethan engaged us in interesting conversation, as always. I can&amp;rsquo;t remember the exact context, but he asked something about somebody and if they were &amp;ldquo;a black.&amp;rdquo; We told him that it was not appropriate to refer to somebody as &amp;ldquo;a black,&amp;rdquo; it could be insulting. Instead he should use &amp;ldquo;black person,&amp;rdquo; or better yet, &amp;ldquo;African American.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baby Driver</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/baby-driver/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2010 23:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/baby-driver/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;They call him baby driver.&amp;rdquo; My dad used to sing that song to us when we were young. I don&amp;rsquo;t know if I ever heard the real version, but I remember it almost as well as him saying &amp;ldquo;wake up and piss, the world&amp;rsquo;s on fire.&amp;rdquo; Anyway, I digress&amp;hellip;
It&amp;rsquo;s been a busy spring here at the Grady house. So busy, in fact, that we really haven&amp;rsquo;t had time to do any yard work besides the required lawn cutting so far.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lots of new words, and the Amish</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/lots-of-new-words-and-the-amish/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2010 10:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/lots-of-new-words-and-the-amish/</guid>
      <description>Quin&amp;rsquo;s been quite the learner the last few months. I think since our vacation in April he&amp;rsquo;s been picking up an average of a couple new words a day. He has his favorites, though. My latest favorites are &amp;ldquo;nan&amp;rdquo; which means &amp;ldquo;dance,&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;nonut,&amp;rdquo; which means &amp;ldquo;donut.&amp;rdquo;
Quin has a definite love of dancing. He has figured out how to turn on various CD players and radios throughout the house, and once they are on, he will come and grab one of us to come and &amp;ldquo;nan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vacation 2010 - April 9 - 10, Driving</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/vacation-2010-april-9-10-driving/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2010 19:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/vacation-2010-april-9-10-driving/</guid>
      <description>We drove&amp;hellip; A lot&amp;hellip;
We left mom and dad&amp;rsquo;s place by 7:15. After a Starbucks run to keep the monster in the passenger&amp;rsquo;s seat happy, and a stop at the gas station for some gas and an energy drink (to keep the van and the monster in the driver&amp;rsquo;s seat happy), we got out of town by 7:45.
Not much to talk about here - we lunched at a Dairy Queen in Gallup New Mexico after passing through our first timezone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vacation 2010 - April 8, Apache Junction</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/vacation-2010-april-8-apache-junction/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2010 18:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/vacation-2010-april-8-apache-junction/</guid>
      <description>We started the day off again with a run through the Usery Recreational Area. This time we knew where we were going, but that didn&amp;rsquo;t make it any less exciting. We saw three hares (I believe that&amp;rsquo;s what they were) and a roadrunner. Jenny was attacked by a cactus which waylaid us for a few minutes, but overall it was a nice run.
After spending several days with Quin, he seems to be getting smarter all the time!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vacation 2010 - April 7, Apache Junction</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/vacation-2010-april-7-apache-junction/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2010 18:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/vacation-2010-april-7-apache-junction/</guid>
      <description>It was nice to be somewhere that we didn&amp;rsquo;t have to be running all the time! To celebrate, Jenny and I went for a run!!! I had made it out in Denver for a quick 3 miler, but Jenny wanted to get out, so we went to the map and found somewhere that &amp;ldquo;looked like it had trails.&amp;rdquo; After driving for about 10 minutes, we found a trailhead at the Usery Recreation Area and parked.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Talks with Ethan.</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/talks-with-ethan./</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2010 13:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/talks-with-ethan./</guid>
      <description>It sometimes frightens me to think what Ethan tells people about us. He and I are sitting in the car waiting for Jenny and mom to come out of a store and he&amp;rsquo;s telling me about how he and a girl from school have made up new words to a song that I had made up when I was a kid. Or was a parody to the tune of &amp;ldquo;this is it&amp;rdquo; by Huey Louis and the News called &amp;ldquo;Smell my Pits.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vacation 2010 - April 6, Sedona and Apache Junction</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/vacation-2010-april-6-sedona-and-apache-junction/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2010 00:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/vacation-2010-april-6-sedona-and-apache-junction/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m writing this three days later, so there is a serious possibility that these memories will be stale&amp;hellip; Oh well, maybe I&amp;rsquo;ll get some comments from my wife and parents to help fill in the blanks.
Quinny got up early this morning! 5:00 AM. A 5PM afternoon nap of 90 minutes didn&amp;rsquo;t help us out here at all. We tried to push him over to Grandpa and Grandma&amp;rsquo;s room right away, but he didn&amp;rsquo;t want to have much to do with that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vacation 2010 - April 5, The Grand Canyon</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/vacation-2010-april-5-the-grand-canyon/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2010 23:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/vacation-2010-april-5-the-grand-canyon/</guid>
      <description>Busy day, this one. We woke up after &amp;ldquo;sleeping in&amp;rdquo; until 6:00 at the Hampton Inn in Flagstaff, AZ. Very nice hotel, reasonably priced, with a nice rooms, decent continental breakfast, and most importantly, a POOL!!! After Quin woke up, he and I went downstairs for some fruit, cereal, and juice. Jenny and Ethan joined us shortly afterwards. After we were sufficiently fed, we got into our swimming suits and took in some much deserved swimming.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vacation 2010 - April 4, Driving...</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/vacation-2010-april-4-driving.../</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2010 00:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/vacation-2010-april-4-driving.../</guid>
      <description>OK, I&amp;rsquo;m a little out of order. Bear with me. April 4, Easter Sunday, was a day of driving. I was actually able to get out of bed and get out for a 3.4 mile run in the crisp Denver morning (41 degrees but sunny). Running in Denver is nice and not so nice. Nice because they have so many running trails and there are so many cute girls that are generally out exercising as well (even when it is cold).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grand canyon</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/grand-canyon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2010 12:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/grand-canyon/</guid>
      <description>Holy crap it&amp;rsquo;s windy!!! Short post for now. Jenny and Ethan are out looking at the little Colorado river gorge about 15 miles east of the south rim park of the grand canyon. It&amp;rsquo;s not too cold out but I bet the wind is gusting up to 50 mph. It&amp;rsquo;s so bad that it tipped over 2 portapotties.
Quinny is napping. We left him in the car to start with but then felt guilty so now I&amp;rsquo;m hanging out with him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vacation 2010 - April 3, Denver</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/vacation-2010-april-3-denver/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2010 23:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/vacation-2010-april-3-denver/</guid>
      <description>OK, back to the standard keyboard. Too much to write to try to do it on my little iPhone.
The day started out pretty early this morning. Quin woke up around 5:00 local time, but that was OK with me since I had fallen asleep last night at 8:30 local. Of course, in a single bedroom apartment, once anybody is up, everybody is pretty much up. By 6:30, everybody was done pretending to be asleep anymore and we got up and ready for the day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vacaton 2010 Leg 1</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/vacaton-2010-leg-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Apr 2010 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/vacaton-2010-leg-1/</guid>
      <description>Vacation 2010 Leg 1 So I&amp;rsquo;m trying a couple of new things this time around. I&amp;rsquo;ve recently identified that I require an ipad in order to survive. In order to prepare myself I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to post my vacation blog entirely from my iPhone. We&amp;rsquo;ll see how long this lasts. I think I may be too old to learn to thumb type and ignore basic punctuation and spelling rules, but I suppose time will tell.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>March Musings</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/march-musings/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2010 15:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/march-musings/</guid>
      <description>On this eve of &amp;ldquo;the closest thing the Irish have to Christmas,&amp;rdquo; I&amp;rsquo;m sitting on my couch musing about my hopelessly silly kids. Nature dictates that the oldest is silly like his dad, but nurture appears to have a strong influence on the youngest. Too bad - we thought he had a chance!!!
We were out and about gathering materials for our latest home improvement project, built-in cabinets and a desk in our office (the wood floor was finished up two weeks ago).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is that a Baby Ruth?</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/is-that-a-baby-ruth/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2010 21:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/is-that-a-baby-ruth/</guid>
      <description>I was traveling to Atlanta this past week, so Jenny and the boys were by themselves for three days! It sounded like things were going pretty well, for the most part, until I was in the Hartfield Jackson Airport in Atlanta awaiting my boarding call to return home to Milwaukee. That was when I received a call from Ethan. &amp;ldquo;Dad,&amp;rdquo; he said, &amp;ldquo;what do you do when Quin poops in the bathtub?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No ni-ni...</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/no-ni-ni.../</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Feb 2010 20:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/no-ni-ni.../</guid>
      <description>Quin is starting to talk quite a bit. I&amp;rsquo;m happy to say that he is finally speaking in sentences! Of course, most, if not all of his sentences are just telling us no to different things that we want him to do. &amp;ldquo;No ni-ni.&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;No eat.&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;No Bath!&amp;rdquo; I guess you have to start somewhere!
The other day, Ethan, Quin, and I were out to eat and had some time to burn before we went to swimming lessons, so we went to Best Buy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Year</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/new-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2010 20:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/new-year/</guid>
      <description>Happy New Year! In the name of New Year&amp;rsquo;s Resolutions, I&amp;rsquo;ve resolved to blog on a more regular basis this year! I&amp;rsquo;ve found that blogging is nice on several levels. It allows people who care to follow along with what is going on with our lives (or ignore it, which is nice as well). This is important right now since my parents have moved to Arizona for the remainder of this winter and will be grandchild starved for 3 months!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kickles and Hillbillies</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/kickles-and-hillbillies/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2009 23:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/kickles-and-hillbillies/</guid>
      <description>Of course my wife reminded me of some things I forgot&amp;hellip; If only she knew how to blog!
The other day Ethan and I were driving to Soccer when we passed a section of road we frequently pass. On one side of the road is a pretty steep, tree-covered hill with a couple of houses on top. Ethan asked me, matter of factly, if the people living there were hillbillies. To be honest, I was laughing to myself, but calmly collected myself before explaining that they were not hillbillies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Freedom...</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/freedom.../</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2009 21:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/freedom.../</guid>
      <description>Quin climbed out of his crib the other day. We were working around the house and he was acting like he was tired. He generally doesn&amp;rsquo;t like to take naps during the day, but we like him to take naps. So I put him in his crib and began to let him &amp;ldquo;cry it out.&amp;rdquo; I went outside to take care of something, and a couple of minutes later came back inside to find Quin standing downstairs, smiling at me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vacation 2009 - Evil River Part II</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/vacation-2009-evil-river-part-ii/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2009 16:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/vacation-2009-evil-river-part-ii/</guid>
      <description>Here it is, the big vacation update! Of course, it&amp;rsquo;s been a month since we went, so the memories have already started to fade, but I&amp;rsquo;ve uploaded some pictures to our photo gallery and the site&amp;rsquo;s slideshow is now showing them. Hopefully this gives a better idea of how the vacation went. To see all of the pictures in the album, either click on the slideshow, or try this link here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quin Quickie</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/quin-quickie/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2009 13:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/quin-quickie/</guid>
      <description>I couldn&amp;rsquo;t resist blogging this before my &amp;ldquo;big vacation update&amp;rdquo; later this week&amp;hellip;
Quin has been talking A LOT MORE lately. I sat down to try to figure out the words he knew now and lost track. He&amp;rsquo;s become much more interesting in the last month or so. Anyway, a game that I always play with him is to push his nose and say &amp;ldquo;beep beep.&amp;rdquo; Ethan might do it to him, too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kissing Cousins</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/kissing-cousins/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2009 20:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/kissing-cousins/</guid>
      <description>Kissing Cousins These pictures are from awhile ago, but I thought they were cute enough to post anyway!!! This is a picture of Quinton kissing his cousin. Man, he&amp;rsquo;s really going for it! OK, they are second cousins once removed, or third cousins or something (you&amp;rsquo;d have to ask Blaine for the exact designation), so that&amp;rsquo;s probably OK in most You can tell they are from awhile ago as they were for Jodi&amp;rsquo;s baby shower - and they&amp;rsquo;ve already had the baby!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cub Scout Camp</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/cub-scout-camp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jul 2009 21:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/cub-scout-camp/</guid>
      <description>Cub Scout Camp Last week, Ethan and I attended Cub Scout day camp for our second year. This year we went on the 3 day camp. Camp started at 9:00 AM and went until 4:00 PM. Besides the mosquitoes, it was a bona-fide blast for both of us. Ethan was able to do all sorts of different activities, including archery (which is is very good at), mini-golf (which he is not so good at), highlander games, knight&amp;rsquo;s quest, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pets...</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/pets.../</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2009 21:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/pets.../</guid>
      <description>Quinton and Ethan&amp;rsquo;s, well, all of our pet Barley passed away on Monday. Two weeks ago she suffered what appears to be a slipped disc in her back. Her back legs quickly became disabled, and over the course of the next two weeks she lost control of her bladder and bowels. She was almost nine years old.
The kids really loved her. Quin probably moreso than Ethan, though she&amp;rsquo;s been a fixture in our house since Ethan has been around.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sesame Street</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/sesame-street/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2009 20:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/sesame-street/</guid>
      <description>Lots has happened since the last time you were updated on my two favorite kids. Ethan and Quin&amp;rsquo;s only remaining great-grandmother passed away, Ethan received his first communion, and Quin has had his first ride on the lawnmower&amp;hellip; Let&amp;rsquo;s begin.
To set the table, I used to watch video blogs on the mac while I was feeding Quin last year. It was nice because I was able to control them with the remote control while I used my other hand to hold the bottle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 S&#39;s for Ethan</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/3-ss-for-ethan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2009 21:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/3-ss-for-ethan/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been awhile since I&amp;rsquo;ve updated this site on my favorite 7-year old. Ethan&amp;rsquo;s been doing quite a bit lately, now in the home stretch of his 2nd grade year, about to receive his first communion. But why the title &amp;ldquo;3 S&amp;rsquo;s for Ethan?&amp;rdquo; Really it all stems from a sad little game I play with my brain when I&amp;rsquo;m trying to remember something. I figure my brain can only remember 3 things at a time, and then only if I name them interestingly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smartest Kid Alive???</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/smartest-kid-alive/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2009 18:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/smartest-kid-alive/</guid>
      <description>I can&amp;rsquo;t be sure, and I&amp;rsquo;m probably not a good judge since he is my child, but I&amp;rsquo;m pretty certain that Quinton is the smartest 13 month old to have graced the planet. My first clue happened a couple of days ago. We sat him in his high-chair to feed him and mixed all of the food onto his tray. His tray does have segmented areas, but we generally just put stuff in the large middle one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Birthdays and Readers</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/birthdays-and-readers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2009 19:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/birthdays-and-readers/</guid>
      <description>Quin and Ethan have been busy folks as of late. Quin went and turned one and we barely even acknowledged it! Well, digitally anyway. In true Grady boy fashion, Quin celebrated his birthday not once, not twice, but three separate times so that he could cover all his bases. Our favorite celebration was the one we had at our house with just our little family, though. It was the first time Quin really got to dig into some chocolate cake, and boy do I think he was impressed!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quinton&#39;s top 10 Lists</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/quintons-top-10-lists/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2009 09:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/quintons-top-10-lists/</guid>
      <description>Top 10 things Quin does that drive mom and dad crazy!!!  Plays with the computer mouse while they&amp;rsquo;re using the computer. Drinks from the dog&amp;rsquo;s dish Plays in the dog&amp;rsquo;s dish Plays in the toilet Takes all the toilet paper and paper towels off of their dowels onto the floor Identifies anything that is not currently on the floor and within his reach and frees it to the floor Eats dog food Climbs the stairs when nobody is watching Touches the TV Licks things (like the gym wall and miscellaneous bolts sticking out from it)  Top 10 things Quin does that make us wish we had a dozen more  Big wet kisses 100 Megawatt smiles Sleeping 11 hours at a crack Constant laughter Cuddles (for anybody, not just mom and dad) Playing the piano Cat-like curiosity Playing peek-a-boo Saying &amp;ldquo;da da&amp;rdquo; (this might be on Jenny&amp;rsquo;s other list) All the rest of the things on the first list  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fully Ambulatory</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/fully-ambulatory/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2009 09:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/fully-ambulatory/</guid>
      <description>As of last night, Quinton has become one of the walkers of the world. He took his first tenuous steps from Jenny to myself last night before bed. Everybody was very excited. Well, Ethan was a little disappointed since he was in the shower when it happened, but was excited nonetheless. Looks like it&amp;rsquo;s time to get the house to the next level of baby-proofness.
Another score for the &amp;ldquo;nurture&amp;rdquo; portion of the nature vs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2009 Update</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/2009-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2009 21:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/2009-update/</guid>
      <description>Happy New Year!
I hope you all had a wonderful 2008 and are ready to endure what is sure to be an interesting and trying 2009. I have mailed a &amp;ldquo;2008 Year in Review&amp;rdquo; to some of you, those that I knew could take it (it&amp;rsquo;s a 30 minute video of our family). If you would like one of your own and did not receive one, please e-mail me and I will be happy to send one out to you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>General Update</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/general-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2008 12:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/general-update/</guid>
      <description>Ethan We had Ethan&amp;rsquo;s parent-teacher conference yesterday. He is doing very well in School, mostly thanks to Jenny. She works with him constantly on his school work as well as reading, basic math and the like. It&amp;rsquo;s a lot of work, but it is apparently paying off. While in the conference we were able to read some of Ethan&amp;rsquo;s stories and reports that he&amp;rsquo;s been writing up. I plan on posting a couple of them to this blog in the near future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Big Strides</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/big-strides/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2008 21:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/big-strides/</guid>
      <description>Quin has learned the fine art of movement. He still doesn&amp;rsquo;t really &amp;ldquo;crawl,&amp;rdquo; necessarily, but he lilts along like an army man. Actually he looks a little like Igor would look if he crawled. Since he&amp;rsquo;s been in motion, he&amp;rsquo;s bee quite happy and quite a handful. I don&amp;rsquo;t remember if Ethan got into as much when he was younger, but Quin really likes to get into everything!
Unfortunately, Quin&amp;rsquo;s also been sick for the last week or so.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s Official!!!</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/its-official/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2008 16:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/its-official/</guid>
      <description>That&amp;rsquo;s right, Quin&amp;rsquo;s a Grady! Poor kid&amp;hellip; On October 2, 2008, we had our final court date at the Waukesha County Juvenile Court to finalize, legally, our adoption. Largely it was uneventful, but it still managed to choke me up a little bit. While there we met another family that was finalizing, except this was their THIRD adoption! Crazy folks!
Quin&amp;rsquo;s getting bigger and moving around more and more all the time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Catching up.</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/catching-up./</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2008 19:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/catching-up./</guid>
      <description>I know that I&amp;rsquo;m getting behind because my wife has told me that I&amp;rsquo;m in trouble because of how infrequently I blog. I didn&amp;rsquo;t even know she knew I had a blog&amp;hellip; Oh well&amp;hellip;
Quin&amp;rsquo;s doing great! He&amp;rsquo;s 7 months old now and is quite mobile. No, he still doesn&amp;rsquo;t (really) crawl, but has developed a rolling technique that enables him to get pretty much wherever he wants to go. He&amp;rsquo;s also started to try out the &amp;ldquo;all fours&amp;rdquo; thing by getting up on his knees and lunching towards things that are slightly out of his reach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guess who has a tooth?</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/guess-who-has-a-tooth/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2008 20:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/guess-who-has-a-tooth/</guid>
      <description>No, it&amp;rsquo;s not Ethan, and it&amp;rsquo;s not Barley either. That&amp;rsquo;s right, Quin&amp;rsquo;s first tooth has finally busted its way through his gums. We were wondering why he&amp;rsquo;s been so crabby lately, and the old &amp;ldquo;well, he&amp;rsquo;s probably teething&amp;rdquo; excuse was wearing a little thin some 4 months later. But lo and behold, it really was true this time!
Here you can see him having a deep conversation with an old Elmo doll.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s the best state fair...</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/its-the-best-state-fair.../</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2008 22:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/its-the-best-state-fair.../</guid>
      <description>Last week, Quin got to partake in his first State Fair. He &amp;ldquo;fared&amp;rdquo; pretty well, though I&amp;rsquo;m not sure it was entirely his cup of tea just yet. Ethan had a blast, at least for the most part. We started out by getting a wrist band and going on the rides. This is really the first year where Ethan was ready to go on the &amp;ldquo;big kids&amp;rdquo; rides.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where the hell did they put them?</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/where-the-hell-did-they-put-them/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2008 21:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/where-the-hell-did-they-put-them/</guid>
      <description>Time is flying by. Quin is starting to get more and more independent, which is nice as he was being a bit clingy for awhile there. He is very good at rolling and can sometimes even roll from his back to his stomach. His latest trick is to stay in a seated position if we put him in one to start with. He&amp;rsquo;s also reaching for toys and other things that are out of reach, which I&amp;rsquo;m told is a developmental milestone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ethan the Triathlete</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/ethan-the-triathlete/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2008 20:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/ethan-the-triathlete/</guid>
      <description>This past weekend was the Pewaukee Sprint Triathlon. I ran in this event last year along with a team that we had assembled known as &amp;ldquo;Big Sky Multisport.&amp;rdquo; We had our own jerseys and a whole bunch of people. Ethan was so impressed when he came to watch! He wanted to be &amp;ldquo;on my team.&amp;rdquo;
This year we did it again, and they have a kid&amp;rsquo;s event.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Milestones</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/milestones/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2008 20:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/milestones/</guid>
      <description>After having been read the riot act by my mother, I have decided to finally make a most delayed post. In the past two weeks, Quin has been passing milestones by the handful and I have neglected to document them here, so here goes.
Two weeks ago Friday, Quin passed not one, not two, but three milestones in a 12 hour period. First, he ate rice cereal for the first time, and gobbled it up completely.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dexterity</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/dexterity/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2008 20:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/dexterity/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m just sitting here doing some scout stuff and Quin is sitting right next to me in one of his bouncy chairs. What&amp;rsquo;s different than normal is that he is grabbing everything within reach. He has access to a bunch of toys within reach and he is studying each one of them intently. This is a first for him and quite exciting for us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A rough 36 hours...</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/a-rough-36-hours.../</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2008 21:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/a-rough-36-hours.../</guid>
      <description>It all started out innocently enough. We were going to church on Sunday morning, after which Ethan was supposed to attend a birthday party for a girl in his class. While in the &amp;ldquo;gathering place&amp;rdquo; after mass, Ethan was horsing around with a buddy of his when his head got bumped and one of his loose teeth started bleeding. On came the waterworks! He insisted that he was in no shape to go to the party.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The &#39;Forest&#39; is strong with this one...</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-forrest-is-strong-with-this-one.../</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2008 20:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-forrest-is-strong-with-this-one.../</guid>
      <description>Birthday Boy May 17th was Ethan&amp;rsquo;s 7th birthday. To celebrate, we invited the boys from his class to join us at the YMCA for some cake, games, and swimming. Unfortunately, Ethan has only 5 boys in his class, including himself. Even more unfortunate, one of the boys didn&amp;rsquo;t show up, so there were only 4 boys there. Actually, that ended up being lucky for us as boys are crazy! The spent the bulk of their time wrestling and smashing into one another.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Superheroes</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/superheroes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2008 20:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/superheroes/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s not secret, Ethan is a HUGE superhero fan. He loves all things Spider-man, Superman (to a lesser degree), Batman, Fast Guy, who he now knows as The Flash, you name it. He even thinks Ghost Rider and Blade are cool. On Friday, he had a book fair at school where he become the proud new owner of a Spider-man encyclopedia. It is a book that has many of the characters from the Spider-man universe, gives a brief dossier on the character, and shows a picture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One Rough Vacation</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/one-rough-vacation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2008 19:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/one-rough-vacation/</guid>
      <description>This past weekend marked one of the most trying vacations we&amp;rsquo;ve had as a family. In fact, it was one of the most trying 24 hours we&amp;rsquo;ve ever had as a complete family. Let me explain&amp;hellip;
We rented a condo in Wisconsin Dells this past weekend with Aimee and Steve (Jenny&amp;rsquo;s sister) and Tim and Laura, and their respective children, all of whom range in age from 6 months to 2 years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Big Update</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/big-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2008 08:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/big-update/</guid>
      <description>Quin is 9 weeks old now!!! We&amp;rsquo;ve had a good couple of weeks with him so I thought I&amp;rsquo;d share with the lot of you.
First off, he&amp;rsquo;s now eating about 5 ounces at a time every 4 hours. Unfortunately, he&amp;rsquo;s still doing that at night as well. Although, some nights he&amp;rsquo;s been known to go 6 or more hours between feedings, and when he does wake up to eat, he&amp;rsquo;s very good about going back to sleep promptly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Trip Home</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-trip-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2008 21:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-trip-home/</guid>
      <description>The Trip Home At 6:30 we got up &amp;ldquo;officially.&amp;rdquo; Jenny had packed the night before so we could maximize our sleep, but Quin had different ideas. By 7:30 we were showered and ready to go. A bellman picked us up at our room and took us to the &amp;ldquo;Common House&amp;rdquo; for checkout. Here we were actually able to check our bags onto the airplane and get our boarding passes. This Magical Express thing was really nice!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disney Day 5</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/disney-day-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2008 21:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/disney-day-5/</guid>
      <description>Morning Swim Finally, our last day at the parks. It&amp;rsquo;s been a pretty eventful week. A bit tiring, but definitely memorable. Today we had reservations at EPCOT early, 4:45, so we planned on spending the day there again. There was a lot at this park that we haven&amp;rsquo;t yet done. Also, mom and dad really like the world showcase, so there seemed plenty to do for the entire family.
We woke up late again today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disney Day 4</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/disney-day-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2008 22:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/disney-day-4/</guid>
      <description>Late Start Quin was up during the night and we were getting tired, so we slept in a little bit this morning. Jenny and I got out for a run around the 1.4 mile running path that goes around the resort (we went twice around), we gave the kids baths, then we grabbed a leisurely breakfast at the Shutters food court at our resort. It was a good jumping off point for the rest of the day, which we planned on spending at Animal Kingdom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disney Day 3</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/disney-day-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2008 21:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/disney-day-3/</guid>
      <description>Magic Kingdom Part II Today we decided to try something a little different. Rather than sleeping in and dealing with the crowds of people, we thought we&amp;rsquo;d leave a little early in hopes of getting on some more rides in less confined areas. So we took off early for the bus (OK, I think we still got on the bus around 9:00) and headed for the Magic Kingdom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disney Day 2</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/disney-day-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2008 22:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/disney-day-2/</guid>
      <description>Good Night&amp;rsquo;s Sleep Our first night in the hotel was blissfully uneventful. My biggest worry coming to this resort with an infant was that he would be up and unconsolable in the night and he would wake people up. Turns out I had nothing to worry about all along. In fact, I would say that Quin probably slept better at the hotel than he does at home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disney Day 1</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/disney-day-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2008 22:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/disney-day-1/</guid>
      <description>A Note on These Posts I&amp;rsquo;m doing these posts a little out of sequence. I&amp;rsquo;ve written notes as things happened, but I&amp;rsquo;m going back and filling in the blanks as I get time to write them. At times it may seem a bit disjointed, so please forgive me. The dates will be posted as though they occurred on the days in which the events actually occurred, however they will not be written or posted on those actual days.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This parenting thing is easy...</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/this-parenting-thing-is-easy.../</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2008 13:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/this-parenting-thing-is-easy.../</guid>
      <description>Jenny has to work today and tomorrow, so I&amp;rsquo;m working from home. So I got my laptop out, put on some slippers, and got ready for some good ole fashioned parenting. I tell you, it really isn&amp;rsquo;t all that hard&amp;hellip;
    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pre Adoptive and a chink in the armor</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/pre-adoptive-and-a-chink-in-the-armor/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2008 07:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/pre-adoptive-and-a-chink-in-the-armor/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s official as of Monday afternoon, we are a pre-adoptive family. On Monday, both birth parents were given one last opportunity to choose to parent Quin. The birth mother showed up and gave up her right to do so, and the birth father did not answer the attempts to contact him. That&amp;rsquo;s an important step for us! That means that there shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be any bad Lifetime movies written about our situation any time soon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Loose teeth and doctor&#39;s visits</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/loose-teeth-and-doctors-visits/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2008 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/loose-teeth-and-doctors-visits/</guid>
      <description>Today, Quin is 16 days old. Almost like his golden birthday in days! Jenny had to go in to work today, so Quin and I worked from home, and let me tell you, he does better work than some of the interns I&amp;rsquo;ve had! I fed him once at 7:00, then he didn&amp;rsquo;t want to eat again until around noon (my mistake as I got lost in e-mails for awhile).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skiing on Mount Olympia</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/skiing-on-mount-olympia/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2008 18:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/skiing-on-mount-olympia/</guid>
      <description>Ethan and I had a wonderful boy&amp;rsquo;s day today. Jenny took Quin up to meet his aunts in the Dells while celebrating their mom&amp;rsquo;s birthday. Since it was a rare beautiful day, Ethan and I decided to go skiing at our local &amp;ldquo;mountain.&amp;rdquo; Really it&amp;rsquo;s a recovered garbage dump, I think&amp;hellip; It&amp;rsquo;s definitely not a mountain, but it&amp;rsquo;s close. The last time Ethan skied was last year in the U.P. and he did really well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bringing Quin home</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/bringing-quin-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2008 18:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/bringing-quin-home/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday we got the call that Quin was going to be discharged from the hospital. It was going to be later in the day, so we took Ethan out of school around 12:30 and headed over to the hospital. When we walked into the nursery, we were surprised to find two doctors circumcising Quin. We thought that had happened already in the morning! Well, it was somewhat interesting to watch, but Ethan was not so impressed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quinton Edward</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/quinton-edward/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2008 15:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/quinton-edward/</guid>
      <description>On February 16, 2008 at 10:47 AM, Quinton Edward Grady was born. OK, that will be his name assuming the whole adoption goes through, but since the birth mother has not named him, we will refer to him from here on out as &amp;ldquo;Quin.&amp;rdquo; Quin was born via a Caesarian section delivery in a Madison area hospital. He weighed 6 pounds 11 ounces and was 19 3/4 inches long.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Brother Coming</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/new-brother-coming/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2008 15:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/new-brother-coming/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m putting a stake in the ground to start doing these again. Perhaps once a week is a good goal, but I need to get it done&amp;hellip;
So much has happened since the last time I &amp;lsquo;blogged, it would be foolish to try to recap. Instead, I&amp;rsquo;ll talk about the most significant event of recent memory, our adoption. Jenny and I have been trying to have another child for several years now, but with no success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Tooth...</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/first-tooth.../</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2006 22:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/first-tooth.../</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been fun the last few weeks. Ethan still is getting green slips at school, but he still tells us about it each time. He also is learning his letters very well and is very good with numbers. Jenny and I are both very proud of his schoolwork.
Tonight was the annual Harvest Dance at school. The gym had a bouncy castle and a bunch of games. We spent nearly 2 hours there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Long time...</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/long-time.../</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2006 22:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/long-time.../</guid>
      <description>OK, it&amp;rsquo;s been quite awhile again, but I thought the time was right to update some of Ethan&amp;rsquo;s stats on this site. Really what forced me to do it was some of the things Ethan said to me tonight.
First thing&amp;rsquo;s first, Ethan has an adult tooth coming in behind his existing baby teeth on the bottom of his mouth. Jenny and I don&amp;rsquo;t really know anything about this, so we took him to the dentist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Northern Exposure</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/northern-exposure/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2006 22:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/northern-exposure/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s a lovely evening in the North Woods. This week is our family vacation, and this year we have chosen to spend it in St. Germain, WI at a cabin on the lake. It&amp;rsquo;s absolutely lovely up here!!! We&amp;rsquo;re not more than 30 feet from the lake.
We weren&amp;rsquo;t here for 10 minutes before Ethan had his swimming suit on and was in the water!!! It&amp;rsquo;s really amazing to me how he&amp;rsquo;s taken to the water in the last few months.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jack Black</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/jack-black/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2006 22:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/jack-black/</guid>
      <description>I just found out that my son is cool. He knows who Jack Black is and wants to see Nacho Libre, and in my book, that makes you cool.
Yesterday we were outside talking about the new DVD he took out from the library. He said that one part doesn&amp;rsquo;t play very well, and told me that the reason was &amp;ldquo;probably because mommy put a fingerprint on the shiny side.&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The things kids will say...</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-things-kids-will-say.../</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2006 16:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-things-kids-will-say.../</guid>
      <description>First joke&amp;hellip; Ethan told me his first real joke the other day. Here it is&amp;hellip; &amp;ldquo;Why is the corn stalk mad? -Because people are always pulling on their ears!&amp;rdquo; Of course he followed this up with &amp;ldquo;Why is the bear mad? -Because people are always pulling their hair!&amp;rdquo; So maybe he doesn&amp;rsquo;t have that great of a sense of humor&amp;hellip;
Clowns&amp;hellip; It was Jenny&amp;rsquo;s birthday a last week. Ethan and I were outside waiting for her to go roller blading.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 Years Old</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/5-years-old/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2006 08:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/5-years-old/</guid>
      <description>My baby is 5 years old! This year&amp;rsquo;s birthday was particularly fun. Not only was he really looking forward to his birthday, but he was looking forward to his parties as well. So far Ethan&amp;rsquo;s had 2 parties. The first was on his birthday, last Wednesday. We had the Abholds, the Witte&amp;rsquo;s, and the Kelchen&amp;rsquo;s over for supper and cake. Ethan loved all of his presents he got there. Then, last weekend, we went up to Minneapolis to have a joint birthday party for Ethan and Bryce with the Grady&amp;rsquo;s.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wisconsin Dells</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/wisconsin-dells/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2006 20:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/wisconsin-dells/</guid>
      <description>We took our annual trip to Wisconsin Dells last weekend. We met the Hupperts, friends of ours from Seattle who now live in Baldwin, WI, at the Wilderness Resort for the evening. Ted and Sue have two little boys, Teddy, who is 3.5, and Charlie, who is 1.5. Ethan had a very good time with Teddy this time. He gets along with kids younger than him very well. Ethan is getting braver and braver as he gets older, but he is still a bit scared of certain things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ice Age - The Meltdown</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/ice-age-the-meltdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2006 21:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/ice-age-the-meltdown/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s another in my series of reviews of Children&amp;rsquo;s movies. This time, Ethan and I went to see Ice Age, The Meltdown. Ice Age 2 is the second movie by Blue Sky Productions (I think) under the Fox production company. Like the first Ice Age, it is a computer animated movie about three prehistoric animals who became a &amp;ldquo;herd&amp;rdquo; of their own.
This time around, the world is warming up and all of the animals live in a large bowl formed by an 80 foot high ice dam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Four Year-Old Wisdom</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/four-year-old-wisdom/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2006 21:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/four-year-old-wisdom/</guid>
      <description>Nothing very long today. I just have some nuggets from the past couple of days that are worth sharing.
Yesterday we were driving back from KFC and Ethan could smell some of the food. He mentioned something about how good the food smelled and then said, &amp;ldquo;Mmm, the sweet smell of french fries!&amp;rdquo;
Then, today we were outside changing the oil in the lawn mower, and Ethan turned to me and said, &amp;ldquo;Dad, if you eat fire, then you will fart fire, and your tongue will be on fire, too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Parent-Teacher Conferences</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/parent-teacher-conferences/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2006 09:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/parent-teacher-conferences/</guid>
      <description>We had our second parent-teacher conference with Ethan&amp;rsquo;s teacher, Mrs. Matyas yesterday. This conference went much better than the first conference. Apparently Ethan is progressing very well and doing a wonderful job in school. He still needs work on his fine motor skills, but he at least knows enough to raise his hand before he talks. I guess he still loves to tell stories. In fact, he tells everybody that he is going to have a baby sister.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ethan Update</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/ethan-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2006 18:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/ethan-update/</guid>
      <description>Nothing special today. I just wanted to jot some random thoughts down about Ethan so that they wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be lost.
 The other day Ethan asked me, &amp;ldquo;Dad, is Jesus stronger than Superman?&amp;rdquo; Ethan has quite an affinity for his &amp;ldquo;booty.&amp;rdquo; The other day, he pulled his pants down in the back, exposing his plumber crack, and asked me, straight-faced, &amp;ldquo;has anybody seen my underwear?&amp;rdquo; He is very interested in babies and how they are made.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cowboy Ethan</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/cowboy-ethan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2006 18:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/cowboy-ethan/</guid>
      <description>    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Funny Sayings</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/funny-sayings/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2006 20:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/funny-sayings/</guid>
      <description>I can&amp;rsquo;t remember the exact context, but the other day Ethan was saying some pretty funny stuff. He was talking about liking something or not liking something (what, I can&amp;rsquo;t remember), and a couple of minutes into it he said, &amp;ldquo;I changed my mind, I like it. I must be out of my mind.&amp;rdquo;
Today we took Ethan to the Curious George movie. Jenny and I both liked it, although it doesn&amp;rsquo;t have as much to enjoy for adults as do some other recent &amp;ldquo;children&amp;rsquo;s&amp;rdquo; movies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pajama Day</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/pajama-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2006 07:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/pajama-day/</guid>
      <description>Ethan is so excited. Today he gets to wear his pajamas to school. When I told him, the first thing he asked me was, &amp;ldquo;is everybody going to wear them?&amp;rdquo; After I told him yes, it was full steam ahead. He picked out the pajamas he wanted, made us wash them, and picked out some slippers. This morning he told me that he didn&amp;rsquo;t want any milk on his cereal so he didn&amp;rsquo;t get his jammies wet&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>March of the Penguins and other movie reviews</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/march-of-the-penguins-and-other-movie-reviews/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2006 08:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/march-of-the-penguins-and-other-movie-reviews/</guid>
      <description>One of Ethan&amp;rsquo;s favorite things to do is to watch movies. He is probably one of the youngest movie &amp;ldquo;quoters&amp;rdquo; that I know. In the last few days, Ethan and I have seen a couple of new movies that are notworthy in that they have left an impression on Ethan.
The first movie we saw was during the Bears-Panthers game on Sunday, Hoodwinked. Hoodwinked is the story of Little Red Riding Hood told from perspective of those involved, Red, Grandma, the Big Bad Wolf, and the axe wielding Schnitzel truck driver.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Little snot...</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/little-snot.../</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2006 12:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/little-snot.../</guid>
      <description>Wow, has my son turned into a little snot all of a sudden. If this is what it&amp;rsquo;s like to have teen-agers, I want no part of it. I know, I know, those are much worse! I&amp;rsquo;m not sure what happened, but since I picked him up from school today he has been quite a little snot. He started by informing me that I&amp;rsquo;m not the boss, and that he didn&amp;rsquo;t like me anymore.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another Christmas Program</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/another-christmas-program/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2005 20:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/another-christmas-program/</guid>
      <description>Ethan had a second Christmas program this year, this time at his old school (daycare). At the daycare Christmas program, you can only watch your child sing because there just isn&amp;rsquo;t room for everybody to be in the LMR (large muscle room) at the same time.
Anyway, after Ethan&amp;rsquo;s portion of the program was done, we joined him, his classmates, and their parents in his room, the 4 1/2 year old room for cookies and punch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Concert</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/christmas-concert/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2005 08:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/christmas-concert/</guid>
      <description>Last night was Ethan&amp;rsquo;s unofficial first Christmas concert as a &amp;ldquo;grade schooler.&amp;rdquo; He&amp;rsquo;s had a concert every year in daycare, but this is the first time he had an &amp;ldquo;audience.&amp;rdquo; Both sets of grandparents braved the 200 mile trek to see their grandson dance and &amp;ldquo;sing&amp;rdquo; Christmas songs with his classmates. It was a nice concert, held in the church with all the other kids in St. Bruno&amp;rsquo;s school, which includes kids through 8th grade.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Treasured Christmas Memory</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/a-treasured-christmas-memory/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2005 17:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/a-treasured-christmas-memory/</guid>
      <description>Life should be filled with more days like today. It was one of the most relaxing, yet fulfulling days I&amp;rsquo;ve had in quite awhile, and will not be soon forgotten.
It started out last night, really. The whole family went to Kohls to do a little &amp;ldquo;midnight&amp;rdquo; Christmas shopping. OK, it was actually about 7:30 when we went, but for all intents and purposes (from Ethan&amp;rsquo;s standpoint) it was close to midnight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Birthday Party</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/first-birthday-party/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2005 08:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/first-birthday-party/</guid>
      <description>Ethan had his first non-family birthday party on Sunday. It was for Robert Dent, a boy from his daycare, who was turning five. They had the party at M&amp;amp;M Gymnastics in New Berlin and it involved doing some tumbling and eating pizza. Looked like fun. Mostly, though, it reminded me how old Ethan was getting.
Ethan also got to spend the day with our friends Micky and Tim on Saturday as Jenny and I had to go to a wedding.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Ghost with One Black Eye</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-ghost-with-one-black-eye/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2005 16:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/the-ghost-with-one-black-eye/</guid>
      <description>Ethan told me a story today. He asked me, &amp;ldquo;Daddy, do you want to hear a scary story?&amp;rdquo; I of course said I did. After which I was delighted to hear the story of the ghost with one black eye. What impressed me the most was his sense of theatrics while telling the story. He had different voices that he would use for the different characters, and whenever he was getting to a &amp;ldquo;scary&amp;rdquo; part, he would whisper very quietly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mission Accomplished</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/mission-accomplished/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2005 19:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/mission-accomplished/</guid>
      <description>I’m sure I’ve been more proud of Ethan, but I can’t remember when. Tonight Ethan showed me that he can snap his fingers. About a week ago he showed me that he could whistle… I think it was a couple of weeks ago that he had asked me on separate occasions how to whistle and how to snap your fingers. I showed him what I knew, but ultimately, it is hard to teach somebody how to do something like that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Physical Achievements</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/physical-achievements/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2005 20:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/physical-achievements/</guid>
      <description>In the past couple of days, Ethan has started doing a couple of remarkable things (in my opinion). He has a pair of roller blades that he got from our friends Maylee and Jason last Christmas. A couple of days ago he decided he was going to put them on, and now he&amp;rsquo;s skating all over the house. It&amp;rsquo;s really fun to watch him skate from wall to table to stairs all over the first floor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Snow</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/first-snow/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2005 09:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/first-snow/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday marked the first snow of the season. Unlike most years when it snows for the first time, this snow stayed on the ground. Ethan was so excited this morning to see snow. His eyes lit up and he exclaimed that &amp;ldquo;it&amp;rsquo;s almost Christmas!&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Badger/Hawkeye Game</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/badgerhawkeye-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2005 21:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/badgerhawkeye-game/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday we went to the Badger/Hawkeye game, a thing we intend to do each year. Todd and Theresa, my uncle and aunt who live near Madison, offerred to watch Ethan for the day. He had a fine time, and the Hawkeyes won the game much to many a Madisonion&amp;rsquo;s chagrin. Ethan has always gotten along very well with Julia, the older of Todd&amp;rsquo;s two children, but lately he has been doing more and getting along very well with John, Julia&amp;rsquo;s younger brother.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Funny Things</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/funny-things/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2005 14:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/funny-things/</guid>
      <description>Ethan has been saying some funny things, lately. First, since it&amp;rsquo;s been Halloween season, he has seen the Grim Reaper walking around on TV and on the streets. He has been calling him the &amp;ldquo;Grim Reefer&amp;rdquo; however.
The other funny thing he has done lately is to sing the song Tootsie Roll. There&amp;rsquo;s just something funny about a 4 year old singing &amp;ldquo;Let me see your tootsie role&amp;rdquo; to me&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kalahari in the Dells</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/kalahari-in-the-dells/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2005 22:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/kalahari-in-the-dells/</guid>
      <description>We went to Wisconsin Dells with the Abholds on Thursday afternoon. My parents obtained a free night stay since they were treated badly at the Kalahari. They gave us the free night stay, so we traded it in for $129 off of a suite. Not a bad deal.
If you’re not familiar with the Kalahari, it is a huge hotel and conference center with a large indoor and outdoor water park attached.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Halloween</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/happy-halloween/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2005 19:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/reclaimed/happy-halloween/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m going to call this year Ethan&amp;rsquo;s first Halloween. Sure he has had four other Halloweens, but this one was special. It was the first time that he actively participated and enjoyed himself. He is growing so fast it is unbelievable, and I don&amp;rsquo;t mean he is getting tall. Instead of being afraid to go to any of the houses, he actively pointed out the houses that he wanted to go to based on what kind of candy he thought they would have.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>