<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>College on The Hydrant</title>
    <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/tags/college/</link>
    <description>Recent content in College on The Hydrant</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2020 09:03:44 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://dogsbuttbrew.com/tags/college/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>College - Year 2</title>
      <link>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/09/college-year-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2020 09:03:44 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://dogsbuttbrew.com/post/2020/09/college-year-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Ahh, COVID. I guess life goes on, or we try to do so, anyway. Ethan, after spending the last 5+ months at home (bonus Ethan time for us!) has now completed his transfer to Colorado State University and we have moved him into his dwelling for the upcoming school year! Even though this is Ethan&amp;rsquo;s second year of school, this year seemed almost worse in some ways than moving him in last year. Last year he was going to Regis, which on a good traffic day was only about a 30 minute drive from home. He had access to the city bus and train system to get him home whenever he liked, and we were pretty &amp;ldquo;comfortable&amp;rdquo; with the school. Not to mention, after last summer, we were kind of ready for him to leave (sorry Ethan)! This year he will be attending a big state school which we haven&amp;rsquo;t had an opportunity to really visit or connect with it at all due to the pandemic. Also, it&amp;rsquo;s a bit further away, 90 minutes in good traffic. Given all that, it just &lt;em&gt;felt&lt;/em&gt; different. Quinton seemed to actually care and notice that it was happening this time around. At one point he asked Jenny and I in an accusatory way why we weren&amp;rsquo;t more upset about Ethan leaving! It was kind of nice having him around for the last 5-6 months&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
